[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2010-06-30 02:42:21
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:CLANNAD BD 24 gb
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,youyuan,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: OPC,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,3,0,2,15,15,10,134
Style: EDC,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H22FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H66880000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,3,0,2,15,15,10,134
Style: staff,simhei,16,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H66FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,4,30,30,10,1
Style: title2,simhei,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: title1,simhei,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H908CB497,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: notice,simhei,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,0,3,3,30,30,10,1
Style: In2en,Verdana,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H28000000,0,0,0,0,100,85,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,8,8,6,0
Style: in2cn,simhei,16,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H28000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,30,30,6,134
Style: up,simhei,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H66000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----OP-----
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.85,0:02:12.70,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(289,210)\fad(400,0)}澄空学园
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.82,0:00:49.35,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}做了一个梦  一个晶莹剔透的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.31,0:00:56.29,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}一个缥缈却又永恒的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.98,0:01:02.74,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}如清风般轻声的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.58,0:01:09.59,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在高空呼唤着我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.40,0:01:16.28,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}若是就此飞向天空
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.28,0:01:22.97,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无论何处都能到达
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.49,0:01:29.84,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在那牵系在一起的双手间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.02,0:01:36.43,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}若能寻觅到那小小的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.78,0:01:43.08,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在光芒中摇曳着的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.42,0:01:49.33,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所有话语和思念
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.54,0:01:55.85,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}一定毫无保留地
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.12,0:02:08.21,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,2000)}传达给远方的你
Comment: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---title---
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.70,0:03:30.40,title1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,0)\pos(322,285)\3c&H7ba285&}另一个世界\N\N智代篇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:03.00,title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(600,0)\pos(320,300)}另一个世界\N\N智代篇
Comment: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---ED---
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.78,0:20:33.55,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}The place changes and goes. Like a wind, like clouds.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.70,0:20:47.35,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Like the traces of the heart, no halt at the places.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.35,0:20:58.85,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}The place is so far away, be far apart.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.85,0:21:11.90,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}people's hand does not reach, so merely has the worship.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.71,0:21:24.20,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}The place is a lofty lord. can't meet nobody put on.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.76,0:21:37.14,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}We will lose the place. so lofty which changes.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.17,0:21:49.09,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Not all were desired. However, we're never sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.98,0:22:03.66,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}still, there is still the place. far away. far away.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.92,0:22:43.59,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}The place buried in deep snow. like the collapsing castle.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.59,0:22:57.04,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}like the head of the shade, figure will be thrown away.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.30,0:23:08.69,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}The place is a lofty lord. can't meet nobody put on.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.11,0:23:25.32,In2en,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}still, there is still the place. far away. far away.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.78,0:20:33.55,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}那里不断变换  如风  又似云
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.70,0:20:47.35,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}好似心底的涟漪  不会停留一处
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.35,0:20:58.85,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}那里如此遥远  远离我们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.85,0:21:11.90,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}远在伸手难及之处  只有虔诚信奉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.71,0:21:24.20,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}那里就如崇高的神明  难以企及
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.76,0:21:37.14,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}终将失去  变得遥不可及的那里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.17,0:21:49.09,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}这一切并非所愿  但我们从不悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.98,0:22:03.66,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}只因那里依然存在  虽然遥不可及
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.92,0:22:43.59,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}那里好似城堡的废墟  埋藏在雪底
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.59,0:22:57.04,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}更像是死灵的首级  躯体早已消逝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.30,0:23:08.69,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}那里就如崇高的神明  难以企及
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.11,0:23:25.32,in2cn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}它依然在那里  远远  远远的
Comment: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---TEXT----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.12,0:00:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋也 起床了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.23,0:00:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子痛 要休息
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.30,0:00:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一周肚子要痛几次啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.37,0:00:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是告诉过你不用特意过来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.20,0:00:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能放着你不管 毕竟我是你的女朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.31,0:00:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们分手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.89,0:00:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是玩笑也请你不要说这种话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.87,0:00:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的会让人伤心的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.31,0:00:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别摆出这种表情嘛 是我不对
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 今天不是学生会长选举的日子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.76,0:00:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打起精神来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.98,0:00:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊 用笑脸来迎接吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.77,0:02:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就要公布了吧 不在自己班里待着可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.93,0:02:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你在一起更能让我安心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.91,0:02:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟智代交往已经有一个月了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.78,0:02:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说发展成现在这样的契机其实也没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.80,0:02:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迟到 翘课 在街上闲逛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.22,0:02:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这样的每一天中 与智代相识
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.62,0:02:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知何时变得亲近了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.54,0:02:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等回过神来时已经变成恋人关系了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.60,0:02:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在公布学生会成员的选举结果
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.06,0:02:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学生会长是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.07,0:03:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂上智代同学 533票当选
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.18,0:03:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了 智代
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.39,0:03:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了你支持我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.03,0:03:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这并不代表着结束吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.36,0:03:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的最终目标是保住那片樱花树吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.49,0:03:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.29,0:03:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋也 从今往后你也愿意待在我的身边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.70,0:03:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还用问吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.85,0:03:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你当选
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.03,0:03:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂上前辈 恭喜你当选
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.52,0:03:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.53,0:03:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直相信你会当选的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.51,0:03:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18}以后我们也会一直支持你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.71,0:03:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过还真是个不可思议的组合啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.40,0:03:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游手好闲三年级学生二人组外加学生会长
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.41,0:03:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所处的世界不是完全不同的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.99,0:03:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是有名的不良学生吗 为什么会跟坂上同学在一起呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.49,0:03:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道吗 智代同学好像跟那些家伙关系很好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.08,0:04:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说 学生会长今天还会来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.53,0:04:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那自然是会来的啦 毕竟每天都有来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.93,0:04:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可真是悠闲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.47,0:04:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.33,0:04:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好好想想吧 在当选了学生会长的现在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.65,0:04:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会比之前更加唠叨不停的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.99,0:04:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在走廊上奔跑什么的 点心 饭 茶要三角进餐什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.99,0:04:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs16}三角进餐:日本的传统习惯，进餐时将各类食物\N以一定的顺序吃，如必须先吃面包，再吃牛奶，最后吃点心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.69,0:04:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想当那么乖的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.08,0:04:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了 出那么大声
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.90,0:04:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智代 去你的！ 我偏偏就先吃蔬菜
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.85,0:04:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs16\fad(100,0)}(极品蔬菜王子）
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.88,0:04:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在说些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.91,0:04:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个笨蛋嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.90,0:04:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.87,0:04:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在那边自己就肯定了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.41,0:04:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天是带这些过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.92,0:04:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为还有学生会的召集工作呢 那么再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.14,0:04:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就忙起来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.62,0:04:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连我那份也有做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.94,0:04:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这样一来就分不清哪份是谁的…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.92,0:04:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好分了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.42,0:04:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 到底跟坂上同学是什么关系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.44,0:04:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢 不过好像关系很好的样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.25,0:05:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是在交往吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.55,0:05:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.67,0:05:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 小声点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.99,0:05:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看什么看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.86,0:05:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.04,0:05:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟中午也很忙的样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.95,0:05:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再等一会儿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.42,0:05:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 朋也 很抱歉你先回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.35,0:05:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智代！？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.29,0:05:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忘记还有关于学园祭相关的会议要开了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.58,0:05:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概会忙到晚上 所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.46,0:05:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长 广播装置不能私用…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.98,0:05:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点关掉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.67,0:05:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的女朋友可真够大胆的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.83,0:05:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上也有人质疑很多人是不是凑热闹才投的票
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.69,0:05:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看过坂上同学在之前学校的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.13,0:05:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这么说不太合适 不过确实是引发过不少问题呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.22,0:05:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那都是以前的事了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.77,0:05:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实如此
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.74,0:05:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过坂上同学在本校也已经引发过数次骚动了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.90,0:06:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一点毋庸置疑吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.72,0:06:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有要强制你们怎么做的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.54,0:06:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想提醒你要有点自觉并好好注意一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.62,0:06:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟你是本校的学生会长呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.57,0:06:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.41,0:06:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师会在意也是没办法的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.49,0:06:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也知道有人在背后议论我们的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.13,0:06:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 那也得看我们自己
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.11,0:06:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错吧 朋也
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.55,0:06:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.80,0:06:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.06,0:06:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园祭啊 我忘得一干二净了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.04,0:06:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说这段时间也会很忙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.05,0:06:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去哪儿玩玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.10,0:06:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放松啦 放松
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.42,0:06:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家的时候去哪儿逛逛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.71,0:06:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你很闲的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.81,0:07:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这副表情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.64,0:07:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等学园祭结束后 智代也会稍微清闲一点的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.98,0:07:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时候又能三个人一起玩啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.28,0:07:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能那样就好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.64,0:07:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过对我而言 能不看到她反而更好一些
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.35,0:07:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说这些了 去向那两个人搭讪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.53,0:07:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊看啊 那个马尾女孩…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.12,0:07:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你在听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.64,0:07:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很热呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.81,0:08:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 如果被发现的话就会被强行带回学生会室
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.09,0:08:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这么忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.84,0:08:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 现在也正在巡逻呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.16,0:08:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太勉强了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.08,0:08:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没勉强 因为我想跟朋也待在一起所以才来这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.52,0:08:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近因为很忙 也没时间跟你在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.98,0:08:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等学园祭结束后 终于要正式地开展保留樱花树的运动了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.39,0:08:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许会变得比现在还要忙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.16,0:08:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.72,0:08:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂上
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.65,0:08:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在找你呢 同窗会的会长们来打招呼了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.29,0:08:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请马上回来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.77,0:08:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能等我把这冰淇淋吃完吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.78,0:08:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经让他们等了三十分钟了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.65,0:09:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有请他们协助保留樱花树的运动
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.60,0:09:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是得罪了他们会很不好办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.27,0:09:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.62,0:09:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.92,0:09:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.71,0:09:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是冈崎朋也吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.07,0:09:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二年级的小子竟然不用敬语啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.36,0:09:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有注意到 自己名声已经不小了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.84,0:09:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是不良的游手好闲之徒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.14,0:09:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你是坂上智代的男朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.27,0:09:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前就想要跟你说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.33,0:09:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你不要再纠缠她了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.83,0:09:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 你在吃飞醋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.02,0:09:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对呢 应该说是感兴趣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.94,0:09:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为她是 往高处走的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.92,0:09:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她处事认真 也很努力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.71,0:09:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后也能够往更高的层次迈进
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.12,0:09:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就是这一类的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.00,0:10:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在拖她的后腿 大家都是这么认为的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.03,0:10:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 想打架吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.19,0:10:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你自己不也明白的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.46,0:10:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己没法为她做任何事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.41,0:10:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要走了 因为必须要去帮坂上的忙才行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.53,0:10:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂上同学非常优秀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.62,0:10:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名声也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.08,0:10:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而与此不相称地
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.50,0:10:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她却和某个把迟到旷课当作家常便饭的同学混在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.07,0:10:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了联系那位同学而私自使用校内广播
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.86,0:10:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在学园祭中离开自己的岗位 和那位同学勾搭在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.01,0:10:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.18,0:10:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是她惹出的问题 就必定和冈崎你有关
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.86,0:11:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋也
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.49,0:11:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.37,0:11:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.40,0:11:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 有紧急情况
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.50,0:11:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.97,0:11:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会很花时间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.96,0:11:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不清楚 大概是吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.61,0:11:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 不要介意
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.79,0:11:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.60,0:11:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原因就在你身上
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.19,0:11:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她为了留下那条樱花步道而四处奔走的事 你知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.08,0:11:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这又怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.99,0:11:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托来做声援的老前辈似乎听到个不好的传闻
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.29,0:11:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人看见坂上智代早上和她的男朋友一起从屋子里走出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.21,0:11:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 她只是来叫我起床罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.67,0:11:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算这是事实 但那人可是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.05,0:11:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成恶评也是自然的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.67,0:11:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂上她是学生会长
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.08,0:11:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站在那个立场上 就必须成为其他同学的榜样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.06,0:12:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这样的人惹出问题 就会对运动造成障碍
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.23,0:12:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你到底明不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.49,0:12:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己在与一个什么样的人交往
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.76,0:12:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己到底是个什么样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.07,0:12:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是什么大问题
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.39,0:12:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正误会也解开了 没什么关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.61,0:12:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这事已经过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.35,0:12:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.11,0:12:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 都因为你呆呆的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.60,0:12:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智代
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.62,0:12:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.69,0:12:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们分手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.08,0:12:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们 果然还是分手比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.85,0:12:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说过不要开这种玩笑…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.44,0:12:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有你自己的目标吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.99,0:13:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果和我在一起的话 可能就无法达成了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.21,0:13:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.83,0:13:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.14,0:13:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.56,0:13:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.89,0:13:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.67,0:13:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.63,0:13:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 不能去看的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.35,0:13:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果 如果离开了我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.20,0:13:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会很困扰的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.99,0:13:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果离开了我的话 每天早上谁去叫你起床
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.98,0:13:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁给你去准备便当
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.96,0:13:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有考试的学习 该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.81,0:13:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.78,0:13:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.32,0:13:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算没有你 我也能做好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.60,0:13:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.03,0:13:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有你在身边的话 我就会变得只想依靠你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.03,0:13:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.88,0:13:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你 想和你在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.90,0:13:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智代…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.71,0:13:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你的感情 并不是恋情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.99,0:14:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个很随便的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.33,0:14:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智代 去回应那些对你的期待吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.12,0:14:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 让我以后
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.43,0:14:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以想起「我曾和这么厉害的家伙交往过啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.06,0:14:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不好 智代
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.79,0:14:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.26,0:14:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向你保证
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.41,0:14:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能 能和我这样的女孩交往…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.71,0:14:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.86,0:14:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保重
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.47,0:14:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.50,0:15:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你们会一路走到结婚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.67,0:15:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪会有这么简单的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.25,0:15:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 还以为她在遇到这种抉择时
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.76,0:15:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起学生会 还是会选择你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.46,0:15:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.00,0:15:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过离开了智代妹妹 朋也君是不是又要变回废柴了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.53,0:16:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 第二问是例一的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.39,0:16:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,推广应用
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.47,0:16:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说了吗 智代同学在全国模拟考拿了第四名
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.90,0:16:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前段时间的志愿活动也被表彰了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.76,0:16:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还听说要去交换留学呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.37,0:16:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的要看了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.07,0:16:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随你便了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.96,0:16:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 我主要是考虑到你的心情嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.45,0:16:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.96,0:17:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真啰嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.43,0:17:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.76,0:17:06.94,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I bite the bullet in order to prevent the loneliness.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.57,0:17:11.09,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,If we hadn't know the row of cherry trees would have been gone,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.33,0:17:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说哪国话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.39,0:17:13.92,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,we wouldn't have found fortune given by them.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.41,0:17:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是在说那些樱花树的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.22,0:17:18.79,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Because we all did nothing,except for making the grade by might and main.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.76,0:17:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是之前在录像里看到的那东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.11,0:17:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.35,0:17:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们曾和这么厉害的女孩子是朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.77,0:17:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.79,0:17:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很忙碌的样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.93,0:17:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.34,0:17:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那脑袋是啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.97,0:18:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑啥 我自己照镜子的时候也觉得别扭死了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.72,0:18:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也没办法啊 又不可能一头金发去面试
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.65,0:18:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 可能不适合你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.09,0:18:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 也不要因此就放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.02,0:18:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总会找到适合自己的工作的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.91,0:18:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易找到的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.58,0:18:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是在这个小镇里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.24,0:18:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕能稍微远离这里一点也好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.96,0:18:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们中的大多数人将在升学后 慢慢步入社会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.86,0:18:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到属于自己的重要工作
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.84,0:18:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们学校至今的…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.83,0:18:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 真的要走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.61,0:18:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一会儿还有送别会呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.40,0:18:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去了也没什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.34,0:18:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一会儿我会去你房间的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.38,0:18:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.68,0:19:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.27,0:19:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.09,0:19:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.19,0:19:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你很久了 想要向你报告一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.62,0:19:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.88,0:19:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的樱花树保住了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.46,0:19:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于定下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.61,0:19:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.92,0:19:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好长
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.55,0:19:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个不容妥协的目标
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.86,0:19:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于实现了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.14,0:19:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦想实现了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.91,0:19:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 也有因此而失去的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.63,0:19:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本应能和喜欢的人一起度过的好几个月时间
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.92,0:19:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.72,0:20:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也一样 比以前更加喜欢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.93,0:20:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是都那么长时间没说过话了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.11,0:20:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.81,0:20:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我在看着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.17,0:20:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在看着你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.44,0:20:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算离开了我 你也做得井井有条
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.08,0:20:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天都按时去上课
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.43,0:20:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点一点地在努力着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.32,0:20:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过便当就没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.35,0:20:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就业问题也尽自己所能努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.63,0:20:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但果然因为在校评价不好 吃了很多闭门羹
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.96,0:20:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而 最近也终于定下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.79,0:20:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一家小公司 搞废物回收的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.34,0:20:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 地点倒是挺近的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.83,0:20:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟就在这个小镇里面 上班会轻松点
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.23,0:20:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这些了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.17,0:20:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.64,0:20:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过去都和你说过些什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.84,0:21:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是用怎样的口吻 是怎么笑过的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.76,0:21:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能和你一起前进
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.87,0:21:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明年也将毕业
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.10,0:21:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会离开这个小镇 前往远方
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.88,0:21:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能前往那遥远的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.84,0:21:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我却不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.08,0:21:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将会一直生活在这个小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.39,0:21:24.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直生活在同一个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.50,0:21:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是这样的人而已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.52,0:21:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 我就前往你的身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.52,0:21:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前往那里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.67,0:21:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 你应该可以去更好的地方的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.34,0:21:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去一所好的大学 邂逅许多的人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.26,0:21:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被赋予重望 然后回报那些期待…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.63,0:21:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还能去更高的层次啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.56,0:21:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比在我这种人的身边更加…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.51,0:21:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说什么「我这种人」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.13,0:21:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说什么「我这种人」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.09,0:21:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的选择
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.93,0:22:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起老师的评价和考试成绩所堆积起来的高度
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.34,0:22:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说 这拥有更大的价值
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.25,0:22:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我要前往朋也的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.63,0:22:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竭尽全力前往那里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.55,0:22:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底谁才是前辈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.97,0:22:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要前往
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.43,0:22:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有点迟了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.07,0:22:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要前往你的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.44,0:22:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋也 朋也
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.57,0:23:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 到底怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.58,0:23:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 不要哭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.04,0:23:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要哭…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
