[Script Info]
Title:Steins;Gate 01 BD gb
Original Script:SumiSora & CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: up,微软雅黑,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00000040,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,6,30,30,10,134
Style: mail,微软雅黑,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,4,30,30,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGHSGothic-W5,21,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,8,128
Style: OPCN,方正大黑_GBK,22,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFKaiSho_U-Md,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,7,128
Style: EDCN,方正楷体_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.62,0:01:09.62,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(580,335)}起源与终结的序章
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.47,0:00:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇宙虽有其起源  却没有终结
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.75,0:00:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,——无限
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.25,0:00:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星球虽也有起源  却因其自身之力走向毁灭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.28,0:00:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,——有限
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.67,0:00:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有睿智之人才是最为愚蠢者
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.12,0:00:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,历史上不胜枚举
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.86,0:00:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也可以说是给那些抵抗者们的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.23,0:00:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神的最后通牒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.10,0:00:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.46,0:00:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.71,0:01:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在开始潜入会场
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.89,0:01:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,EL PSY CONGROO
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.71,0:01:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人很少啊  果然是「{\1c&0000E0&}机关{\r}」插手来干扰了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.36,0:01:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要举行什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.51,0:01:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你连这也不知道就跟来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.34,0:01:39.68,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（中钵博士时间机器发明成功记者招待会）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.69,0:01:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间机器  好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.19,0:01:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中钵博士抢在我们这些研究员之前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.26,0:01:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,促成了这世纪大发明的发表会
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.17,0:01:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让我好好听听他的高见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.25,0:01:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地震吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.63,0:01:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是上面吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.59,0:02:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.60,0:02:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是为了这个把我叫来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.78,0:02:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个系列已经剩得不多了但是真由氏…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.61,0:02:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,100元硬币用完了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.15,0:02:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别撒娇了真由理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.20,0:02:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是青梅竹马我也不会借钱
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.51,0:02:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就让你见识下人生的残酷
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.32,0:02:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊  没有涂装啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.49,0:02:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金…金属
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.14,0:03:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是金属啊  「金属呜帕」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.12,0:03:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很稀有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.39,0:03:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  非常的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.38,0:03:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  就给你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.65,0:03:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗  小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.37,0:03:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是「凤凰院凶真」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.04,0:03:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.77,0:03:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了是凤凰院凶真…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.94,0:03:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来在8楼大厅  中钵博士的招待会即将召开
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.15,0:03:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入场自由  接下来…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.50,0:03:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间机器的基本构造请参阅分发的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.01,0:03:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里我只解释一下基础的理论
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.08,0:03:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金属呜帕好像弄丢了  我去找找看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.00,0:03:45.10,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止世界上的科学家们对于时间旅行…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.85,0:03:50.88,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  只是主要的理论就存在11种
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.20,0:03:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于时间机器的基本构造…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.23,0:03:53.86,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,综合各种可能性和其原理
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.25,0:03:56.48,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从各种角度考虑得出的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.85,0:04:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.51,0:04:03.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了突然地
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.91,0:04:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.49,0:04:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的时间机器理论是什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.88,0:04:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「克尔黑洞」「世界线」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.44,0:04:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不全都是{\1c&0000E0&}约翰·提托{\r}的拷贝吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.88,0:04:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提托自称是时间旅行者
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.58,0:04:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2000年就把这些理论在网上发表过了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.61,0:04:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别告诉我你不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.32,0:04:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真无礼  我当然知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.03,0:04:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把我和那骗人的理论混为一谈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.32,0:04:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就给我们说明一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.99,0:04:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于你的和提托的时间机器理论的区别
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.19,0:04:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.63,0:04:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提托吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.02,0:04:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来约翰·提托的书里也写着类似的东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.11,0:04:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.80,0:04:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的台词
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.76,0:04:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.30,0:04:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才  你有什么话想说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.58,0:04:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.48,0:04:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.70,0:04:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,15分钟左右之前
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.33,0:05:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说些什么莫名…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.14,0:05:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑…红莉栖？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.64,0:05:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前在「科学」杂志上发表了论文的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.45,0:05:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道得还挺多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.37,0:05:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是哪个大学研究室里的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.66,0:05:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.06,0:05:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是「机关」派来的特务
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.89,0:05:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机关？  那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.59,0:05:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是有事想问…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.05,0:05:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有回答你的必要
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.38,0:05:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我  被机关的特务抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.37,0:05:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  是牧濑红莉栖
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.57,0:05:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在跟谁说话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.51,0:05:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.16,0:05:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边我会想办法逃脱…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.26,0:05:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？  电源…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.71,0:05:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.93,0:05:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就特别地告诉你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.77,0:05:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是除了我以外的人碰了的话就会自动切断电源的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.07,0:05:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特殊任务用的手机
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.46,0:05:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.16,0:05:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  自言自语么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.14,0:05:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就长话短说了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.03,0:05:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你想要对我说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.00,0:06:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,15分钟之前
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.92,0:06:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是要想说什么的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.40,0:06:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一副被逼得走投无路的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.51,0:06:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是看穿一切
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.68,0:06:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天才少女哟  下次见面时就是敌人了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.80,0:06:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.03,0:06:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.87,0:06:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.08,0:06:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.47,0:06:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见过我？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.08,0:06:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.33,0:06:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理  你在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.02,0:06:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发了短信的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.69,0:06:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金属呜帕不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.97,0:06:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明还写了名字拿着的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.47,0:06:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄丢了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.73,0:07:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.89,0:07:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.14,0:07:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金属呜帕在网拍可是能卖1万左右呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.30,0:07:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1…万？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.82,0:07:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去找
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.94,0:07:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们实验室现在正是资金短缺中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.58,0:07:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算找到了我也不会卖的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.67,0:07:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有1万的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.14,0:07:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就可以筹集新的未来道具的部件了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.19,0:07:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了不会卖的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.79,0:07:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.97,0:07:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先到外面去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.67,0:07:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.73,0:07:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有谁在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.31,0:08:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑…红莉栖
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.96,0:08:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.72,0:08:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有人被捅了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.34,0:08:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.71,0:08:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.03,0:08:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  脸色苍白哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.98,0:08:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死…人了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.30,0:08:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在8楼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.04,0:09:10.64,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(250,33)\frz16}阿至
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.04,0:09:10.64,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,140)\frz16}出事了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.04,0:09:10.64,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(420,240)\frz16}牧濑红莉栖  被什么人\N给捅了一刀好像…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.56,0:09:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.60,0:09:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.47,0:09:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘟嘟噜
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.55,0:09:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.47,0:10:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这到底是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.66,0:10:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.77,0:10:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人呢  人怎么都消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.17,0:10:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.99,0:10:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是消失了吧  刚才还在这里的人全都
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.37,0:10:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从眼前…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.27,0:10:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.17,0:10:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会不知道  你也看见了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.91,0:10:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.73,0:10:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.41,0:10:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有看见
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.03,0:10:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.56,0:12:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！  那边的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.81,0:12:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看得见我们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.31,0:12:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不回答
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.18,0:12:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的就是屏幕对面一脸呆相的你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.83,0:12:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也罢  这里就是未来道具研究所
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.54,0:12:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先介绍一下所属研究员吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.95,0:12:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是实验室成员No.001
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.81,0:12:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实验室创始人兼疯狂科学家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.31,0:12:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本人  凤凰院凶真
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.99,0:12:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明叫「小冈伦」比较可爱的说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.57,0:12:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.34,0:12:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部伦太郎只是为了隐匿身份的假名
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.64,0:12:39.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着是实验室成员No.002
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.96,0:12:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兴趣是制作Cosplay的红一点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.54,0:12:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,椎名真由理
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.84,0:12:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘟嘟噜  我是真由氏☆
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.19,0:12:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着是实验室成员No.003
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.35,0:12:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级嘿客  桥田至
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.07,0:12:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是嘿客是黑客吧常考
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.72,0:12:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以上三人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.55,0:13:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  差不多该放弃了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.15,0:13:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别对500日元买来的处理品软件抱期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.07,0:13:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我听好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.46,0:13:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的实验室就在沿着中央大道往前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.11,0:13:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在末广町车站的十字路口向左转入仓前路
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.45,0:13:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在下个红绿灯之前的小道中的杂居大楼里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.62,0:13:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未来道具研究所的目的是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.79,0:13:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借由世界的支配构造的变革
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.97,0:13:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生产将其卷入混沌的发明
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.87,0:13:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.08,0:13:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白的话  就把你的秘密如实招来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.40,0:13:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  从羊驼先生看来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.11,0:13:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏们是不是就像游戏一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.26,0:13:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙根本就没有是现实还是游戏的想法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.64,0:13:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那阿至喜欢的二次元的女孩子也是那样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.77,0:13:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那得另当别论
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.03,0:13:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那些女孩都是我的老婆
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.19,0:13:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至的老婆的话题都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.89,0:13:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是啊  是个很有意思的主题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.80,0:13:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如我们是屏幕里的存在的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.06,0:14:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有能够确认的方法吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.39,0:14:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.99,0:14:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即答啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.33,0:14:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  你这种议论毫无意义
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.57,0:14:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑关于对抗机关
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.82,0:14:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打破世界的支配构造的方法要有意义得多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.44,0:14:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又开始了厨二病
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.69,0:14:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乙！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.69,0:14:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx80\fscy80}辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.74,0:14:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴  超级嘿客
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.61,0:14:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是疯狂科学家凤凰院——
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.68,0:14:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.32,0:14:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是设定的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.78,0:14:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的   阿至
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.23,0:14:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要只自顾自  别人的话也要好好听啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.44,0:14:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的「只有不想被你这么说」原来是这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.59,0:14:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来  报道的直升机好像到现场了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.86,0:14:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天12点左右
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.24,0:14:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在东京千代田区秋叶原发现的疑似人造卫星的坠落物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.38,0:14:51.21,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请看  从这里的地面看去  也是相当巨大的物体…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.06,0:14:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…究竟是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.89,0:14:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今早  我和真由理为了去看中钵博士的招待会
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.63,0:15:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从实验室前往广播会馆
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.16,0:15:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是当我回过神来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.13,0:15:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人造卫星就坠落在了那里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.14,0:15:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.59,0:15:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.84,0:15:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  在电视上看到坠落的报道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.14,0:15:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦就说着「机关终于开始行动了」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.74,0:15:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一起来看了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.78,0:15:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中止？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.95,0:15:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上小冈伦不是生气地说「那个博士居然临阵脱逃了」的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.21,0:15:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是中钵博士的招待会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.35,0:15:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12点在广播会馆举行的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.27,0:15:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了就没有举行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.19,0:15:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是挺好的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.42,0:15:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,举行了的话小冈伦大概就成了人造卫星的肉垫了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.74,0:15:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这记忆上的差别
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.88,0:15:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是「机关」的记忆操作
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.27,0:15:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.47,0:15:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,325)\fscy80\fscx80}Steins  Gate
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.47,0:15:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是「命运石之门」的选择
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.05,0:15:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是设定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.98,0:15:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那个斯坦因什么的开始就莫名其妙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.28,0:16:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至  给我{\1c&0000E0&}未来道具1号机{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.43,0:16:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羊驼先生生气了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.29,0:16:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.99,0:16:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为换了频道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.81,0:16:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的Mr.布朗  居然让我用劣质产品
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.72,0:16:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是白给的东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.79,0:16:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至！  搬起电视机！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.47,0:16:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果断拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.37,0:16:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为今天很热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.29,0:16:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说别以为胖子就一定有力气哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.13,0:16:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是该自豪的地方吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.19,0:16:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mr.…布朗…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.35,0:16:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是告诉你叫我天王寺先生了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.33,0:16:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想拜托你尽快…修理
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.30,0:16:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经弄坏了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.66,0:16:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是  对布朗管的爱不够啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.57,0:16:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,修理费一千日元
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.31,0:16:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说有错的话  该是你把劣质产品给我…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.07,0:16:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对房东该用这种口气吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.41,0:16:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免去修理费吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.36,0:17:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小真由理  不要再和这家伙在一起了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.94,0:17:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是真由氏是小冈伦的人质
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.41,0:17:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人质啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.72,0:17:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里也坏掉了啊  修理费两千日元
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.57,0:17:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.15,0:17:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不爽的话就搬回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.71,0:17:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.64,0:17:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.05,0:17:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机关似乎终于连那个光头和尚也拉拢了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.95,0:17:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我遭到了妨碍行为
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.72,0:17:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.44,0:17:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦真是喜欢{\1c&0000E0&}乐倍{\r}呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.94,0:17:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是被选中之人的智慧饮品呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.46,0:17:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蝉鸣声  真厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.17,0:18:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至  既然机关派Mr.布朗对我们进行妨碍
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.67,0:18:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就已经刻不容缓了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.40,0:18:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻开始实施那个计划
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.39,0:18:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划？  是啥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.80,0:18:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划就是计划
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.31,0:18:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了未来道具8号机投入实战以外还会有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.15,0:18:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电话微波炉（暂定）啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.39,0:18:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  微波炉投入实战是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.37,0:18:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你的交往也差不多也有三年半了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.95,0:18:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中二年级的时候因为班级不同而几乎没怎么说过话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.71,0:18:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以实际上只有两年吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.40,0:18:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些小事情都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.86,0:18:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  我们相处很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.36,0:18:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也差不多该能跟得上我的话了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.53,0:18:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那·是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.67,0:18:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不·可·能·的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.28,0:18:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  还要再试试吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.05,0:18:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.91,0:18:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理  拿香蕉来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.89,0:18:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要做胶化香蕉吗  太浪费了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.30,0:18:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么小气的话是赢不了机关的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.41,0:18:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢不了也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.35,0:19:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊  香蕉可是真由氏买来的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.96,0:19:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.69,0:19:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是RENG  电话微波炉（暂定）
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.98,0:19:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里可以进行时间设定
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.52,0:19:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请在按#号键后输入想要加热的秒数
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.30,0:19:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,120#
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.90,0:19:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很漂亮的转盘吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.45,0:19:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和平时不同这是在倒转啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.44,0:19:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒转？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.27,0:19:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定这里有着重大的意义
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.94,0:19:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑到量子的问题  再导入{\1c&0000E0&}洪特规则{\r}…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.20,0:19:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有是有…才怪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.26,0:19:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.14,0:19:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.40,0:19:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.83,0:19:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既不会变热也不会变冷
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.20,0:19:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏的多汁炸鸡No.1变成糊状…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.36,0:19:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(370,325)\fscy80\fscx80}Steins  Gate
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.36,0:19:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之肯定发生了什么和「命运石之门」有关的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.64,0:19:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是那个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.95,0:19:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至  要不要尝尝这香蕉…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.03,0:19:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.31,0:19:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就将这荣誉让给真由理吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.23,0:20:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.53,0:20:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胶化香蕉又黏又软的  也没有味道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.96,0:20:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你尝过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.82,0:20:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.62,0:20:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「你的香蕉软软的呢」说说看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.33,0:20:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  你的香蕉软…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.02,0:20:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让她说啊你这变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.96,0:20:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,融化了…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.17,0:20:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从实验室出来十分钟还不到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.45,0:20:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天从距离上来说到菲伊莉斯炭那里就是极限喽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.86,0:20:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要能在「MayQueen+Nyan2」开就好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.82,0:20:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能在女仆咖啡店开大学讲座
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.77,0:20:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不关系到学分  就绝对不来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.11,0:20:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉快
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.88,0:20:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.21,0:20:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人造卫星掉下来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.79,0:20:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还在说这事？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.69,0:20:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至你不去广播会馆看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.35,0:21:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正围观者太多根本就看不到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.02,0:21:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过反正在{\1c&0000E0&}@channel{\r}可以看到Snake的直播
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.19,0:21:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  暂时中止作业
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.49,0:21:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是{\1c&0000E0&}祭典{\r}？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.37,0:21:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  那个时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.14,0:21:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手机借我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.02,0:21:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.02,0:21:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少废话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.66,0:21:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不允许侵犯个人隐私绝对…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.71,0:21:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你发过短信吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.54,0:21:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于牧濑红莉栖被捅了的短信
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.50,0:21:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上星期发来的那个？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.43,0:21:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上星期？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.52,0:21:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还分了3条让人超不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.36,0:21:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.15,0:21:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收信日期  7月23日12点56分
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.37,0:21:36.98,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(400,200)}牧濑红莉栖
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.98,0:21:37.60,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(400,200)}被什么人给捅了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.60,0:21:38.07,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(400,200)}一刀好像
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.58,0:21:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.22,0:21:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上星期…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.47,0:21:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发信记录
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.78,0:21:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有…  今天是几号？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.61,0:21:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2…28号
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.38,0:21:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.13,0:21:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短信…被发送到了过去
Comment: 0,0:02:13.19,0:02:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---OP---
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.71,0:10:52.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}数十億もの　鼓動の数さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.03,0:10:59.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたには　瞬き程度の些事な等級
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.77,0:11:04.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}過去に囚われて　未来も嘆くも
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.73,0:11:10.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}塵一つ　誤算を許さぬ必然
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.82,0:11:16.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『無限』に広がる夢も　描く未来も
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.10,0:11:22.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕達に許された　虚栄の権利
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.81,0:11:28.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『有限』それは二つの　針が示す
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.05,0:11:33.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷な約定と　選択へ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.54,0:11:35.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.97,0:11:42.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だからいま　１秒ごとに　世界線を超えて
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.73,0:11:47.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君のその笑顔　守りたいのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.67,0:11:54.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そしてまた　悲しみの無い　時間のループへと
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.71,0:11:57.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}飲み込まれてゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.26,0:12:01.04,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独の観測者
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.71,0:10:52.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}连同数十亿的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.03,0:10:59.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}对你来说  不过是转瞬即逝的琐事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.77,0:11:04.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}被过去所囚困  未来和悲叹
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.73,0:11:10.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}微尘般的误算  亦不允许的必然
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.82,0:11:16.85,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无限扩展的梦想  描绘的未来也
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.10,0:11:22.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我们所被赋予的  虚荣的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.81,0:11:28.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}有限  那即是两根指针所标示
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.05,0:11:33.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷的约定和选择
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.54,0:11:35.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an2}Hacking to the Gate ——
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.97,0:11:42.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所以现在  越过每一秒的世界线
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.73,0:11:47.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想守护你的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.67,0:11:54.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}于是进入没有悲伤的  时间的轮回
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.71,0:11:57.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}逐渐被吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.26,0:12:01.04,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独的观测者
Comment: 0,0:00:52.16,0:00:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---ED---
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.35,0:22:28.57,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}規制された視界　無慈悲なる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.09,0:22:37.45,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二の支配　逃れられない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.96,0:22:45.92,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}安息の　明日を　願った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.70,0:22:54.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手の中の　尊い事象の地平へ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.38,0:23:03.99,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚われし盟約　現れた偽証の輪郭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.99,0:23:12.89,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命の天地は　盲目な時間を刻んだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.13,0:23:15.44,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}羽ばたけバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.44,0:23:17.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇跡のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.41,0:23:21.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたへ捧ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.92,0:23:24.29,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}涙のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.29,0:23:26.38,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眩しいバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.38,0:23:29.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全てが————
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.63,0:23:33.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今書き換えられる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.35,0:22:28.57,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}扣上枷锁的视野如此无情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.09,0:22:37.45,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二条支配无法逃脱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.96,0:22:45.92,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}祈求得以安息的明日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.70,0:22:54.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手中的至爱流向事象的地平
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.38,0:23:03.99,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚禁的盟约  显现伪证的轮廓
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.99,0:23:12.89,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命的天地  刻上盲目的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.13,0:23:15.44,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}展翅而飞Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.44,0:23:17.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇迹的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.41,0:23:21.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全都为你献上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.92,0:23:24.29,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}泪水的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.29,0:23:26.38,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}耀眼的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.38,0:23:29.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}这一切——
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.63,0:23:33.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}现在都将改写


