[Script Info]
Title:Steins;Gate 02 BD gb
Original Script:SumiSora & CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: up,微软雅黑,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00000040,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,6,30,30,10,134
Style: mail,微软雅黑,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,4,30,30,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGHSGothic-W5,21,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,8,128
Style: OPCN,方正大黑_GBK,22,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFKaiSho_U-Md,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,7,128
Style: EDCN,方正楷体_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:02:13.19,0:02:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---OP---
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.71,0:01:32.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}数十億もの　鼓動の数さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.03,0:01:39.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたには　瞬き程度の些事な等級
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.77,0:01:44.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}過去に囚われて　未来も嘆くも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.73,0:01:50.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}塵一つ　誤算を許さぬ必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.82,0:01:56.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『無限』に広がる夢も　描く未来も
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.10,0:02:02.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕達に許された　虚栄の権利
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.81,0:02:08.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『有限』それは二つの　針が示す
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.05,0:02:13.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷な約定と　選択へ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.54,0:02:15.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.97,0:02:22.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だからいま　１秒ごとに　世界線を超えて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.73,0:02:27.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君のその笑顔　守りたいのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.67,0:02:34.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そしてまた　悲しみの無い　時間のループへと
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.71,0:02:37.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}飲み込まれてゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.26,0:02:41.04,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独の観測者
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.71,0:01:32.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}连同数十亿的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.03,0:01:39.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}对你来说  不过是转瞬即逝的琐事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.77,0:01:44.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}被过去所囚困  未来和悲叹
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.73,0:01:50.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}微尘般的误算  亦不允许的必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.82,0:01:56.85,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无限扩展的梦想  描绘的未来也
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.10,0:02:02.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我们所被赋予的  虚荣的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.81,0:02:08.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}有限  那即是两根指针所标示
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.05,0:02:13.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷的约定和选择
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.54,0:02:15.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an2}Hacking to the Gate ——
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.97,0:02:22.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所以现在  越过每一秒的世界线
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.73,0:02:27.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想守护你的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.67,0:02:34.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}于是进入没有悲伤的  时间的轮回
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.71,0:02:37.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}逐渐被吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.26,0:02:41.04,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独的观测者
Comment: 0,0:00:52.16,0:00:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---ED---
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.35,0:22:27.57,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}規制された視界　無慈悲なる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.09,0:22:36.45,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二の支配　逃れられない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.96,0:22:44.92,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}安息の　明日を　願った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.70,0:22:53.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手の中の　尊い事象の地平へ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.38,0:23:02.99,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚われし盟約　現れた偽証の輪郭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.99,0:23:11.89,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命の天地は　盲目な時間を刻んだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.13,0:23:14.44,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}羽ばたけバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.44,0:23:16.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇跡のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.41,0:23:20.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたへ捧ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.92,0:23:23.29,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}涙のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.29,0:23:25.38,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眩しいバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.38,0:23:28.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全てが————
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.63,0:23:32.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今書き換えられる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.35,0:22:27.57,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}扣上枷锁的视野如此无情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.09,0:22:36.45,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二条支配无法逃脱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.96,0:22:44.92,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}祈求得以安息的明日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.70,0:22:53.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手中的至爱流向事象的地平
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.38,0:23:02.99,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚禁的盟约  显现伪证的轮廓
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.99,0:23:11.89,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命的天地  刻上盲目的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.13,0:23:14.44,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}展翅而飞Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.44,0:23:16.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇迹的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.41,0:23:20.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全都为你献上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.92,0:23:23.29,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}泪水的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.29,0:23:25.38,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}耀眼的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.38,0:23:28.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}这一切——
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.63,0:23:32.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}现在都将改写
Comment: 0,0:00:52.16,0:00:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---TXT---
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.00,0:02:49.04,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(580,335)}时间跳跃的妄想狂
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.85,0:00:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂… 小冈伦？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.60,0:00:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.98,0:00:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.86,0:00:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有  有实体
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.61,0:00:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是幽灵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.35,0:00:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想被警察抓走吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.61,0:00:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想知道真相
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.62,0:00:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被捅的好像是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.74,0:00:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么真相啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.17,0:00:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是笨蛋吗  想死吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.90,0:00:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露易丝酱的名台词出现了这是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.76,0:00:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.59,0:00:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被捅了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.35,0:00:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约3小时前  在广播会馆的中钵博士记者招待会…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.09,0:00:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦  妄想只对我们说就够了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.86,0:00:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中钵博士的招待会中止了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.83,0:00:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.97,0:00:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.23,0:00:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多到时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.38,0:01:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.39,0:01:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你要逃走吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.19,0:01:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.68,0:01:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是「你」  是凤凰院——
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.35,0:01:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.72,0:02:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天非常感谢各位前来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.51,0:02:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这样的演讲我没什么经验
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.36,0:02:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许会有些不习惯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.29,0:03:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还请多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.16,0:03:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讲师原来是牧濑红莉栖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.13,0:03:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不是幽灵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.49,0:03:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还在说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.61,0:03:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次被要求以时间机器做主题进行演讲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.06,0:03:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然与在「科学」杂志上刊登的论文的主题不同
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.86,0:03:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是想努力来说说看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.91,0:03:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间机器？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.02,0:03:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从结论来说的话——
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.71,0:03:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为所谓时间机器是非常荒唐的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.16,0:03:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么可以下这样的结论
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.34,0:03:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来将一边…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.78,0:03:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我反对！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.20,0:03:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间机器做不出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.21,0:03:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下结论还太早了！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.14,0:03:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦又乱来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.40,0:03:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.00,0:03:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起说是太早
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.38,0:03:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是应该在理论上否定的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.30,0:03:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才是我的见解
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.63,0:03:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.71,0:04:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  就改成讨论的形式吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.03,0:04:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样似乎也能让顽固的人理解
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.11,0:04:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧  凤凰院凶真先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.12,0:04:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑红莉栖
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.21,0:04:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,综上所述  {\1c&0000E0&}宇宙弦理论{\r}中的时间旅行并不现实
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.90,0:04:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要挑战看看吗  凤凰院先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.23,0:04:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛  那就请去找到{\1c&0000E0&}异物质{\r}吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.76,0:04:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凤凰院先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.44,0:04:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的演讲就到此结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.31,0:04:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想反驳的话我会听的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.03,0:04:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凤凰院先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.63,0:04:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点天才就自鸣得意
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.23,0:04:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.98,0:04:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小丫头恐怕是机关的特务
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.76,0:05:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次演讲本身就是精心设计的对我的精神攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.01,0:05:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会上当
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.23,0:05:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哈哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.79,0:05:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,8…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.11,0:05:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,9
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.57,0:05:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一次
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.91,0:05:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.44,0:05:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.42,0:05:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉佳好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.70,0:05:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦  嘟嘟噜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.87,0:05:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部前辈…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.68,0:05:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  凶真…师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.40,0:05:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘了暗语了哦  琉佳子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.73,0:05:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,E…EL  PSY  CON…CONGARI…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.37,0:05:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是CONGROO
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.78,0:05:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对…对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.67,0:05:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  要拿的东西呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.03,0:05:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.46,0:05:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉呢  真由氏一个人拿不动
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.84,0:05:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是父亲拿过来的  因为家里吃不完
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.53,0:06:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛  感谢对实验室的食物提供
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.55,0:06:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实验室成员的士气也会提高吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.50,0:06:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  你能高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.26,0:06:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.76,0:06:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉佳每天都做挥刀练习呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.03,0:06:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  因为是和冈部…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.51,0:06:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真师傅的约定
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.63,0:06:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.86,0:06:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖刀五月雨感知到琉佳子是合格的使用者时
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.31,0:06:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会发挥真正的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.05,0:06:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘记了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.99,0:06:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.76,0:06:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种剑在武器屋本铺只要980日元
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.98,0:06:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真物超所值呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.83,0:06:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  让我看看锻炼的成果吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.75,0:06:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以驱邪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.37,0:06:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大  大概…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.86,0:06:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  正式的驱邪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.83,0:06:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是让爸爸…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.62,0:06:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依附在我右手上的恶灵！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.92,0:06:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点驱邪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.98,0:06:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那力量侵犯全身之前
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.07,0:06:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.33,0:06:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和上次的手弄反了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.52,0:07:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天恶灵附到这边来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.31,0:07:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漆原琉佳
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.13,0:07:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音和举止看上去都像是女人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.48,0:07:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  比女人更像女人的美少女
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.56,0:07:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是是男的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.50,0:07:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然比真由理高
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.40,0:07:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身形却很纤细
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.04,0:07:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是是男的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.70,0:07:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很适合巫女服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.31,0:07:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是是男的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.88,0:07:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已经傍晚了  真热呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.36,0:07:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知了还在叫
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.57,0:07:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.05,0:07:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是男的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.63,0:07:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.70,0:07:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉佳还会驱邪真厉害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.13,0:07:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是神社里的儿子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.54,0:07:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唰  唰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.17,0:07:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.82,0:07:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,禁止通行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.35,0:07:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为通过这里就是广播会馆的后面了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.56,0:08:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,广播会馆…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.16,0:08:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个也给我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.89,0:08:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到打工的时间了吧  来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.72,0:08:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.18,0:08:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为今天会很晚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.12,0:08:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想结束了就直接回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.05,0:08:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.05,0:08:33.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的没听到惨叫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.28,0:08:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惨叫？  什么时候？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.45,0:08:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天在广播会馆
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.54,0:08:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没听到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.37,0:08:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.23,0:08:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了  那就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.11,0:08:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.30,0:08:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然谁都不记得了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.92,0:08:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理也好  阿至也好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.49,0:08:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑红莉栖也是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.35,0:09:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真早呢  Mr.布朗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.96,0:09:00.28,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\pos(320,10)}营业
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.08,0:09:01.05,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\pos(320,10)}休息
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.64,0:09:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了别用那个称呼了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.87,0:09:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天有打工的面试
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.14,0:09:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.65,0:09:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个阴沉又没客人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.11,0:09:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭男人当店长的店里…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.29,0:09:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.81,0:09:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.82,0:09:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？  我听说这是流行的打招呼方式呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.21,0:09:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道打工的就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.19,0:09:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.44,0:09:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.22,0:09:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿万音铃羽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.30,0:09:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年龄呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.86,0:09:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,18
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.66,0:09:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工动机呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.56,0:09:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我喜欢布朗管
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.88,0:09:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,录取
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.59,0:09:40.15,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.83,0:09:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  这是笑话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.26,0:09:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算计好的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.22,0:09:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来你是？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.88,0:09:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫冈部  住在这上面的笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.47,0:09:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是冈部  是凤凰院…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.73,0:09:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦死了  房租翻倍哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.70,0:09:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是冈部伦太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.65,0:09:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.75,0:09:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  那袋子里是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.74,0:09:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提供给实验室的智能玉米
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.87,0:10:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要的话  就付出相应的代价…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.01,0:10:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉米是那一小粒一小粒的？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.15,0:10:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.60,0:10:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.67,0:10:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以看看…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.92,0:10:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多人因为认识我而被机关盯上了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.80,0:10:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨拉  克劳迪亚  西蒙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.66,0:10:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗  不介意的话可以和我商量哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.82,0:10:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别当真啊  是这家伙编的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.80,0:10:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就这样想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.97,0:10:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天这个世界会向我下跪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.40,0:10:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哈哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.22,0:10:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种在流行…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.92,0:10:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12时左右坠落
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.05,0:10:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理他们说得没错
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.93,0:11:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,招待会中止
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.38,0:11:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑红莉栖  案件
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.83,0:11:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所看到的  是幻觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.72,0:11:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约翰·提托？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.23,0:11:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间机器被{\1c&0000E0&}SERN{\r}所独占
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.87,0:11:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通人和企业都无法得到
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.91,0:11:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们只将其为自己的利益所用
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.69,0:11:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给世界带来了{\1c&0000E0&}反乌托邦{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.65,0:11:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了改变未来而来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.46,0:12:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了破坏SERN所创造的反乌托邦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.46,0:12:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次夺回自由
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.02,0:12:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是你想说SERN是独裁者吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.67,0:12:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是俗称的祖父{\1c&0000E0&}时间悖论{\r}呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.38,0:12:14.88,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)}（如果进行时间旅行的话  能见到过去的自己吗）
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.02,0:12:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.73,0:12:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可以见到过去的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.26,0:12:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种情况下  世界线会移动
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.84,0:12:19.79,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（世界线是什么  多元世界说）
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.45,0:12:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先时间并不是从过去流向未来的一根线
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.26,0:12:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是由名为「世界线」的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.51,0:12:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无数平行流动的河流般的东西所构成的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.34,0:12:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说你今天  被杀人魔杀死了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.85,0:12:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这被从未来来的我制止了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.85,0:12:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界将分歧成  你被杀死的  和你活下来的  两个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.23,0:12:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次的提托是日本人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.07,0:12:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2000年时出现在美国网络上自称时间旅行者
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.72,0:13:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说从2036年为了拯救未来世界而时间旅行来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.78,0:13:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时在网络上造成了巨大的骚动
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.94,0:13:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还出了好几本相关书籍
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.07,0:13:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  现在竟然还会有讨论约翰·提托的笨蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.48,0:13:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这个链接  了解下提托再来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.22,0:13:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至这家伙  居然把提托的链接删掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.15,0:13:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12条？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.58,0:13:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.38,0:13:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算过了10年  可是造成了那么大的骚动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.24,0:13:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.59,0:13:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.99,0:13:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.33,0:13:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相关书籍应该是收集在这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.38,0:13:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.59,0:13:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  阿至
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.06,0:13:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？  我现在和菲伊莉斯炭…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.69,0:13:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,书弄哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.04,0:13:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,书是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.03,0:13:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于约翰·提托的书
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.26,0:13:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该整理放在书架上了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.78,0:14:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄到哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.80,0:14:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…  小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.06,0:14:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.47,0:14:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约翰·提托是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.62,0:14:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.53,0:14:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我几乎是通宵地调查了关于约翰·提托的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.75,0:14:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用网络搜索
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.63,0:14:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收集了各种情报
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.73,0:14:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.47,0:14:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望提托能回答一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.55,0:14:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10年前  也就是2000年的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.08,0:14:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个说话很有意思的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.68,0:14:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是很遗憾我并没有去过2000年
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.23,0:14:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且也没有去的打算
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.47,0:14:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  站住
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.38,0:14:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Wait  wait  wait
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.59,0:14:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.26,0:14:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.08,0:14:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.47,0:14:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  请等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.83,0:14:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才拍了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.22,0:15:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了你的人身安全还是赶紧删除吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.66,0:15:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.14,0:15:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果让你感到不愉快的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.57,0:15:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都拍了些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.95,0:15:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,证明
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.46,0:15:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.23,0:15:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.83,0:15:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.02,0:15:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.30,0:15:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事想问你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.29,0:15:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.12,0:15:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好古老的电脑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.54,0:15:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.62,0:15:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.80,0:15:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熟悉的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.26,0:15:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是阿至的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.31,0:15:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.98,0:15:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和你无关
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.65,0:15:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得把照片删了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.82,0:15:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.89,0:15:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短信地址…那个人的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.34,0:15:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.75,0:15:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙  想威胁我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.57,0:15:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我的话  就删掉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.41,0:16:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.59,0:16:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我不能出卖同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.40,0:16:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能告诉你的只有我的短信地址
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.27,0:16:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字是？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.61,0:16:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是写着凤凰院凶真吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.32,0:16:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.36,0:16:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发条空白短信过来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.93,0:16:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回复你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.34,0:16:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来喵  主人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.22,0:16:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.14,0:16:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来喵  小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.50,0:16:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  真由理
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.89,0:16:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打工的时候是真由氏喵喵哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.46,0:16:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来「小冈伦」和「欢迎回来」好像啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.12,0:16:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.38,0:16:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在里面哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.15,0:16:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.63,0:16:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你好久了喵
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.28,0:17:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天就来一次的约定呢喵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.41,0:17:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉  因为机关的妨碍太激烈…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.84,0:17:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵喵？  机关居然逼近到这里了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.67,0:17:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么今天也是为了打倒机关的机密会议喵？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.39,0:17:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是  平时用的隐蔽地点就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.46,0:17:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白喵  于是希望让菲伊莉斯也加入喵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.99,0:17:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  机关可没有简单到你也能对付
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.05,0:17:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我菲伊莉斯可是有禁断的秘奥义喵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.96,0:17:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？  难道你已经学会了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.23,0:17:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此喵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.80,0:17:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍受住圭亚那高地的修行  克服了师傅的死
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.18,0:17:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯终于
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.05,0:17:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到了喵！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.33,0:17:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅  绝对的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.54,0:17:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么关于短信里说的事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.52,0:17:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想对赢家说了就等于败了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.64,0:17:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧  我对充满谎言的女人没有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.86,0:17:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的「轮不到你来说」原来是这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.29,0:17:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴  你这个见异思迁的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.10,0:17:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你二次元的老婆在哭哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.67,0:17:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯炭另当别论
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.83,0:18:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是三次元还是二次元之魂都寄宿着
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.70,0:18:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起那个  想让你看看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.85,0:18:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这张照片…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.39,0:18:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  这是{\1c&0000E0&}IBN{\r}5100吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.29,0:18:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,IBN？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.13,0:18:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦幻的古董电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.31,0:18:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多是一个月前吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.29,0:18:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流传着它沉睡在秋叶原某处的传闻
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.43,0:18:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听了那个才来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.96,0:18:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.55,0:18:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是没找到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.28,0:18:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连{\1c&0000E0&}疾风迅雷的Knight-Hart{\r}都出场了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.28,0:18:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是没找出来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.43,0:18:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后结论就是从一开始就没有吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.28,0:18:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那么贵重的东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.22,0:18:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发售距今30年以上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.41,0:18:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时是价格太高  谁都买不起电脑的时代
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.70,0:18:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稀有度超高的例子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.65,0:18:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.34,0:18:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是刚才的女人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.73,0:18:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「马上就发短信了」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.80,0:18:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我叫桐生萌郁」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.53,0:18:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「20岁  自由职业者」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.40,0:18:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「就算你不同意我也要发」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.01,0:19:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和刚才的女人难道是同一个人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.45,0:19:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.27,0:19:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该感谢我没有出卖你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.00,0:19:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「那是贵重的电脑」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.37,0:19:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「不在秋叶原的可能性很高」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.70,0:19:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,EL  PSY  CONGROO
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.10,0:19:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人  久等了喵喵
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.93,0:19:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「世界有危险」来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.03,0:19:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.48,0:19:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.56,0:19:22.66,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.01,0:19:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃好吃  这个真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.74,0:19:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在大学的研究室进行分析的结果
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.73,0:19:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,证明了胶化香蕉分子级上被分解得粉碎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.66,0:19:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成了不是香蕉的什么东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.98,0:19:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那岂不是很不妙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.33,0:19:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.38,0:19:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的情况下所能想到的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.72,0:19:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有电话微波炉（暂定）的电磁波的影响吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.18,0:19:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出处是？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.53,0:19:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯狂科学家的直感
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.88,0:19:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无根据…好了  连接完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.67,0:20:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那么就用这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.55,0:20:03.02,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}（真由氏的）
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.54,0:20:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…不是真由氏的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.17,0:20:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.51,0:20:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是用真由理提供的研究资金
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.03,0:20:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去买来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.50,0:20:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说那就是真由氏的…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.75,0:20:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  整把放进去确认变化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.67,0:20:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一根就够了吧{\1c&0000E0&}常考{\r}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.51,0:20:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样能够确认电话微波炉（暂定）的真正力量吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.62,0:20:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个（暂定）太麻烦了差不多该去掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.89,0:20:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在实验上吝啬钱的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.92,0:20:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是无法改变世界的支配构造的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.04,0:20:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想改变的只有小冈伦而已
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.41,0:20:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.93,0:20:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.71,0:20:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.76,0:20:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.61,0:20:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失了  香蕉…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.84,0:20:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.93,0:21:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.14,0:21:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快发动紧急要求666号「Cooling-off」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.96,0:21:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政府的认证？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.44,0:21:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是该说这种话的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.08,0:21:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自演  乙！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.51,0:21:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别废话  你藏哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.22,0:21:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小冈伦藏起来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.00,0:21:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.82,0:21:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这难道是可以进行瞬间移动的微波炉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.49,0:21:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.00,0:21:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.93,0:21:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你要怎么解释
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.59,0:21:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从把上扭下来应该是放进了微波炉的香蕉…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.86,0:21:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胶化…香蕉？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.02,0:21:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但…但是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.11,0:21:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是和把完全连在一起了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.72,0:21:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才确实是扭下来了一根吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.77,0:21:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大…大概
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.39,0:21:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…果然是瞬间移动？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.46,0:21:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这么一回事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.56,0:21:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在做很有意思的实验呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.45,0:21:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部伦太郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.93,0:22:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是凤凰院凶真先生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.99,0:22:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑…红莉栖！


