[Script Info]
Title:Steins;Gate 06 gb
Original Script:SumiSora & CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: up,微软雅黑,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00000040,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,6,30,30,10,134
Style: mail,微软雅黑,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,7,15,15,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGHSGothic-W5,21,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,8,128
Style: OPCN,方正大黑_GBK,22,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFKaiSho_U-Md,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,7,128
Style: EDCN,方正楷体_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.06,0:02:40.04,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(580,335)}蝶翼的偏差值
Comment: 0,0:00:08.94,0:00:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---OP---
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.59,0:01:23.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}数十億もの　鼓動の数さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.91,0:01:30.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたには　瞬き程度の些事な等級
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.65,0:01:35.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}過去に囚われて　未来も嘆くも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.61,0:01:41.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}塵一つ　誤算を許さぬ必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.70,0:01:47.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『無限』に広がる夢も　描く未来も
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.98,0:01:53.45,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕達に許された　虚栄の権利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.69,0:01:59.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『有限』それは二つの　針が示す
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.93,0:02:04.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷な約定と　選択へ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.42,0:02:06.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.85,0:02:13.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だからいま　１秒ごとに　世界線を超えて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.61,0:02:18.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君のその笑顔　守りたいのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.55,0:02:25.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そしてまた　悲しみの無い　時間のループへと
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.59,0:02:28.14,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}飲み込まれてゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.14,0:02:31.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独の観測者
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.59,0:01:23.75,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}连同数十亿的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.91,0:01:30.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}对你来说  不过是转瞬即逝的琐事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.65,0:01:35.61,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}被过去所囚困  未来和悲叹
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.61,0:01:41.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}微尘般的误算  亦不允许的必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.70,0:01:47.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无限扩展的梦想  描绘的未来也
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.98,0:01:53.45,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我们所被赋予的  虚荣的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.69,0:01:59.51,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}有限  那即是两根指针所标示
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.93,0:02:04.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷的约定和选择
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.42,0:02:06.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an2}Hacking to the Gate ——
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.85,0:02:13.44,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所以现在  越过每一秒的世界线
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.61,0:02:18.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想守护你的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.55,0:02:25.59,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}于是进入没有悲伤的  时间的轮回
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.59,0:02:28.14,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}逐渐被吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.14,0:02:31.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独的观测者
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---ED---
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.35,0:22:27.57,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}規制された視界　無慈悲なる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.09,0:22:36.45,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二の支配　逃れられない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.96,0:22:44.92,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}安息の　明日を　願った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.70,0:22:53.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手の中の　尊い事象の地平へ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.38,0:23:02.99,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚われし盟約　現れた偽証の輪郭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.99,0:23:11.89,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命の天地は　盲目な時間を刻んだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.13,0:23:14.44,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}羽ばたけバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.44,0:23:16.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇跡のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.41,0:23:20.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたへ捧ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.92,0:23:23.29,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}涙のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.29,0:23:25.38,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眩しいバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.38,0:23:28.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全てが————
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.63,0:23:32.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今書き換えられる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.35,0:22:27.57,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}扣上枷锁的视野如此无情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.09,0:22:36.45,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二条支配无法逃脱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.96,0:22:44.92,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}祈求得以安息的明日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.70,0:22:53.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手中的至爱流向事象的地平
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.38,0:23:02.99,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚禁的盟约  显现伪证的轮廓
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.99,0:23:11.89,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命的天地  刻上盲目的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.13,0:23:14.44,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}展翅而飞Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.44,0:23:16.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇迹的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.41,0:23:20.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全都为你献上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.92,0:23:23.29,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}泪水的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.29,0:23:25.38,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}耀眼的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.38,0:23:28.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}这一切——
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.63,0:23:32.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}现在都将改写
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---TEXT---
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.24,0:10:19.65,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部是个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.00,0:10:21.40,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱智！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.04,0:18:07.76,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了\N至少回个信吧\N还是说不在家吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.76,0:18:08.99,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快起来\N难道说还在睡吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.16,0:18:14.37,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好黑\N现在在爬楼梯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.14,0:18:19.88,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在门前\N要敲门了哦\N在的话就回个声
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.31,0:18:29.24,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N你说了可以来看的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.48,0:19:34.04,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)}（无标题）\N希望能让我拍照
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.32,0:20:45.94,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)}听到了\N把短信发到过去\N是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.16,0:21:33.05,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道\N难道是FB？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.52,0:14:39.88,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Yahoo\N好久不见  冈部
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.88,0:14:41.02,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样\N关于IBN5100\N知道些什么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.72,0:00:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是距人造卫星坠落五天后的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.82,0:00:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋叶原的广播会馆楼前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.83,0:00:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也从一早起就有许多人前来围观
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.34,0:00:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仍被搁置的人造卫星依然国籍不明
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.91,0:00:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有搬走的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.51,0:00:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能打扰一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.76,0:00:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是来参观人造卫星的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.91,0:00:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从哪里来的呢  方便的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.64,0:02:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.78,0:02:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.18,0:02:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿万音氏第一次吃牛肉盖浇饭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.05,0:02:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.73,0:02:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有听说过  真好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.31,0:02:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加上生鸡蛋的话会更好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.20,0:02:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是战士的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.50,0:03:02.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要学会一个人来盖浇饭店才好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.07,0:03:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我和阿至都经常会来这家店
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.13,0:03:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你邀请我们的话  随时奉陪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.16,0:03:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我想起来喽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.64,0:03:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前小冈伦吃大碗牛肉饭  是我垫的钱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.23,0:03:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是有那么一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.92,0:03:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是好像而是确有其事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.51,0:03:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还钱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.73,0:03:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不巧的是我今天没带钱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.08,0:03:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我  马上从瑞士银行的户头把钱汇过来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.95,0:03:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  机关把日内瓦的服务器给黑了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.68,0:03:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  何等的事态
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.22,0:03:36.88,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,禁止用手机
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.97,0:03:39.75,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是装样子罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.80,0:03:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘟嘟噜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.18,0:03:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃姐也在一起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.31,0:03:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为正好中午休息
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.90,0:03:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是再早点的话就能一起吃了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.65,0:03:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那明天中午大家一起去吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.79,0:03:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这回就让小冈伦请客…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.38,0:03:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.41,0:03:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为机关的阻挠  恢复服务器要花一星期？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.76,0:04:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是红莉栖
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.30,0:04:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦助手  昨天好好休息了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.77,0:04:06.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要叫助手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.16,0:04:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂打工的  午饭吃完了就赶紧干活
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.93,0:04:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.17,0:04:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圆桌会议？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.50,0:04:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.15,0:04:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.70,0:04:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是实验室成员之间的会议
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.02,0:04:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种东西以前有搞过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.79,0:04:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说圆桌什么的在哪儿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.46,0:04:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里没实物
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.52,0:04:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在我们实验室成员的心中  不是么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.44,0:04:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是「不是么」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.49,0:04:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要擅自在别人心里放奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.97,0:04:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏的心里是不是也有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.59,0:04:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  当然有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.99,0:04:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.74,0:04:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是圆桌是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.34,0:04:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说为什么是圆桌啊  亚瑟王？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.49,0:04:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底我虽说是实验室成员也是有时间限制的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.06,0:05:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  是圆桌会议
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.26,0:05:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算对真由理  也有必要把我们现处的情况告诉她
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.30,0:05:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况是…？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.56,0:05:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.24,0:05:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了超越SERN我们必须尽早
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.58,0:05:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完善电话微波炉（暂定）的时间机器功能
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.42,0:05:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对真由氏来说太复杂了还是搞不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.06,0:05:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之SERN是坏蛋  就这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.10,0:05:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是要完善电话微波炉（暂定）
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.26,0:05:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把短信发回过去的实验我们不是成功了么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.31,0:05:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有两次而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.32,0:05:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且在什么时候会发生这种现象  还没有弄清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.50,0:05:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前的实验的话  只有在放电现象发生的时候才发送成功的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.61,0:05:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊对了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.26,0:05:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白什么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.56,0:05:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  「发往过去的短信」说起来太拗口
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.08,0:06:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先从命名开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.04,0:06:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  又来装样子？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.06,0:06:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说什么又来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.36,0:06:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在愚弄我凤凰院凶真吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.33,0:06:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你也就想取些奇怪的名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.87,0:06:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真失敬  那么就来公布吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.13,0:06:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对这发往过去的短信的现象这样命名
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.25,0:06:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(345,325)\fscy80\fscx80}nostalgia  drive
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.25,0:06:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其名为「超越时间前往乡愁之旅」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.13,0:06:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便一提  是写作「超越时间前往乡愁之旅」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.18,0:06:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,读作「nostalgia  drive」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.87,0:06:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难懂  驳回
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.89,0:06:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙  区区助手以为自己有驳回的权限吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.17,0:06:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么多数表决如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.87,0:06:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赞成「nostalgia  drive」的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.13,0:06:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背叛了啊  真由理  阿至
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.83,0:06:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得就像红莉栖说的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.57,0:06:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏记不住那么长的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.08,0:06:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太中二病了吧常考
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.44,0:06:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该重视易懂性呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.31,0:06:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是回溯时间的短信  溯行短信不就好了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.82,0:06:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是溯行？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.26,0:07:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是一点也不好懂嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.48,0:07:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里当然是「跨越时间的短信」了吧常考
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.26,0:07:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表现有点生硬啊  拗口
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.36,0:07:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮不到你说
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.78,0:07:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦的nostalgia什么的不是更长嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.54,0:07:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要浪漫就行了浪漫
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.51,0:07:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么省略一下  跨越时间
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.52,0:07:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话  是什么跨越时间都搞不清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.56,0:07:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是短信  是少女  还是香蕉？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.73,0:07:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘟嘟噜  真由氏也想到了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.25,0:07:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个呢  「back  to  the  mail」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.23,0:07:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直译的话就是「回到短信」  意义不明
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.90,0:07:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那「DeLorean  Mail」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.82,0:07:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越搞不懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.14,0:07:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.95,0:07:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如干脆省略了  叫「D-Mail」不就好了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.91,0:07:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这个好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.00,0:07:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就这么决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.65,0:07:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么从现在开始进行D-Mail（暂定）的实验
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.24,0:07:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（暂定）也属于被省略内容
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.23,0:07:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(355,325)\fscy80\fscx80}Operation  Urd
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.23,0:07:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作战名为「掌管过去的女神作战」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.38,0:07:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个也不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.64,0:07:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是D-Mail的发送条件还是不清楚的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.00,0:08:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和放电现象的关系也不明
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.24,0:08:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是从现在起要去确认的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.95,0:08:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我凤凰院凶真有一个假说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.12,0:08:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们漏掉了最单纯最具决定性的条件
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.73,0:08:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说  发生时间
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.75,0:08:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初的D-Mail是12点至13点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.35,0:08:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二次是在18点左右发生的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.33,0:08:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是在这两个时间带进行实验的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.65,0:08:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以再现…也许
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.63,0:08:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再怎么说这也太单纯了吧常考
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.92,0:08:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有尝试的价值
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.11,0:08:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理  拿香蕉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.85,0:08:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏的香蕉少了很多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.43,0:08:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有连香蕉都要放进去的必要吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.39,0:08:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连香蕉都要放进去…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.27,0:08:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至  现在克制点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.05,0:08:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是为了确认是否会变成凝胶状
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.56,0:08:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧助手  快点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.89,0:08:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把香蕉放进去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.88,0:08:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把香蕉放进去…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.43,0:08:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,适可而止吧  你这变态
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.52,0:08:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  之后会给你买新的香蕉的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.34,0:08:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？  真高兴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.30,0:09:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦和阿至一点也不给我买
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.16,0:09:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.40,0:09:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.46,0:09:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别展示冒失娘属性
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.92,0:09:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.58,0:09:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼的痛的都飞走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.66,0:09:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Thanks  真由理
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.99,0:09:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边不要总是制造百合力场  来做D-Mail的准备
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.68,0:09:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.75,0:09:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间设定为120秒OK？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.60,0:09:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.66,0:09:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(280,325)\fscy80\fscx80}Operation  Urd
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.66,0:09:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「掌管过去的女神作战」  开始！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.78,0:09:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.98,0:09:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了  来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.53,0:09:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,香蕉呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.84,0:09:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成胶化香蕉了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.04,0:09:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哈哈哈  终于明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.72,0:09:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然如我所料  D-Mail的发送条件是时间啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.02,0:09:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真行啊冈部
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.56,0:10:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为太单纯了都没察觉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.42,0:10:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不甘心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.73,0:10:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使这样也向我送上赞词的样子值得赞扬
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.53,0:10:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个D-Mail收到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.47,0:10:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.20,0:10:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收信日期是五天前
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.33,0:10:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑氏发了两条吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.54,0:10:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  只发了一条
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.62,0:10:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被分解成了两条
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.23,0:10:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便问下这条短信的意思是？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.20,0:10:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己去查下如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.39,0:10:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.46,0:10:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前的D-Mail也是被分解了  文章从中间就断开了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.37,0:10:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,返回的时间也都是五天前
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.37,0:10:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  有什么规律性…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.04,0:10:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来那条短信
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.19,0:10:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是说我是脑袋空空的笨蛋吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.41,0:10:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发现得太慢了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.50,0:10:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  克里斯汀娜
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.37,0:10:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁乱…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.74,0:10:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你买这么多要干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.10,0:11:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食物有容易保存的泡面就足够了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.91,0:11:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巧克力这样会融化的买一包就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.38,0:11:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是为了庆祝实验成功
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.56,0:11:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  放回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.79,0:11:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘁  真小气
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.08,0:11:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.71,0:11:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然正为实验成功而得意
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.92,0:11:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们知道了SERN那可怕的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.06,0:11:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连真由理都被卷了进来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.80,0:11:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.07,0:11:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,325)\fscy80\fscx80}shining  finger
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.07,0:11:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是闪光的指压师吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.92,0:12:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.57,0:12:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从刚才开始就在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.60,0:12:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没带…手机吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.27,0:12:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我凤凰院凶真的手机现在正用在名垂青史的伟大实验上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.57,0:12:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此不在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.75,0:12:18.55,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束了  哦？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.13,0:12:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小…小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.19,0:12:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的色色的…呃不
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.58,0:12:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性感的三次元女性是哪位啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.97,0:12:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我来介绍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.87,0:12:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪光的指压师  桐生萌郁
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.41,0:12:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请…请多指教  桐生…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.32,0:12:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有对三次元抱有希望的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.46,0:12:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  你好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.79,0:12:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说刚才开始就做着愉快的事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.60,0:12:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.79,0:12:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正在进行将会名垂青史的实验…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.31,0:12:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名垂青史是不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.83,0:13:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但店长很不爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.67,0:13:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说二楼的震动太厉害了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.44,0:13:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「房租要涨一万日元啊  喂！」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.06,0:13:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.39,0:13:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.00,0:13:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  这里就交给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.14,0:13:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至去通知助手暂时中止实验
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.27,0:13:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白  你现在非常的耀眼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.22,0:13:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑红莉栖也还在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.62,0:13:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  说起来刚才也在盯着她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.77,0:13:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这之前也是  为什么要针对她
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.22,0:13:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去发生过什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.03,0:13:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在过去什么也没发生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.56,0:13:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  那是8岁的夏天
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.63,0:13:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在密西西比河畔  逃跑的红色耳朵的…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.61,0:13:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了什么也没有了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.91,0:13:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前是初次见面
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.54,0:13:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个还是快点去和店长道歉比较好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.19,0:13:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底在上面干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.46,0:13:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才开始就夸张地摇晃了好多次
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.69,0:14:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实正在进行能改写人类科学史的世纪性实验
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.14,0:14:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是请放心  今天已经不会再…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.44,0:14:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都说了住手了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.61,0:14:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在搞什么啊  我不是说了实验中止了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.47,0:14:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑氏说最后再来一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.34,0:14:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你发了短信  没看到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.15,0:14:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能看得到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.89,0:14:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都在五天前忠告过你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.04,0:14:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.23,0:14:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有好像除了实验以外小冈伦的手机也响了好几次哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.56,0:14:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不直接说出来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.22,0:14:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.51,0:14:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不太明白  但好像是缺钙了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.97,0:14:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁的错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.60,0:14:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过数据也收集够了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.18,0:14:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于D-Mail的规律也大致明白了这倒是不错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.43,0:14:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.10,0:15:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于D-Mail能够回溯的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.34,0:15:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计时器的1秒相当于现实的1小时
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.12,0:15:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,120秒等于5天
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.41,0:15:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就是5天前了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.34,0:15:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现了可以调整发送到什么时候是不是很厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.31,0:15:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是能发送的字数是英文最多36个字母
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.87,0:15:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日文18个文字
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.69,0:15:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太少了  这是要改进的地方呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.24,0:15:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是大东西之类的没办法发送太多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.69,0:15:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是那个克布黑洞…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.13,0:15:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是克尔黑洞
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.57,0:15:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个黑洞的洞太紧了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.62,0:15:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏刚才的话再说一遍  从洞那里开始…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.56,0:15:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了  你这变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.93,0:15:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  具体的验证明天以后再进行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.81,0:15:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  有一点需要宣布
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.19,0:15:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2010年8月2日
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.64,0:15:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会成为永远留在人类历史上的一天吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.66,0:15:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这一天
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.79,0:15:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们未来道具研究所
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.98,0:15:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首次在人类史上的时间机器开发中——
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.06,0:15:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取得成功了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.54,0:16:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是首次吧  都被SERN抢先了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.78,0:16:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底也算不上是开发了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.13,0:16:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是偶然能用了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.78,0:16:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个家伙都这样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.82,0:16:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然对于我堂堂的宣言连一点敬意都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.91,0:16:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.85,0:16:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实验很顺利真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.33,0:16:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.48,0:16:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你并没有在移动
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.99,0:16:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里  空间和时间互相交换了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.98,0:16:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(310,325)\fscy80\fscx80}event  horizon
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.98,0:16:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\1c&0000E0&}事象地平线{\r}吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.66,0:16:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无法在空间中移动
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.72,0:17:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有时间被无限地延长
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.92,0:17:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的1秒对于我来说  是永远
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.29,0:17:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇宙的尽头在逃远
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.09,0:17:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不对  是在被拉长
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.16,0:17:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.05,0:17:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是宇宙？  还是我？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.62,0:17:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以回头
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.69,0:17:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远并不是无限
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.51,0:17:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使时间被向着永远拉长
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.15,0:17:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终结  也是存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.31,0:17:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1秒后  何时才会到来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.27,0:17:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面向前方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.08,0:17:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到达终点
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.40,0:17:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以回头
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.31,0:17:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是短信魔吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.23,0:17:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是这么纠缠不休
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.65,0:18:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「昨天对不起」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.08,0:18:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「接下来可以去你那里吗」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.43,0:18:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就想不到我还在睡觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.65,0:18:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用不着「难道」我就是在睡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.93,0:18:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.66,0:18:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要发短信
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.89,0:18:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明就在眼前
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.95,0:18:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会看的  有话直说
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.09,0:18:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你看是可以  不过居然这么一大早就跑来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.24,0:18:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么  你这家伙的真正目的是想采访我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.00,0:18:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不说话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.09,0:18:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  是这么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.50,0:18:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在害怕我疯狂科学家凤凰院凶真邪恶的气场吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.42,0:18:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.48,0:18:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用短信比较…轻松
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.74,0:19:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  IBN5100…希望能让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.68,0:19:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  但是只能看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.77,0:19:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后看了就回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.56,0:19:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.27,0:19:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙难道只是单纯的古董电脑迷吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.07,0:19:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了我的脸以外
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.85,0:19:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果拍了的话  就只能灭口…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.99,0:19:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「想要借用一下  行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.88,0:19:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮我一起搬就…」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.95,0:19:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会借你成了前提啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.59,0:19:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且真心想借的话就面向这边直接说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.26,0:20:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能借…给我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.86,0:20:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很遗憾但是不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.86,0:20:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底我也只是暂借而已
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.30,0:20:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用完了就要还给原主
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.03,0:20:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原主是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.06,0:20:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柳林神社
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.84,0:20:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.49,0:20:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是昨天的桐生氏？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.05,0:20:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天没有介绍呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.52,0:20:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最爱的右手  超级嘿客阿至
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.48,0:20:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了是超级黑客
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.54,0:20:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了对了  比起这个我想把电话微波炉改良一下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.95,0:20:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在需要很麻烦的步骤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.47,0:20:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了把D-Mail发到过去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.09,0:20:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  是你听错了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.37,0:20:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是把短信发到过去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.66,0:20:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是「Baduan Xinfa Daoguo Qu」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.96,0:20:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是现在已经失传的古代苏美尔语
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.46,0:20:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是「你吃早饭了吗」的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.26,0:20:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx85\fscy85}嘟嘟噜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.18,0:21:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.74,0:21:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在做时间机器的实验前让真由氏热一下炸鸡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.93,0:21:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部  关于时间机器我想到了一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.76,0:21:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我  麻烦来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.44,0:21:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.87,0:21:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,8号机的情报被泄露给了第三者
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.28,0:21:20.05,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯知道  我会想办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.86,0:21:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么情况？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.08,0:21:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们全员都被华丽地无视？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.71,0:21:22.98,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据状况即使灭口也要阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.26,0:21:24.54,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让机关知道…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.84,0:21:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在通话中给我发短信
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.15,0:21:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.56,0:21:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,F…B？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.95,0:21:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.69,0:21:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这样就全都告诉你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.69,0:21:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然秘密已经被知道了那就没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.39,0:21:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐生萌郁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.84,0:21:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从今天起就是实验室成员No.005


