[Script Info]
Title:Steins;Gate 18 gb
Original Script:SumiSora & CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: up,微软雅黑,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00000040,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,6,30,30,10,134
Style: mail,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,15,15,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGHSGothic-W5,21,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,8,128
Style: OPCN,方正大黑_GBK,22,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFKaiSho_U-Md,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,7,128
Style: EDCN,方正楷体_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.06,0:02:08.06,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(545,335)}自我相似的雌雄同株
Comment: 0,0:00:17.05,0:00:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---OP---
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.81,0:00:51.97,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}数十億もの　鼓動の数さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.13,0:00:58.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたには　瞬き程度の些事な等級
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.87,0:01:03.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}過去に囚われて　未来も嘆くも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.83,0:01:09.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}塵一つ　誤算を許さぬ必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.92,0:01:15.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『無限』に広がる夢も　描く未来も
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.20,0:01:21.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕達に許された　虚栄の権利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.91,0:01:27.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『有限』それは二つの　針が示す
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.15,0:01:32.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷な約定と　選択へ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.64,0:01:34.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.07,0:01:41.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だからいま　１秒ごとに　世界線を超えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.83,0:01:46.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君のその笑顔　守りたいのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.77,0:01:53.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そしてまた　悲しみの無い　時間のループへと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.81,0:01:56.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}飲み込まれてゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.36,0:02:00.14,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独の観測者
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.81,0:00:51.97,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}连同数十亿的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.13,0:00:58.87,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}对你来说  不过是转瞬即逝的琐事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.87,0:01:03.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}被过去所囚困  未来和悲叹
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.83,0:01:09.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}微尘般的误算  亦不允许的必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.92,0:01:15.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无限扩展的梦想  描绘的未来也
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.20,0:01:21.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我们所被赋予的  虚荣的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.91,0:01:27.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}有限  那即是两根指针所标示
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.15,0:01:32.64,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷的约定和选择
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.64,0:01:34.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an2}Hacking to the Gate ——
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.07,0:01:41.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所以现在  越过每一秒的世界线
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.83,0:01:46.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想守护你的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.77,0:01:53.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}于是进入没有悲伤的  时间的轮回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.81,0:01:56.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}逐渐被吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.36,0:02:00.14,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独的观测者
Comment: 0,0:00:50.96,0:00:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---ED---
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.45,0:22:27.67,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}規制された視界　無慈悲なる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.19,0:22:36.55,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二の支配　逃れられない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.06,0:22:45.02,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}安息の　明日を　願った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.80,0:22:54.03,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手の中の　尊い事象の地平へ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.48,0:23:03.09,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚われし盟約　現れた偽証の輪郭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.09,0:23:11.99,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命の天地は　盲目な時間を刻んだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.23,0:23:14.54,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}羽ばたけバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.54,0:23:17.03,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇跡のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.51,0:23:20.91,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたへ捧ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.02,0:23:23.39,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}涙のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.39,0:23:25.48,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眩しいバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.48,0:23:28.73,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全てが————
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.73,0:23:32.91,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今書き換えられる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.45,0:22:27.67,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}扣上枷锁的视野如此无情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.19,0:22:36.55,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二条支配无法逃脱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.06,0:22:45.02,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}祈求得以安息的明日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.80,0:22:54.03,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手中的至爱流向事象的地平
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.48,0:23:03.09,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚禁的盟约  显现伪证的轮廓
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.09,0:23:11.99,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命的天地  刻上盲目的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.23,0:23:14.54,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}展翅而飞Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.54,0:23:17.03,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇迹的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.51,0:23:20.91,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全都为你献上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.02,0:23:23.39,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}泪水的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.39,0:23:25.48,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}耀眼的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.48,0:23:28.73,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}这一切——
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.73,0:23:32.91,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}现在都将改写
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---TEXT---
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.48,0:00:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉佳子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.26,0:00:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静下来听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.64,0:00:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实你曾经是个男的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.04,0:00:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又要说那种话吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.27,0:00:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  不要哭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.09,0:00:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静下来听我说到最后
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.66,0:00:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都是为了真由理
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.14,0:00:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须要变回男人才行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.20,0:00:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自我相似的雌雄同株
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.48,0:02:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.36,0:02:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直就像倒泡炒面的水失败了  把面全洒到了池子里的一副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.60,0:02:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不如说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.72,0:02:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易集齐的积分卡准备去用掉的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.06,0:02:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果发现过期了以后的表情…这样才对
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.30,0:02:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你还有回敬玩笑的心情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.90,0:02:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦！  真由氏对你非常失望
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.56,0:02:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.21,0:02:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装傻可不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.45,0:02:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把小琉佳给弄哭了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.18,0:02:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为…为什么你会知道？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.53,0:02:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我请她一起来实验室  结果突然就哭起来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.78,0:02:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我问她怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.96,0:02:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说被你说自己是男的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.83,0:03:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,D-Mail的事情也听说了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.94,0:03:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,D-Mail?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.50,0:03:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要想蒙混过关可不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.91,0:03:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦应该好好向小琉佳道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.68,0:03:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.71,0:03:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然对漆原小姐说那么过分的话？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.20,0:03:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  等等  不是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.74,0:03:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这其中有很深的原因…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.18,0:03:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么原因？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.01,0:03:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,助手  跟我来一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.99,0:03:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.71,0:03:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.55,0:03:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  下一封要消除的D-Mail
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.03,0:03:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是发给琉佳子出生之前的他母亲的寻呼机的短信
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.86,0:03:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漆原小姐其实是男的？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.63,0:03:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难以置信
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.35,0:03:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是是事实
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.41,0:03:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经是事实
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.02,0:03:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是…男的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.26,0:03:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说跟桥田一样？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.44,0:04:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这太糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.44,0:04:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  样子看上去是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.88,0:04:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还可以接受
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.33,0:04:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  要拯救真由理
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.82,0:04:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不得不让琉佳子变回男人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.03,0:04:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这次冈部知道漆原小姐发送的D-Mail的内容吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.23,0:04:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不用特意跟她说明事实
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.18,0:04:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞒着她自己解决不行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.14,0:04:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道琉佳子母亲的寻呼机号码
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.30,0:04:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说  比起低劣的小动作
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.52,0:04:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他真相才是有诚意的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.54,0:04:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那诚意的结果就是让她哭了不是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.14,0:04:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你平常的「设定」对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.63,0:04:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是玩笑对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.69,0:04:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.06,0:04:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没想过冈部师傅会说这种话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.30,0:04:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是立了flag吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.96,0:04:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,flag？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.48,0:05:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没说什么「这场战斗结束后就会结婚」之类的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.72,0:05:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是死亡flag
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.59,0:05:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的是恋爱flag
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.06,0:05:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋爱？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.28,0:05:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  被最喜欢的冈部说「你是个男的」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.77,0:05:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少女心都碎了一地了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.00,0:05:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…但是  琉佳子是男的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.36,0:05:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是前一个世界线上的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.24,0:05:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有重要的话要说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.52,0:05:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能到神社来一趟
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.77,0:05:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.39,0:05:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才对不起了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.42,0:05:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我才是  哭了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.11,0:05:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后？  你说有重要的话要说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.96,0:05:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  我有一个请求
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.56,0:05:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请求？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.81,0:05:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信冈部师傅说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.27,0:05:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.34,0:05:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是让我变回男孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.90,0:06:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就请…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.94,0:06:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请和我成为恋人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.16,0:06:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋…恋人？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.68,0:06:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我要当你的恋人？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.82,0:06:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.11,0:06:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢冈部师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.44,0:06:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…明天  一天就行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.39,0:06:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请和我成为恋人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.13,0:06:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…但是  你是男…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.41,0:06:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.64,0:06:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  你别哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.48,0:06:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  明天一天就行的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.30,0:06:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就当你的恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.72,0:06:36.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.24,0:06:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要哭？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.39,0:06:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.53,0:06:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才稍微有点心动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.57,0:06:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以明天你要和漆原小姐去约会？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.77,0:06:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.97,0:06:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯狂的科学家要和女高中生约会
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.94,0:06:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.17,0:07:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说才这样强忍羞耻和你这个助手商量怎样才能约好会
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.63,0:07:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说我不是助手嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.13,0:07:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵喵  凶真要和谁出去约会吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.28,0:07:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了  冰咖啡喵
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.79,0:07:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会对象是真由氏吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.32,0:07:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说是这位呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.58,0:07:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  这家伙是助手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.23,0:07:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是为了修得奥义的任务
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.47,0:07:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是随心所欲地对身边的各个女孩出手呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.46,0:07:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  对身边各种女孩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.75,0:07:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  不要说完让人误解的话就闪人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.06,0:07:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…  冈部你…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.75,0:07:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了修得奥义就会什么事都干吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.29,0:07:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我说的是…  那个「设定」里面的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.54,0:07:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么连你也搬出「设定」来了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.44,0:07:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明白你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.84,0:07:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说…说说而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.15,0:08:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算有心上人  只要为了修得奥义
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.02,0:08:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就什么事都干得出来的「设定」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.88,0:08:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么特别的意义
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.41,0:08:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你要生气？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.49,0:08:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没生气
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.27,0:08:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说  你要是这种设定的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.41,0:08:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就和漆原小姐去约会不就行了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.56,0:08:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说一开始我就说了要去约会的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.24,0:08:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.26,0:08:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的话也让我好好听听吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.46,0:08:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是约会的事的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.08,0:08:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就交给已经和几十个女孩子亲热过的我来处理吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.28,0:08:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈奈  小栞  穗香  凛子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.41,0:08:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那都是游戏中的女性吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.18,0:08:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的是现实中的约会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.75,0:08:47.33,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注：均为地名
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.75,0:08:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说约会就是去青山或者表参道或者西麻布
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.40,0:08:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流行时髦的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.49,0:08:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个豪华的夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.51,0:08:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别的晚餐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.13,0:08:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行…这是另外一个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.85,0:09:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现实中不存在的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.18,0:09:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些都否定了还怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.57,0:09:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说  和艾萨克·牛顿一样天生IQ170的我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.61,0:09:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凤凰院凶真
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.48,0:09:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说感兴趣的  比起女人来还是研究…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.99,0:09:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是个处男  真是多谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.90,0:09:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说你又如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.11,0:09:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有那么值得自满的丰富的约会经验吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.02,0:09:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.96,0:09:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不是钻进学习和研究之中
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.24,0:09:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种经验不是零吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.54,0:09:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是经历了一个孤零零的青春时代么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.55,0:09:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦  处女不行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.27,0:09:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次约会最重要的是要如何给对方留下好印象
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.85,0:09:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于服装  不需要穿名牌
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.80,0:09:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要让人觉得干净整洁…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.14,0:09:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.20,0:09:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有比白大褂更干净的了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.99,0:09:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人穿白大褂出去约会的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.31,0:10:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于约会场所也是一样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.93,0:10:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要勉强去高档饭店
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.09,0:10:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去自己平常去的店子就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.90,0:10:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平常去的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.92,0:10:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里不行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.36,0:10:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  谁愿意在这种煞风景的店里约会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.52,0:10:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说其他平常去的地方…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.94,0:10:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,May  Queen？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.23,0:10:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次约会去女仆咖啡厅？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.35,0:10:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器屋本铺
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.35,0:10:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买武器做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.98,0:10:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是在对着约会手册照本宣科而已
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.23,0:10:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别一副高高在上的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.71,0:10:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这美式处女
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.22,0:10:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是美式处女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.31,0:10:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除你之外还有谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.88,0:10:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好  处男  乙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.09,0:10:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说  比起看那种书还是这个好吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.05,0:10:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是黄色游戏的攻略本吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.01,0:10:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.12,0:10:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起约会不就是色情活动嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.83,0:10:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牵手什么的不也很色吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.22,0:10:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互相挽着手然后胸部碰着手臂之类的状态
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.03,0:10:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太色情了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.04,0:10:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  约会结束时就是接吻结尾吧  可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.04,0:11:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生赢家们都是混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.44,0:11:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果  什么计划都没有就早上了吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.48,0:11:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别嘟囔了  赶紧换衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.82,0:11:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,标签撕掉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.67,0:11:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那领带怎么打的啊  真不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.40,0:11:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  让人操心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.44,0:11:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.28,0:11:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得有种让人把脖子勒住的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.11,0:11:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  手帕也带上
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.23,0:11:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道该怎么用吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.49,0:11:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「现在我也在等着你」的暗号？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.27,0:11:34.23,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs18}「幸福的黄色手帕」是70年代的日本电影，剧中黄色手帕被作为依然在等待的暗号
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.27,0:11:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是幸福的黄色手帕
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.71,0:11:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种扭曲的知识算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.73,0:11:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说太老套了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.34,0:11:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是也知道嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.24,0:11:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.24,0:11:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正确的是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.49,0:11:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「当女生要坐在公园凳子上的时候为她铺上」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.19,0:11:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.42,0:11:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我后面悄悄跟上你们然后在关键时刻我会发短信给你建议的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.32,0:11:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  你要跟过来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.05,0:11:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桥田也一起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.53,0:11:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.93,0:11:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(270,325)\fscy80\fscx80\fsp0}Operation  Valkyria
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.93,0:11:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女武神作战  行动开始
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.54,0:12:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是北欧神话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.79,0:12:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在碰头的时候严禁迟到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.41,0:12:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最迟也要提前15分钟到达
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.88,0:12:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.92,0:12:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.81,0:12:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为已经出来得很早了  但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.96,0:12:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你久等了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.93,0:12:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…我也是刚刚才到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.08,0:12:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.95,0:12:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那么出发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.57,0:12:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.84,0:12:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是头一次看到没穿白大褂的冈部师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.22,0:12:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  因为是约会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.93,0:12:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和女孩子一起散步的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.43,0:12:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己要自然地走在靠车道的一侧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.83,0:12:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.50,0:13:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不…没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.93,0:13:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.89,0:13:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不自然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.07,0:13:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  在与汽车和摩托车擦身而过的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.74,0:13:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要若无其事地保护女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.59,0:13:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.65,0:13:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部师傅？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.99,0:13:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛痛痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.87,0:13:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.72,0:13:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来只是摔倒了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.08,0:13:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还在那里被女仆给救了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.77,0:13:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连餐巾纸都收下了  究竟在搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.22,0:13:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑氏好像很不爽啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.15,0:13:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今…今天真是风和日丽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.82,0:13:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.78,0:13:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是稍微有几片云彩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.85,0:13:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.80,0:13:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个蛋糕非常好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.74,0:13:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  咖啡也很好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.46,0:14:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  明明至今为止都能很自然地交谈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.56,0:14:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但一想到这是约会就…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.26,0:14:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里真是一家很棒的店啊  经常来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.55,0:14:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.28,0:14:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去很不妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.46,0:14:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是对话的传接球
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.37,0:14:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其…其实今天是第一次来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.85,0:14:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.16,0:14:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到第一次的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.68,0:14:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天8月14日是日本史上第一次授予专利的专利纪念日
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.12,0:14:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟在往哪传啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.08,0:14:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部师傅懂的真多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.45,0:14:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.09,0:14:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑氏  差不多该回去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.47,0:14:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是在看着  什么忙都没帮上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.19,0:14:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们要看到最后
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.40,0:14:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.57,0:14:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.87,0:14:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然很无聊吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.68,0:14:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我这样的人一起约会
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.28,0:14:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨…笨蛋  你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.34,0:14:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来要在街上闲逛了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.52,0:15:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.25,0:15:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小琉佳？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.20,0:15:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.24,0:15:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一个劲地走  都到上野走了一个来回了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.83,0:15:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.40,0:15:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得我们初次相遇时候的事情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.13,0:15:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.60,0:15:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被拿着相机的男人们纠缠着
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.63,0:15:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很为难的时候  你救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.73,0:15:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非…非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.98,0:15:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.83,0:15:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？为什么要道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.39,0:15:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我…虽然长成这样但却是男的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.94,0:16:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你是男是女  都没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.35,0:16:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情怎样都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.28,0:16:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候冈部师傅对我说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.69,0:16:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我感到非常的开心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.76,0:16:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有了那句话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.66,0:16:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才会喜欢上冈部师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.08,0:16:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「那种事情怎样都无所谓」吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.40,0:16:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…不  等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.45,0:16:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那岂不是琉佳子还是男人的时候的记忆吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.36,0:16:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  我…我究竟在说些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.78,0:16:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得好混乱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.39,0:16:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和菲伊莉斯的时候一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.74,0:16:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前的世界线的记忆…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.11,0:16:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真的是非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.76,0:16:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能成为我的恋人  非常的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.24,0:16:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常的…幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.61,0:16:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是妈妈的寻呼机号码
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.81,0:17:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉肉蔬菜蔬菜肉肉蔬菜蔬菜
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.47,0:17:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到这个的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.55,0:17:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漆原小姐的妈妈应该会认为之前的信息只是恶作剧了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.49,0:17:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.30,0:17:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  冈部
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.37,0:17:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘟嘟噜  听我说  听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.42,0:17:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏刚才看到了小琉佳和谁在约会
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.94,0:17:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是小冈伦哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.12,0:17:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？骗人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.08,0:17:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的绝对不是小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.09,0:17:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为穿着普通的衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.21,0:17:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且也很有绅士风度
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.93,0:17:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此  那样的才不是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.09,0:17:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样子琉佳子根本算不上是和我约会过了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.73,0:17:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.00,0:18:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会还没有结束
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.38,0:18:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？但是冈部师傅…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.10,0:18:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是凶真  连我的名字都忘了吗  琉佳子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.77,0:18:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是男的  是女的  还是恋人  混乱的其实是我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.54,0:18:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情怎样都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.26,0:18:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.26,0:18:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是我  琉佳子是琉佳子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.83,0:18:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的弟子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.23,0:18:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.06,0:18:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白的话  就把妖刀五月雨拿过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.76,0:18:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.10,0:00:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.27,0:18:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.40,0:18:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.69,0:18:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了琉佳子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.41,0:18:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来围绕着这把妖刀的传说要追溯到义经的时代
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.51,0:18:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是显现着死之色的满月之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.56,0:18:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孤身一人迷了路的…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.96,0:18:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又开始了啊  小冈伦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.08,0:18:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  和小琉佳和好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.75,0:19:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像已经不需要我们帮忙了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.17,0:19:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请去救真由理吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.01,0:19:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部师傅正在寻找的古董电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.42,0:19:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,IBN5100吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.05,0:19:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实到去年的正月为止都在我家的仓库里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.80,0:19:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我把它弄坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.10,0:19:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在打扫仓库的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.67,0:19:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以都是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.15,0:19:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部师傅  拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.08,0:19:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请一定要救真由理
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.18,0:19:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能久违地和冈部师傅一起修行真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.02,0:19:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉佳…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.43,0:19:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.35,0:19:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的话…我会哭出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.08,0:19:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候就要说惯例的暗号呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.11,0:19:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,EL  PSY  CONGARI
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.53,0:20:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是CONGROO
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.40,0:20:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,EL  PSY…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.85,0:20:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我并不想变回去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.28,0:20:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  因为
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.98,0:20:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是变回男孩子的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.49,0:20:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不得不把对冈部师傅的这份感情埋藏于心底
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.96,0:20:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为觉得明明是男的却还喜欢冈部师傅的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.97,0:20:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.79,0:20:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉佳子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.36,0:20:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变回男孩子的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.16,0:20:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的事情也全都会忘记吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.34,0:20:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.30,0:20:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久违的两人修行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.45,0:20:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像这样感受着冈部师傅身体的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.19,0:20:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果要体会这么痛苦的心情的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.77,0:20:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不该许愿要成为女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.70,0:20:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你变回了男人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.43,0:20:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于我来说琉佳子就是琉佳子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.18,0:20:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有任何改变
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.56,0:21:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.43,0:21:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是男是女
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.65,0:21:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情怎样都无所谓  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.21,0:21:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  再一会儿就好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.25,0:21:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请记住我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.02,0:21:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记住身为女孩子的我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.93,0:21:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我绝不会忘记的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.67,0:21:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  冈部师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.37,0:21:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漆原琉佳  言行举止都只能让人联想到女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.15,0:21:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是比女孩子更像女孩子的美少女
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.15,0:21:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  琉佳子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.89,0:21:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.14,0:21:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.02,0:21:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突…突然说些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.66,0:21:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.74,0:21:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.09,0:21:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很敬佩您
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.11,0:21:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…是男的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.86,0:22:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的短信  还有一条


