[Script Info]
Title:Steins;Gate 20 gb
Original Script:SumiSora & CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: up,微软雅黑,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00000040,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,6,30,30,10,134
Style: mail,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,15,15,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGHSGothic-W5,21,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,8,128
Style: OPCN,方正大黑_GBK,22,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFKaiSho_U-Md,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,7,128
Style: EDCN,方正楷体_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.98,0:02:25.96,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(545,335)}怨声断绝的凋亡
Comment: 0,0:00:34.00,0:00:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---OP---
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.66,0:01:09.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}数十億もの　鼓動の数さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.98,0:01:16.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたには　瞬き程度の些事な等級
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.72,0:01:21.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}過去に囚われて　未来も嘆くも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.68,0:01:27.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}塵一つ　誤算を許さぬ必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.77,0:01:33.80,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『無限』に広がる夢も　描く未来も
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.05,0:01:39.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕達に許された　虚栄の権利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.76,0:01:45.58,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『有限』それは二つの　針が示す
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.00,0:01:50.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷な約定と　選択へ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.49,0:01:52.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.92,0:01:59.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だからいま　１秒ごとに　世界線を超えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.68,0:02:04.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君のその笑顔　守りたいのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.62,0:02:11.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そしてまた　悲しみの無い　時間のループへと
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.66,0:02:14.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}飲み込まれてゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.21,0:02:17.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独の観測者
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.66,0:01:09.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}连同数十亿的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.98,0:01:16.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}对你来说  不过是转瞬即逝的琐事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.72,0:01:21.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}被过去所囚困  未来和悲叹
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.68,0:01:27.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}微尘般的误算  亦不允许的必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.77,0:01:33.80,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无限扩展的梦想  描绘的未来也
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.05,0:01:39.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我们所被赋予的  虚荣的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.76,0:01:45.58,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}有限  那即是两根指针所标示
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.00,0:01:50.49,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷的约定和选择
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.49,0:01:52.61,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an2}Hacking to the Gate ——
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.92,0:01:59.51,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所以现在  越过每一秒的世界线
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.68,0:02:04.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想守护你的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.62,0:02:11.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}于是进入没有悲伤的  时间的轮回
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.66,0:02:14.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}逐渐被吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.21,0:02:17.99,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独的观测者
Comment: 0,0:00:51.96,0:00:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---ED---
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.35,0:22:28.57,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}規制された視界　無慈悲なる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.09,0:22:37.45,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二の支配　逃れられない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.96,0:22:45.92,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}安息の　明日を　願った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.70,0:22:54.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手の中の　尊い事象の地平へ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.38,0:23:03.99,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚われし盟約　現れた偽証の輪郭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.99,0:23:12.89,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命の天地は　盲目な時間を刻んだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.13,0:23:15.44,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}羽ばたけバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.44,0:23:17.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇跡のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.41,0:23:21.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたへ捧ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.92,0:23:24.29,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}涙のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.29,0:23:26.38,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眩しいバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.38,0:23:29.63,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全てが————
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.63,0:23:33.81,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今書き換えられる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.35,0:22:28.57,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}扣上枷锁的视野如此无情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.09,0:22:37.45,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二条支配无法逃脱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.96,0:22:45.92,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}祈求得以安息的明日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.70,0:22:54.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手中的至爱流向事象的地平
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.38,0:23:03.99,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚禁的盟约  显现伪证的轮廓
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.99,0:23:12.89,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命的天地  刻上盲目的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.13,0:23:15.44,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}展翅而飞Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.44,0:23:17.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇迹的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.41,0:23:21.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全都为你献上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.92,0:23:24.29,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}泪水的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.29,0:23:26.38,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}耀眼的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.38,0:23:29.63,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}这一切——
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.63,0:23:33.81,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}现在都将改写
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---TEXT---
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.75,0:00:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样继续依赖着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.64,0:00:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被抛弃而死去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.80,0:00:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4天后  8月15日
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.89,0:00:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的死被这个世界所决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.84,0:00:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不可避免的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.07,0:00:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那种事情我可不干
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.96,0:00:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要反抗世界
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.15,0:00:24.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会救出真由理
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.11,0:00:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投币式储物柜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.23,0:00:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「大楼」前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.57,0:00:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,IBN5100
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.69,0:02:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部  怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.78,0:02:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  用这个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.40,0:02:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.51,0:02:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,IBN5100在投币储物柜里？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.36,0:02:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌郁坦白的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.21,0:02:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有被回收的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.13,0:03:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.03,0:03:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么好说的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.30,0:03:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这东西撬开柜子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.22,0:03:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点  你好好回想一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.50,0:03:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.16,0:03:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到现在为止的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.30,0:03:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管取消了很多D-Mail
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.32,0:03:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你仍未能得到IBN5100
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.16,0:03:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概  只要你不回到原来的世界线上去就不行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.37,0:03:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  为此只能按照顺序来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.53,0:03:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明已经近在眼前了啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.16,0:03:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我们抓到了线索
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.07,0:03:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐生萌郁的话  会听从那个叫FB的人的命令对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.79,0:03:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人就是Rounder的指挥官对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.80,0:03:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.91,0:04:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要监视着IBN5100  也许就能够和她接触
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.33,0:04:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.03,0:04:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也…想见FB
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.13,0:04:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是不想见么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.54,0:04:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许见了面会让你异常失望之类的？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.42,0:04:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想了解…真相
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.20,0:04:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你了解了又要怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.04,0:04:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.68,0:04:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我会和你一起行动吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.30,0:04:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  也不是无法交流的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.92,0:04:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.48,0:04:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.46,0:04:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和桐生萌郁在一起？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.31,0:05:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会那样？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.83,0:05:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  那个人是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.96,0:05:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之就是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.14,0:05:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一有动静我就会联系你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.72,0:05:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  等等  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.75,0:05:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.67,0:05:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.46,0:05:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.56,0:05:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.69,0:05:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得最近  和小冈伦都没怎么说过话的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.59,0:05:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.82,0:05:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小绹
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.57,0:05:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘟嘟噜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.65,0:05:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,助手姐姐  嘟嘟噜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.21,0:05:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是红莉栖姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.13,0:05:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您好  昨天真对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.52,0:05:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉冈部  房租涨5000
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.18,0:05:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.37,0:06:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来那家伙今天没见到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.01,0:06:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体搞坏了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.20,0:06:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然俗话说傻瓜不会得感冒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.82,0:06:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好像在到处搜集用来实验的道具
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.74,0:06:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实验啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.51,0:06:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是幸福的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.73,0:06:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区一个学生居然能租个大房子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.46,0:06:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有像你们这样的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.81,0:06:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起想做什么就做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.34,0:06:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.19,0:06:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.79,0:06:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  要是不快点的话限时大减价就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.40,0:06:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  走吧绹
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.16,0:06:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.01,0:06:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜  姐姐们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.62,0:06:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.25,0:06:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚饭你想吃什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.97,0:06:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  什么呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.61,0:06:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB的短信吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.52,0:06:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.28,0:06:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.73,0:07:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「M4的判断我认为是正确的」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.30,0:07:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「说实话  没有人干得比M4更卖力」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.42,0:07:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,M4？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.09,0:07:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB给我起的行动代号
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.25,0:07:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有FB和我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.00,0:07:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.34,0:07:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「你的确不擅长和别人打交道  M4」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.49,0:07:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「但那不也是你的个性吗？」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.44,0:07:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母亲吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.40,0:08:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  IBN5100
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.90,0:08:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  那家伙就是FB？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.80,0:08:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.31,0:08:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB是个女的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.30,0:08:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.79,0:09:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.82,0:09:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.12,0:09:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后我会解释
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.70,0:09:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mr.布朗…？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.47,0:10:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便问一下你的驾驶经验？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.76,0:10:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纸上驾照
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.28,0:10:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托开稳一点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.75,0:10:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对那个男的有印象吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.13,0:10:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没见过
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.82,0:10:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.65,0:10:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4天后  8月15日
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.68,0:10:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的死被这个世界所决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.68,0:10:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不可避免的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.97,0:11:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞往法国的航班
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.15,0:11:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,SERN所在国吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.32,0:11:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来像是FB的女人没出现呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.32,0:11:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少联系一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.34,0:11:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.72,0:11:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.88,0:11:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.03,0:11:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对真由理…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.79,0:11:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来  好像很久都没和她说过话了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.66,0:11:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子也这么说过
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.59,0:11:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.18,0:11:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.59,0:11:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有直接去找他问了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.20,0:12:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问他是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.44,0:12:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去问那个我们都很熟的人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.12,0:12:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦  这么一大早的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.86,0:12:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？  先进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.39,0:12:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.41,0:12:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻就来付上涨的6000日元租金了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.08,0:12:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  这里你应该吐槽说「是不是多了1000日元啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.24,0:12:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事情想问您
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.17,0:12:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么啊  这么一本正经地…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.62,0:12:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识一个名叫「FB」的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.52,0:12:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们全都看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.74,0:12:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,IBN5100从这里被搬出去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.21,0:13:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是想要你怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.62,0:13:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是想见到FB
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.28,0:13:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请告诉我们  她究竟在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.44,0:13:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像背叛了啊  M4
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.61,0:13:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB为我取的行动代号
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.77,0:13:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是只有FB和我才知道的秘密…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.76,0:13:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.61,0:13:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.54,0:13:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(350,325)\fscy80\fscx80\}Ferdinand  Braun
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.54,0:13:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道「费迪南德·布朗」吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.04,0:13:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是发明了布朗管的诺贝尔物理学奖得主
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.36,0:13:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名不虚传啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.78,0:13:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的头文字呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.15,0:13:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,F…B？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.55,0:13:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  你就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.22,0:13:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是  骗人的…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.21,0:13:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依赖之后又开始逃避现实吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.00,0:13:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绹在睡觉  换个地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.56,0:14:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个城市也在不断地发生变化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.57,0:14:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是  FB？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.98,0:14:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.37,0:14:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  短信呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.51,0:14:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都是我写的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.96,0:14:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会用女性用语吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.16,0:14:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是为了欺骗你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.93,0:14:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.41,0:14:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.99,0:14:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对别的人也都
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.98,0:14:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假扮成他所期望的人物形象来发短信
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.60,0:14:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.01,0:14:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样的家伙最好骗了  真是帮大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.71,0:14:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么和她断绝联系
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.57,0:14:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到IBN5100的时候那家伙就已经没用了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.19,0:14:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就舍弃了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.46,0:14:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过广告短信来召集成员
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.27,0:14:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的家伙们也方便差遣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.62,0:14:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用完之后也很好处理
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.19,0:14:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是原本就没有容身之地的家伙们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.46,0:14:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你居然是SERN的走狗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.70,0:14:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走狗？哼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.19,0:15:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃羽…桥田铃女士
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.51,0:15:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是为了让你干这些事而照顾你的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.63,0:15:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么会知道铃女士的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.34,0:15:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和铃女士没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.94,0:15:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和铃女士没有任何关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.98,0:15:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.83,0:15:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们又知道些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.60,0:15:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有在寒冬的下水道里面睡过觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.69,0:15:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候我还是个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.74,0:15:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混凝土可真是冷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.54,0:15:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,严寒入骨
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.87,0:15:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连续三四天什么都没有吃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.71,0:15:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要一躺下  它们就会过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.85,0:15:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老鼠会把你误认为尸体  来咬你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.09,0:15:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.97,0:15:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼前出现了一根丝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.32,0:16:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜘蛛丝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.37,0:16:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就只能去爬了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.06,0:16:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算那前方会让双手沾满污秽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.10,0:16:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那样沿着丝往上爬着
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.63,0:16:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回过神来发现自己已经是牵线木偶了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.20,0:16:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法逃脱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.59,0:16:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,断了线的木偶…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.55,0:17:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赐背叛者以死
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.55,0:17:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然完成任务后也一样会被消除
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.21,0:17:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说了我是「走狗」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.76,0:17:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本不是什么狗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.80,0:17:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是家畜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.88,0:17:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也曾想过要逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.90,0:17:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的我也有了重要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.84,0:17:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想把她卷进来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.42,0:17:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.84,0:17:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失败是绝对不被允许的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.35,0:17:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要逃跑的话  连家人也会…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.54,0:17:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.99,0:17:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是绹对此一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.46,0:18:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我死了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.42,0:18:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.38,0:18:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈…冈部…君
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.35,0:18:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈…部…君
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.11,0:18:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对…对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.33,0:18:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不…起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.98,0:19:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈…冈部  手机！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.95,0:19:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,D-Mail  冈部！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.07,0:19:15.03,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收信人  M4\N停止搜索IBN5100\N原地待命不要擅自行动
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.72,0:19:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌郁？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.79,0:19:35.22,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发信人：闪光的指压师\NIBN5100暂时不需要了\N萌郁
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.62,0:19:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要了？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.13,0:19:42.81,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上司命令我停止行动
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.12,0:19:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  我是漆原
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.12,0:19:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  凶真…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.93,0:19:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  IBN5100？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.82,0:19:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.24,0:19:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.83,0:20:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.81,0:20:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桥田的话不在哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.53,0:20:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说了要去CM吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.66,0:20:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  请听一下我的请求吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.31,0:20:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.42,0:20:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要避免真由理死亡的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.47,0:20:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要从我们现在所处的α世界线中脱出
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.92,0:20:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前往冈部发送第一封D-Mail之前的世界线
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.04,0:20:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,——β世界线才行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.24,0:20:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此只有删除在SERN的数据库里的数据
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.39,0:20:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏会死之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.02,0:20:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿万音氏是未来人而且是我的女儿之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.88,0:20:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果全都是妄想的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.49,0:20:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦我觉得你能当轻小说作家了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.48,0:20:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是真的就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.45,0:20:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑氏你信吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.28,0:20:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为假设来说还是可信的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.95,0:20:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的话还真想要些客观的数据
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.23,0:20:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个实在是没可能吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.69,0:20:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所制作出来的时间跳跃机器的质量非常可靠
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.34,0:21:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  是  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.76,0:21:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是理所当然的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.78,0:21:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.09,0:21:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.01,0:21:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.60,0:21:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟是什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.55,0:21:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.54,0:21:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连接好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.59,0:21:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要搞清楚设置才行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.40,0:21:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但10分钟内应该能完成
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.91,0:21:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  超级嘿客
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.55,0:21:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是超级黑客
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.63,0:21:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一封D-Mail吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.64,0:21:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是指那封吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.08,0:21:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我被捅了还是什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.78,0:21:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是你就打算摸我的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.14,0:21:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止的D-Mail全都被取消
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.05,0:21:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将世界线返回原样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.43,0:21:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里是——
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.12,0:21:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,SERN支配世界的反乌托邦不会出现的世界线
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.35,0:21:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理不会死亡的世界线
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.31,0:22:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  在那条世界线上…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.29,0:22:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧濑红莉栖会——
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.83,0:22:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死去


