[Script Info]
Title:Steins;Gate 19 gb
Original Script:SumiSora & CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: up,微软雅黑,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00000040,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,6,30,30,10,134
Style: mail,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,15,15,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGHSGothic-W5,21,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,8,128
Style: OPCN,方正大黑_GBK,22,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFKaiSho_U-Md,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,7,128
Style: EDCN,方正楷体_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.82,0:03:37.81,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(545,335)}无限连锁的凋亡
Comment: 0,0:00:16.00,0:00:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---OP---
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.66,0:00:50.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}数十億もの　鼓動の数さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.98,0:00:57.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたには　瞬き程度の些事な等級
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.72,0:01:02.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}過去に囚われて　未来も嘆くも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.68,0:01:08.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}塵一つ　誤算を許さぬ必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.77,0:01:14.80,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『無限』に広がる夢も　描く未来も
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.05,0:01:20.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕達に許された　虚栄の権利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.76,0:01:26.58,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『有限』それは二つの　針が示す
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.00,0:01:31.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷な約定と　選択へ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.49,0:01:33.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.92,0:01:40.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だからいま　１秒ごとに　世界線を超えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.68,0:01:45.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君のその笑顔　守りたいのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.62,0:01:52.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そしてまた　悲しみの無い　時間のループへと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.66,0:01:55.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}飲み込まれてゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.21,0:01:58.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独の観測者
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.66,0:00:50.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}连同数十亿的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.98,0:00:57.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}对你来说  不过是转瞬即逝的琐事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.72,0:01:02.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}被过去所囚困  未来和悲叹
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.68,0:01:08.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}微尘般的误算  亦不允许的必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.77,0:01:14.80,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无限扩展的梦想  描绘的未来也
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.05,0:01:20.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我们所被赋予的  虚荣的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.76,0:01:26.58,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}有限  那即是两根指针所标示
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.00,0:01:31.49,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷的约定和选择
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.49,0:01:33.61,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an2}Hacking to the Gate ——
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.92,0:01:40.51,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所以现在  越过每一秒的世界线
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.68,0:01:45.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想守护你的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.62,0:01:52.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}于是进入没有悲伤的  时间的轮回
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.66,0:01:55.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}逐渐被吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.21,0:01:58.99,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独的观测者
Comment: 0,0:00:50.96,0:00:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---ED---
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.25,0:22:27.47,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}規制された視界　無慈悲なる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.99,0:22:36.35,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二の支配　逃れられない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.86,0:22:44.82,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}安息の　明日を　願った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.60,0:22:53.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手の中の　尊い事象の地平へ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.28,0:23:02.89,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚われし盟約　現れた偽証の輪郭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.89,0:23:11.79,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命の天地は　盲目な時間を刻んだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.03,0:23:14.34,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}羽ばたけバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.34,0:23:16.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇跡のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.31,0:23:20.71,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたへ捧ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.82,0:23:23.19,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}涙のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.19,0:23:25.28,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眩しいバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.28,0:23:28.53,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全てが————
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.53,0:23:32.71,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今書き換えられる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.25,0:22:27.47,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}扣上枷锁的视野如此无情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.99,0:22:36.35,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二条支配无法逃脱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.86,0:22:44.82,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}祈求得以安息的明日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.60,0:22:53.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手中的至爱流向事象的地平
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.28,0:23:02.89,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚禁的盟约  显现伪证的轮廓
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.89,0:23:11.79,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命的天地  刻上盲目的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.03,0:23:14.34,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}展翅而飞Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.34,0:23:16.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇迹的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.31,0:23:20.71,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全都为你献上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.82,0:23:23.19,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}泪水的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.19,0:23:25.28,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}耀眼的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.28,0:23:28.53,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}这一切——
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.53,0:23:32.71,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}现在都将改写
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---TEXT---
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.14,0:02:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿扁了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.23,0:02:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天也要去CM…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.55,0:02:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天也要去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.81,0:02:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.75,0:02:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是这个时间回来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.45,0:02:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.92,0:02:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  红莉栖也一起来么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.24,0:02:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不太喜欢去人多的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.27,0:02:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二天应该没有那么多人的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.91,0:02:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小冈伦也一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.72,0:02:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部  过来一下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.83,0:02:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.15,0:03:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一回来你就这样阴沉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.52,0:03:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道不知道真由理一直都在为你打气么？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.28,0:03:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.78,0:03:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我能冷静吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.88,0:03:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在明天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.99,0:03:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算今天她没事  明天也…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.76,0:03:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经数不清这是第几遍跟你说明了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.57,0:03:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.24,0:03:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话要跟你说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.51,0:03:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天  真由理…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.07,0:03:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概会死
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.37,0:03:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始是13日的晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.17,0:03:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后每当我取消一封D-Mail  就能延后一天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.08,0:04:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明天跟她去CM
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.98,0:04:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有办法救她吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.90,0:04:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会看着她最后的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.54,0:04:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.45,0:04:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望知道这条世界线上准确的截止时间
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.47,0:04:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后根据这个再进行时间跳跃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.03,0:04:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没别的办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.18,0:04:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来该取消的  是叫桐生萌郁的人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.04,0:04:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  内容也知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.11,0:04:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她让过去的自己不要换手机
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.40,0:04:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次必须得用她的手机来发
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.46,0:04:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去找这个人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.49,0:04:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,CM由我跟她去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.66,0:04:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.63,0:04:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是顺利的话  就能在真由理…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.69,0:04:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前  说不定就能解决了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.67,0:04:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白自己在说什么吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.32,0:04:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是没找到萌郁的话  那就…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.75,0:04:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会马上联络你的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.58,0:05:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  什么话都可以对我说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.18,0:05:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论是什么  不论何时  都可以来找我谈
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.06,0:05:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  你一直都…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.09,0:05:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.00,0:05:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论在哪条世界线上  你都不是孤身一人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.74,0:05:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有我在
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.52,0:05:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  在有明
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.13,0:05:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多人啊  超乎想像
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.13,0:05:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.84,0:05:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有收到萌郁的回信  但是找到她打工的地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.71,0:05:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我调查一下那边看看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.85,0:05:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.77,0:05:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要勉强
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.85,0:05:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐生萌郁？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.58,0:05:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  以前干了两三天就辞职了的临时工就是这个名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.19,0:06:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住所？我是知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.61,0:06:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么人啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.02,0:06:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.03,0:06:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.05,0:06:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐生萌郁  自杀了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.11,0:06:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没弄错吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.45,0:06:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.11,0:06:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.16,0:06:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.41,0:06:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遗体已经送到了千代田第三医院
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.35,0:06:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似没有什么亲属  很头疼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.76,0:06:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.10,0:06:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.69,0:06:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自杀？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.06,0:06:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.87,0:06:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被同伙杀了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.20,0:06:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在杀真由理之前？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.83,0:06:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.39,0:07:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理由什么的无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.45,0:07:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么下去的话  真由理就…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.43,0:07:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间跳跃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.66,0:07:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳跃到萌郁死之前
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.36,0:07:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈…冈部…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.17,0:07:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.18,0:07:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.24,0:07:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真…真由理…真由理她…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.05,0:07:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,截止时间是19:52
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.69,0:07:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.42,0:07:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.57,0:07:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你吃了这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.19,0:07:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.66,0:07:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是写着的吗  牧濑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.92,0:07:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你在听么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.82,0:07:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.27,0:08:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.31,0:08:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.61,0:08:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错啊  红莉栖
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.56,0:08:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.82,0:08:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道一个叫桐生萌郁的女人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.04,0:08:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.29,0:08:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚时间跳跃过来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.86,0:08:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.60,0:08:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.62,0:09:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.33,0:09:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.04,0:09:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.87,0:09:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.58,0:09:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.23,0:09:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.82,0:09:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不给我短信
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.59,0:09:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  给我回信
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.26,0:09:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.83,0:09:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐生萌郁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.43,0:09:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经按你说的去做了  为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.28,0:09:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.47,0:09:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.58,0:09:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我命令吧  FB
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.29,0:09:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听不到吗？喂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.16,0:09:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.53,0:09:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.53,0:09:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.58,0:09:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.12,0:09:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.55,0:09:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.89,0:10:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.01,0:10:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…不会原谅她的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.88,0:10:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.01,0:10:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.24,0:10:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.21,0:10:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是牧濑  手机呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.65,0:10:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抢过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.55,0:10:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好发D-Mail
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.95,0:10:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.42,0:10:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么声音？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.34,0:10:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用在意
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.47,0:10:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  真由理呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.73,0:10:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在布朗管工房  42寸电视现在开着
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.75,0:10:45.63,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧换手机  马上就断货了买不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.02,0:10:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红莉栖  赶紧启动
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.15,0:10:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.09,0:10:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就能结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.96,0:10:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要发送了这个  真由理就…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.98,0:11:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我  把手机还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.89,0:11:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？  什么事都没发生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.42,0:11:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.27,0:11:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发送了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.18,0:11:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发送了  正常启动了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.34,0:11:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了放电现象  怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.70,0:11:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命运探知没有发动
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.70,0:11:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(280,325)\fscy80\fscx80\fsp0}Reading Steiner
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.40,0:11:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命运探知没有发动…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.40,0:11:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(270,325)\fscy80\fscx80\fsp0}Reading Steiner
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.47,0:11:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.54,0:11:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我  还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.20,0:11:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  怎么回事啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.01,0:11:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我  还给我  还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.47,0:11:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.86,0:11:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,D-Mail的效果会受收件人的影响
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.89,0:11:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用冈部的写法不能改变桐生萌郁的行动？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.05,0:11:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那该怎么做？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.69,0:12:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并没有改变
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.44,0:12:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她并没有换手机
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.13,0:12:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.24,0:12:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是好好确认过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.23,0:12:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四天前我换了手机
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.63,0:12:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是想告诉自己不要换比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.98,0:12:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在发送之前她换成别的短信了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.01,0:12:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.91,0:12:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说不知道D-Mail的内容了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.18,0:12:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该还存有收信记录的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.50,0:12:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就调查…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.03,0:12:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.51,0:12:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  冈部
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.99,0:12:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.67,0:12:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会再和你联络的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.02,0:12:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.49,0:12:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.01,0:12:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.67,0:12:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我  还给我！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.75,0:12:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你们在搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.28,0:13:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.66,0:13:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.16,0:13:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我  还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.73,0:13:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  究竟在搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.80,0:13:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.12,0:13:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  最近的情侣啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.36,0:13:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕  好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.88,0:14:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么做…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.06,0:14:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.11,0:14:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.66,0:14:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得你发送了D-Mail的事情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.78,0:14:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,D…什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.20,0:14:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个星期前你应该收到了一条奇怪的短信
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.82,0:14:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从未来的自己那里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.99,0:14:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.26,0:14:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把内容告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.58,0:14:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话就还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.34,0:14:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  说不出口吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.42,0:14:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和IBN5100和Rounder有关的事情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.68,0:14:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说中了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.89,0:14:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回答我  短信究竟是什么内容
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.08,0:14:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想要手机了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.96,0:14:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能背叛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.90,0:14:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背叛谁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.91,0:14:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫「FB」的家伙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.27,0:14:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的指令都是由FB下达的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.76,0:15:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB就是我的全部
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.36,0:15:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙就是你们的指挥官吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.93,0:15:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能背叛吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.79,0:15:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是相当忠诚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.79,0:15:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那个叫FB的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.56,0:15:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于你的事情好像无所谓啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.90,0:15:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你将会就这样被FB所抛弃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.07,0:15:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.39,0:15:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有联络了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.39,0:15:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被背叛了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.14,0:15:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被抛弃了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.30,0:15:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  FB才不是那样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.35,0:15:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB拯救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.93,0:15:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被利用了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.35,0:16:13.51,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)}收件箱\N募集Rounder\NFB\N2006:6:21
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.90,0:16:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我能说出那种话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.67,0:16:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.76,0:16:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB是像母亲一样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.49,0:16:20.72,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怎样的工作呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.96,0:16:26.18,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是提供适合当事人的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.81,0:16:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拥有一种时间机器
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.74,0:16:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从未来发来的短信就是证据
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.77,0:16:28.18,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也能做到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.37,0:16:32.10,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.58,0:16:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人需要我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.94,0:16:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没工作过
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.09,0:16:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有任何特长
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.60,0:16:37.78,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.78,0:16:41.24,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.35,0:16:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我全都看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.94,0:16:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.57,0:17:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4天后  你将在这个房间里自杀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.73,0:17:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等待着FB的联络
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.60,0:17:09.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人在这里孤独地死去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.31,0:17:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.09,0:17:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.61,0:17:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从FB那里已经不会再来任何联络了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.61,0:17:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被抛弃了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.13,0:17:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.89,0:17:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从什么时候起就没有联络了  啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.86,0:17:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都在等着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.60,0:17:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得这很奇怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.49,0:17:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会死去…就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.27,0:17:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.78,0:17:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个阴暗而又空荡荡的房间里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.27,0:17:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.10,0:17:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀害了真由理的你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.76,0:17:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里  一个人  被抛弃  被背叛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.75,0:17:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像个垃圾一样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.73,0:17:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,断送性命
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.73,0:17:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fsy80\fscx80}不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.48,0:17:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都不会来救你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.54,0:17:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连FB也不会
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.14,0:17:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.79,0:17:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.08,0:18:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.04,0:18:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说了「母亲」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.64,0:18:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FB是女的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.22,0:18:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.76,0:18:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.38,0:18:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有见过面
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.78,0:18:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想见面
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.28,0:18:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见面的话一定会非常失望
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.32,0:18:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来连电话都没有打过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.39,0:18:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真亏你能对这种家伙言听计从
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.69,0:19:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给了我容身之地
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.68,0:19:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,容身之地？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.46,0:19:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是傻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.67,0:19:17.64,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,古董电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.64,0:19:18.24,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在柳林神社仓库
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.24,0:19:19.64,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧回收
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.22,0:19:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.80,0:19:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让我担心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.42,0:19:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在担心我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.11,0:19:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有担心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.89,0:19:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.68,0:19:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.46,0:19:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么偷走了IBN5100的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.79,0:19:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌郁
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.97,0:19:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.04,0:19:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他什么都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.72,0:19:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照预定要消除D-Mail
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.90,0:19:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,7月31日的上午11点左右吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.80,0:19:57.63,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,400)}别去神社那是陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.22,0:20:00.27,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,0)}没有东西！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.40,0:19:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,启动了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.14,0:20:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定要
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.49,0:20:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.64,0:20:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.64,0:20:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.06,0:20:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去的桐生萌郁没有相信D-Mail吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.83,0:20:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防万一  还是相信了最初的D-Mail吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.96,0:20:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用别的写法再发一次…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.88,0:20:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.62,0:20:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕能让萌郁行动的只有那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.10,0:20:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能用那家伙的手机发短信的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.42,0:20:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就应该会无条件地服从
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.65,0:20:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.66,0:20:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去找FB
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.62,0:20:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于他的所在有什么线索吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.73,0:20:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不可能会告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.39,0:21:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才所说的  我杀了人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.58,0:21:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是未来的事情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.98,0:21:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  如果是FB的命令的话你会下手的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.54,0:21:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  一定会
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.85,0:21:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使知道是在被利用吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.71,0:21:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样继续依赖着
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.84,0:21:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被抛弃而死去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.29,0:21:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4天后  8月15日
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.32,0:21:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的死被这个世界所决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.30,0:21:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不可避免的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.36,0:21:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那种事情我可不干
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.22,0:21:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要反抗世界
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.43,0:21:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会救出真由理
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.49,0:21:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投币式储物柜
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.59,0:22:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「{\1c&0000E0&}大楼{\r}」前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.84,0:22:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,IBN5100


