[Script Info]
Title:Steins;Gate 17 gb
Original Script:SumiSora & CASO
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: up,微软雅黑,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正小标宋_GBK,20,&H00000040,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,6,30,30,10,134
Style: mail,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,15,15,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGHSGothic-W5,21,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,4,0,2,30,30,8,128
Style: OPCN,方正大黑_GBK,22,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H80FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,4,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: EDJP,DFKaiSho_U-Md,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,30,30,7,128
Style: EDCN,方正楷体_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H30000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.64,0:03:53.64,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(545,335)}虚像歪曲的混合
Comment: 0,0:00:30.00,0:00:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---OP---
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.66,0:01:05.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}数十億もの　鼓動の数さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.98,0:01:12.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたには　瞬き程度の些事な等級
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.72,0:01:17.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}過去に囚われて　未来も嘆くも
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.68,0:01:23.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}塵一つ　誤算を許さぬ必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.77,0:01:29.80,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『無限』に広がる夢も　描く未来も
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.05,0:01:35.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}僕達に許された　虚栄の権利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.76,0:01:41.58,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}『有限』それは二つの　針が示す
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.00,0:01:46.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷な約定と　選択へ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.49,0:01:48.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.92,0:01:55.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だからいま　１秒ごとに　世界線を超えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.68,0:02:00.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君のその笑顔　守りたいのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.62,0:02:07.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そしてまた　悲しみの無い　時間のループへと
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.66,0:02:10.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}飲み込まれてゆく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.21,0:02:13.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独の観測者
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.66,0:01:05.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}连同数十亿的心跳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.98,0:01:12.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}对你来说  不过是转瞬即逝的琐事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.72,0:01:17.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}被过去所囚困  未来和悲叹
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.68,0:01:23.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}微尘般的误算  亦不允许的必然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.77,0:01:29.80,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}无限扩展的梦想  描绘的未来也
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.05,0:01:35.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}我们所被赋予的  虚荣的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.76,0:01:41.58,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}有限  那即是两根指针所标示
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.00,0:01:46.49,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}残酷的约定和选择
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.49,0:01:48.61,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\an2}Hacking to the Gate ——
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.92,0:01:55.51,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所以现在  越过每一秒的世界线
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.68,0:02:00.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想守护你的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.62,0:02:07.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}于是进入没有悲伤的  时间的轮回
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.66,0:02:10.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}逐渐被吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.21,0:02:13.99,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}孤独的观测者
Comment: 0,0:00:51.06,0:00:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---ED---
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.25,0:22:28.47,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}規制された視界　無慈悲なる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.99,0:22:37.35,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二の支配　逃れられない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.86,0:22:45.82,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}安息の　明日を　願った
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.60,0:22:54.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手の中の　尊い事象の地平へ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.28,0:23:03.89,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚われし盟約　現れた偽証の輪郭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.89,0:23:12.79,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命の天地は　盲目な時間を刻んだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.03,0:23:15.34,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}羽ばたけバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.34,0:23:17.83,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇跡のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.31,0:23:21.71,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたへ捧ぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.82,0:23:24.19,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}涙のバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.19,0:23:26.28,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}眩しいバタフライ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.28,0:23:29.53,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全てが————
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.53,0:23:33.71,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}今書き換えられる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.25,0:22:28.47,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}扣上枷锁的视野如此无情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.99,0:22:37.35,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}十二条支配无法逃脱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.86,0:22:45.82,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}祈求得以安息的明日
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.60,0:22:54.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}手中的至爱流向事象的地平
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.28,0:23:03.89,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}囚禁的盟约  显现伪证的轮廓
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.89,0:23:12.79,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}生命的天地  刻上盲目的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.03,0:23:15.34,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}展翅而飞Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.34,0:23:17.83,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}奇迹的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.31,0:23:21.71,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}全都为你献上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.82,0:23:24.19,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}泪水的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.19,0:23:26.28,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}耀眼的Butterfly
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.28,0:23:29.53,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}这一切——
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.53,0:23:33.71,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}现在都将改写
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,---TEXT---
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.01,0:00:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.89,0:00:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从Mr.布朗的家回去后
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.51,0:00:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终  什么事也没发生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.65,0:00:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌郁他们本来应该
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.44,0:00:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现在13日星期五的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.84,0:00:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说我发送的放弃跟踪铃羽的短信
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.23,0:00:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改变了世界线了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.59,0:00:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  就这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.20,0:00:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理也不会死  什么事也不会发生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.60,0:00:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.06,0:00:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏的怀表停掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.06,0:00:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪  明明刚刚才上过发条的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.04,0:02:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.17,0:02:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说的是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.20,0:02:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.55,0:02:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理…在两小时后？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.54,0:02:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你重复着时间跳跃  无数次…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.04,0:02:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经历了那个？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.93,0:02:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定不好受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.25,0:02:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据阿万音小姐所说的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.91,0:02:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我们从现在所在的α世界线收束范围移动到β世界线的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.91,0:02:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(343,325)\fscy80\fscx80}Attractor Field
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.66,0:03:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理就能得救
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.18,0:03:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此  我们必须要使用IBN5100
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.59,0:03:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,删除掉SERN所掌握的关于你们的情报
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.04,0:03:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  本应该在柳林神社的IBN5100
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.37,0:03:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在世界线发生移动的同时消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.15,0:03:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止所发送的D-Mail中造成世界线移动的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.65,0:03:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有六合彩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.86,0:03:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐生小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.85,0:03:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漆原小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.85,0:03:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.97,0:03:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有跟踪阿万音小姐的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.73,0:03:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取消掉最后的那条跟踪阿万音小姐的短信之后
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.35,0:03:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,袭击延后了一天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.88,0:03:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说  只要按相反顺序取消掉所发送过的D-Mail的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.02,0:03:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能回到拥有IBN5100的原世界线中去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.36,0:03:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只是假说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.51,0:03:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有任何科学依据
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.69,0:03:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.18,0:03:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要存在可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.37,0:04:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是我提议的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.89,0:04:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是要取消掉所有的D-Mail…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.17,0:04:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  工作量相当大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.36,0:04:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不得不做
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.54,0:04:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保重
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.49,0:04:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的大脑是重要的样本
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.69,0:04:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算移动过世界线也能保持记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.14,0:04:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能忍受时间跳跃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.71,0:04:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该测量一下…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.67,0:04:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  红莉栖
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.46,0:04:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫我红莉栖  我…会忘掉的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.59,0:04:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.28,0:04:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.87,0:05:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照顺序的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.23,0:05:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个应该取消的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.20,0:05:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯的D-Mail
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.11,0:05:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.12,0:05:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至  菲伊莉斯在哪里你应该心里有数吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.62,0:05:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.58,0:05:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪  在哪里啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.34,0:05:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,UPX会场
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.54,0:05:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在雷Net的ABGC的决赛刚刚结束
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.98,0:05:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ABGC？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.22,0:05:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fsp0}雷Net Access Battlers Grand Championship的缩略啊常考
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.20,0:05:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日本雷Net玩家齐聚一堂的大会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.74,0:05:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  现在以菲伊莉斯取得优胜结束
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.93,0:05:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好兴奋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.19,0:05:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯发送了D-Mail之后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.75,0:05:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋叶原变了回原来的电器街
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.11,0:05:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不清楚短信的内容
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.79,0:05:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底发送给谁了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.83,0:05:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发送了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.74,0:05:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.31,0:06:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯  怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.22,0:06:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  母猫跟一个穿白衣的男人在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.97,0:06:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能让他们跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.01,0:06:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  应该说他们跑不了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.84,0:06:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我的黑暗力量手中  谁都跑不了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.46,0:06:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁在追你啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.16,0:06:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Viral Attackers喵
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.18,0:06:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Viral Attackers？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.17,0:06:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论使用何种卑鄙手段都要取胜的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.60,0:06:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本不配玩雷Net的家伙们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.70,0:06:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为输给了菲伊莉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.29,0:06:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就来伏击了喵
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.32,0:06:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伏击…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.24,0:06:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.36,0:07:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪里了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.85,0:07:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该还在附近
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.56,0:07:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.60,0:07:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来  刚才你好像给我打电话了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.25,0:07:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.46,0:07:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能告诉我D-Mail的内容
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.66,0:07:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,D-Mail？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.28,0:07:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发送给过去的短信
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.39,0:07:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给过去的短信？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.84,0:07:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么喵？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.40,0:07:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这条世界线上的菲伊莉斯并没有D-Mail的记忆…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.93,0:07:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  该怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.70,0:07:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.05,0:07:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如  我说假如
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.36,0:07:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要是制作出了时间机器  你会相信吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.96,0:07:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真说是的话我就相信
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.14,0:07:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.10,0:07:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯也开发出了能移动到二次元世界的机器喵
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.54,0:08:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如  秋叶原是一个充满了萌元素的街区
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.46,0:08:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用时间机器  把它变成了像现在一样的电器街
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.48,0:08:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会用什么样的方式？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.02,0:08:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么心理游戏啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.25,0:08:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是什么  回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.33,0:08:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这么说…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.97,0:08:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  充满萌元素的街区很让人开心喵
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.21,0:08:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  以前跟爸爸说过
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.15,0:08:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我在秋叶原开一家女仆咖啡店如何之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.63,0:08:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  遗憾的是被他拒绝了喵
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.83,0:08:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的是May  Queen吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.94,0:08:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你知道那个名字？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.07,0:08:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都没告诉爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.18,0:08:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前有的  May  Queen
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.72,0:08:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这秋叶原
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.84,0:08:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋叶原本来就是一个充满了萌元素的街区
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.15,0:08:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.22,0:08:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比谁都爱这个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.26,0:09:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是因为你所发送的短信
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.34,0:09:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个街区都变样了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.12,0:09:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底发送了什么样的短信？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.81,0:09:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.16,0:09:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了  在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.77,0:09:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了喵？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.25,0:09:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.89,0:09:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,May  Queen本来应该在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.02,0:09:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要开的店
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.29,0:09:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.05,0:09:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里工作过
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.45,0:09:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理也是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.00,0:09:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿至是这里的常客
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.18,0:09:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是在这里认识的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.98,0:09:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来  主人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.66,0:10:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.56,0:10:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上菲伊莉斯杯白天部分就要开始了喵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.46,0:10:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作战代号  G·B·A·C·K
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.74,0:10:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「世界有危险」来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.28,0:10:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天来了好多主人  好热闹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.72,0:10:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.95,0:10:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.02,0:10:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是不取消D-Mail的话  会怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.73,0:10:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理的性命…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.37,0:10:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.63,0:10:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你骗人喵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.27,0:10:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是骗人的喵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.33,0:10:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏的性命有危险是怎么回事喵？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.54,0:10:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道了短信的内容了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.42,0:10:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.89,0:10:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不取消它不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.93,0:10:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.67,0:10:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.43,0:10:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由理…真由理死了也无所谓吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.43,0:10:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能喵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.15,0:10:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.87,0:10:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.88,0:11:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让十年前死去的爸爸复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.28,0:11:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我改变了爸爸会死去的过去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.95,0:11:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.54,0:11:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.44,0:11:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你斯文扫地了呢  小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.42,0:11:47.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  公主殿下  跟我们走一趟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.05,0:11:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放手喵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.37,0:11:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.71,0:11:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  我们抓到母猫了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.46,0:11:55.67,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的那超危险的气场
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.67,0:11:59.81,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才开始就一直告诉我要把她染成黑色…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.01,0:11:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快就见到那位大人了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.48,0:11:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那之前  我们就…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.37,0:12:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.89,0:12:03.93,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够站在第一线的永远只有一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.38,0:12:09.04,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是披着黑色羽毛的孔雀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.94,0:12:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开她
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.89,0:12:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.90,0:12:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.09,0:12:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还打算继续耍帅吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.85,0:12:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手  拜托你们住手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.37,0:12:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.51,0:12:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.41,0:12:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  给我站住  你们都干了些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.90,0:12:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了啊  4℃大人参上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.87,0:12:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？怎么了你们这帮家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.00,0:12:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？警察…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.56,0:12:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？逮捕…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.54,0:12:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.74,0:12:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.70,0:12:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.21,0:12:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.44,0:12:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接到联系说你获胜了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.98,0:13:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶来为你庆祝  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.80,0:13:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会场里找不到人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.34,0:13:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打手机也不接所以找了好半天
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.37,0:13:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈部君  该怎么向你道谢才好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.30,0:13:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道谢什么的  不需要…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.07,0:13:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我去观看比赛的话说不定就不会发生这种事情了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.50,0:13:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  爸爸因为有工作所以也没办法喵
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.01,0:13:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留未穗…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.14,0:13:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,IBN5100?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.14,0:13:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  听说您以前出手了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.78,0:13:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.21,0:13:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能取回呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.00,0:13:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有原因的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.88,0:13:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了件对不起桥田女士的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.77,0:13:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桥田女士…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.44,0:13:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是桥田铃女士吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.56,0:13:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.12,0:13:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是她把IBN5100交给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.86,0:13:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没关系  一定会找到IBN5100的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.00,0:14:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃羽为我们拿到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.00,0:14:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  可以告诉他吗喵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.10,0:14:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.38,0:14:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命恩人很想知道啊喵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.21,0:14:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前  留未穗曾经被绑架过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.01,0:14:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候公司规模还没有现在这么大
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.89,0:14:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿不出赎金
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.21,0:14:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那时候出现了愿意高价收购IBN5100的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.36,0:14:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就出手了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.71,0:14:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏这样才能凑齐了赎金
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.10,0:14:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那以后  无论发生什么我都会遵守和女儿之间的约定
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.62,0:14:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是多么微小的约定  也无论发生什么事情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.58,0:14:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.97,0:14:53.76,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}画上的字  左：爸爸  右：留未穗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.93,0:14:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让十年前死去的爸爸复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.14,0:15:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我改变了爸爸会死去的过去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.28,0:15:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果取消D-Mail的话  那个人…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.95,0:15:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦  你要发送D-Mail吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.33,0:15:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么做的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.64,0:15:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都会消失的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.74,0:15:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果不这么做的话  真由理  你就会…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.36,0:15:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以进来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.23,0:15:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请进
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.79,0:15:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.18,0:15:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…刚才真是谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.89,0:15:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我非常的害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.88,0:15:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是第一次感受到那么多人的黑色感情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.03,0:15:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来他们所有人都穿的一身黑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.14,0:15:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  我明明很认真地在说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.58,0:16:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.20,0:16:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.41,0:16:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能叫我「留未穗」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.40,0:16:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真  不  如果没有冈部先生的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.96,0:16:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不知道会发生什么事情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.64,0:16:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别改口  和平时一样就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.94,0:16:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  凶真  真是非常感谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.83,0:16:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真呢  是我的王子殿下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.67,0:16:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王子殿下？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.63,0:16:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是什么王子殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.95,0:16:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是疯狂的那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.28,0:16:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.81,0:16:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏的性命有危险  是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.17,0:16:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.28,0:16:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是10年前  我8岁的生日
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.93,0:16:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和爸爸约好了一起出去玩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.52,0:16:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是由于工作原因去不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.93,0:17:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是没办法的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.86,0:17:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但很寂寞  觉得爸爸其实并不爱我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.45,0:17:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想着「爸爸什么的不管了  干脆死掉算了」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.05,0:17:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.82,0:17:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是和爸爸的最后一次交谈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.10,0:17:17.57,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事故中确认死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.56,0:17:19.64,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)}日本人…秋叶幸高
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.80,0:17:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要改变那样的过去  发了D-Mail
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.90,0:17:23.47,up,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你女儿在我手里  赎金1亿  去坐新干线
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.30,0:17:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是你父亲就避开了事故
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.70,0:17:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也没有积极地将萌文化融入街区
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.32,0:17:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋叶原就仍然是电器街吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.45,0:17:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很幸福啊  这10年
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.88,0:17:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲…留未穗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.66,0:17:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发D-Mail吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.15,0:17:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸在10年前的事故中去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.05,0:17:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才是真实
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.10,0:17:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这10年只是一场梦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.48,0:17:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他一起生活  也明白他是多么爱我了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.47,0:18:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏是我的朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.40,0:18:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可没法耍什么性子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.02,0:18:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.94,0:18:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.04,0:18:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想起了世界线变化前的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.55,0:18:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是变化后的事情也还记着
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.66,0:18:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变化前和后的事情纠缠在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.46,0:18:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快要分不清哪边才是真实了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.99,0:18:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定还有什么别的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.56,0:18:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  再找红莉栖商量一次
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.57,0:18:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经够了  不想给凶真添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.57,0:18:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为凶真是我的王子殿下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.34,0:18:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要从梦中醒来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.81,0:18:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我只有一个请求
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.06,0:19:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以让我稍微哭一会儿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.90,0:19:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.80,0:19:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯小姐她…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.88,0:19:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  接受了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.67,0:19:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做准备吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.22,0:19:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了喵
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.87,0:19:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵喵  怎么了喵  凶真
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.68,0:19:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么精神哦喵
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.72,0:19:48.89,mail,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)}绑架是开玩笑的\N爸爸我爱你\N回头见哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.87,0:19:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便问一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.57,0:19:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界变回原状之后
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.62,0:19:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的记忆就会全都消失吗喵
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是拥有改变过去之前和之后两边的记忆吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.52,0:20:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定不会忘记的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.11,0:20:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.74,0:20:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯不想忘记和凶真一起度过的时光
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.29,0:20:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.18,0:20:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,启动了  冈部
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.14,0:20:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜  爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.88,0:20:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.37,0:20:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有看到菲伊莉斯的手机啊喵
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.80,0:20:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.46,0:20:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由氏也说不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.49,0:20:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的就只有凶真了喵
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.03,0:20:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵？喵喵
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.24,0:20:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真  你看了这里面的「那个」吗喵
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.49,0:21:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看了的话就忘掉吧  那是必须封印的东西喵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.80,0:21:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真  刚才那是应该吐槽的地方喵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.41,0:21:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「那个」是指什么啊「那个」像这样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.24,0:21:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲伊莉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.18,0:21:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.09,0:21:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.39,0:21:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那双手算是什么意思啊  那双手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.38,0:21:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又打算做什么变态的事情了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.47,0:21:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小冈伦真大胆啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.88,0:21:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶真和菲伊莉斯在前世是与巨大的黑暗作斗争的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.17,0:21:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相爱的恋人喵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.71,0:21:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关系很亲密的喵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.46,0:21:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和各种各样的人战斗着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.71,0:21:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说菲伊莉斯小姐和冈部是同一类人…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.28,0:21:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.78,0:21:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柳林神社里并没有IBN5100
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.29,0:21:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10年前  菲伊莉斯确实把它供奉在了这里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.01,0:22:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到去年都还在这里  但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.23,0:22:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟在哪里


