[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.45,0:02:54.45,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}记忆之门
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.92,0:24:15.98,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\pos(178,296)}遥遥家路
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.00,0:22:36.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだうしろ姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.59,0:22:43.07,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.79,0:22:49.20,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}やさしさで胸がいたくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.73,0:22:56.60,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々がいとおしくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.79,0:23:09.86,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音(ね)に　夕闇に　懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.57,0:23:22.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも一緒だよ、と　叶わぬことくり返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:27.93,0:23:33.53,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}ぬくもりはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.23,0:23:39.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}あざやかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.58,0:23:46.82,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.37,0:23:56.57,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来にかえながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.00,0:22:36.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだうしろ姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.59,0:22:43.07,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.79,0:22:49.20,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}やさしさで胸がいたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.73,0:22:56.60,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々がいとおしくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.79,0:23:09.86,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音(ね)に　夕闇に　懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.57,0:23:22.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも一緒だよ、と　叶わぬことくり返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.93,0:23:33.53,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}ぬくもりはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.23,0:23:39.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}あざやかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.58,0:23:46.82,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.37,0:23:56.57,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来にかえながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.00,0:22:36.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.59,0:22:43.07,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.79,0:22:49.20,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.73,0:22:56.60,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.79,0:23:09.86,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下  回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.57,0:23:22.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离  辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:27.93,0:23:33.53,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.23,0:23:39.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.58,0:23:46.82,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.37,0:23:56.57,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.00,0:22:36.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.59,0:22:43.07,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.79,0:22:49.20,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.73,0:22:56.60,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.79,0:23:09.86,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下  回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.57,0:23:22.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离  辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.93,0:23:33.53,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.23,0:23:39.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.58,0:23:46.82,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.37,0:23:56.57,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.30,0:01:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢各位乘坐JL九州列车
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.81,0:01:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本列车为箱田方向特急YAMOME38号
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.04,0:01:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真令人期待呢  等到站了想去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.52,0:01:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  能让开吗  这是我的座位
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.32,0:02:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人  有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.09,0:02:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  什么事都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.43,0:02:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直闲置着的老家就要被出售了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.15,0:02:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是决定最后再去看一眼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.41,0:02:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出生不久母亲就去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.26,0:02:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是和父亲两人仅生活了几年的家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.96,0:02:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为当时还太小  记不太清了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.92,0:02:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着地图应该能找得到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.51,0:02:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂夏目  给我买车内便当  这事最优先！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.94,0:02:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师  为什么跟来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.13,0:02:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车内便当  车内便当…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.81,0:03:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便当  绿茶  咖啡  果汁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.61,0:03:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美酒配上佳肴如何呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.45,0:03:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给我便当
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.89,0:03:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一份便当是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.81,0:03:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  请给我两份
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.38,0:03:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两份？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.61,0:03:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  就两份
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.57,0:03:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,箱田站到了  箱田站
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.32,0:03:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  要换乘了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.06,0:03:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想先绕道去一个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.70,0:03:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钥匙似乎放在离老家最近的亲戚家里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.92,0:03:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须去那里领取
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.03,0:04:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识路吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.74,0:04:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  以前也受到过那家人的关照
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.81,0:04:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想能边走边记起路吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.96,0:04:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢  往左还是往右
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.70,0:04:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  看下地图…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.54,0:04:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连往左还是往右都不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.59,0:04:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让总是四处寄住都分不清哪是哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.49,0:04:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是这边吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.48,0:04:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是靠不住的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.37,0:04:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦夏目  有乌冬面店
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.97,0:04:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就以那家店为中心来回忆吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.94,0:04:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还从没靠着乌冬面店来认路呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.67,0:05:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个味道…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.59,0:05:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放学回家的路上总能闻到这个香味呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.53,0:05:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是靠着奇怪的东西想起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.10,0:05:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往这边  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.45,0:05:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂等一下  不吃面吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.46,0:05:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚吃过便当了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.67,0:05:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌冬…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.32,0:05:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这条路  这家的柿子常常掉到路上来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.64,0:05:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看  那户人家的山茶花很漂亮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.44,0:05:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那户人家住着一位温柔的老奶奶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.00,0:05:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时不时的会偷偷地给我一些点心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.23,0:06:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会忘记了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.62,0:06:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.39,0:06:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动作麻利点  走了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.62,0:06:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妖怪的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.01,0:06:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来这一带也有着很多妖怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.56,0:06:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概就是那幢了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.16,0:06:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是拿钥匙而已  老师就在外面等着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.98,0:06:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带着猫咪显得挺奇怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.19,0:06:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么奇怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.09,0:06:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为回报回去的时候会请你吃乌冬面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.42,0:06:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但若我很久都没出来  你可要来救我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.26,0:06:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  为什么  那里有什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.34,0:06:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说可以吃掉这里的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.27,0:07:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.16,0:07:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想起来了  这幢房子里住着奇怪的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.48,0:07:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  小学生的时候  你不记得了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.39,0:07:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然待的时间很短
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.52,0:07:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目贵志对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.73,0:07:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天好像会来我家
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.73,0:07:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然说想回老家看看  真不知怎么搞的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.81,0:07:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不想回家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.35,0:07:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.40,0:07:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不想见他嘛  是个阴沉的孩子  真是讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.92,0:07:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超莫名其妙的东西在我家围墙上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.47,0:07:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谁…难道就是那个孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.29,0:07:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是长得很不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.73,0:07:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错…吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.97,0:08:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君  好久不见  真是长大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.27,0:08:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.54,0:08:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听馆花先生说钥匙在您这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.34,0:08:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说了  那…要进来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.38,0:08:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不用了  我马上就要走了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.40,0:08:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.63,0:08:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  不是挺好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.80,0:08:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得来一次  喝个茶再走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.42,0:08:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.07,0:08:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.54,0:08:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了  妈妈快泡茶  好渴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.69,0:08:42.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  贵志君快进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.69,0:08:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.64,0:08:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下糟了…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.23,0:08:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然在  还在朝这边看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.51,0:08:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要不对望就应该没事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.56,0:09:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想在这惹麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.57,0:09:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是在这里…  有了有了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.52,0:09:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.72,0:09:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢您
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.44,0:09:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…几乎没怎么打扫呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.13,0:09:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.24,0:09:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看那边也已经很旧了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.09,0:09:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算找到买主恐怕也要拆毁重建
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.42,0:09:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就没怎么看管
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.46,0:09:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近带买主前去看房时才看了下情况
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.91,0:09:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  只是想再看一眼而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.36,0:09:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.41,0:09:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.90,0:09:57.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…对不起  能借一下洗手间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.64,0:10:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  以前在这里经常被那个吓到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.16,0:10:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是是错觉吗  感觉那家伙比以前更大了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.36,0:10:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是吓了一跳  那个孩子好像变了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.32,0:10:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时要是好好相处就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.97,0:10:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢  你当时明明那么讨厌他
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.56,0:10:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为爸妈对他那么好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.04,0:10:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他却老是做出些奇怪的事来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.17,0:10:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然摇摇晃晃跑去哪里之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.88,0:10:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们家才被人说闲话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.67,0:10:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明骗人的坏孩子是那孩子才对
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.91,0:10:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了  三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.12,0:10:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也是经历了很多伤心事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.66,0:10:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.34,0:10:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为可怜所以娇惯他这点最讨厌了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.19,0:10:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.10,0:10:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过现在应该不再是骗子了对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.99,0:10:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.21,0:11:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴…嘴巴…给我画张嘴巴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.98,0:11:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.04,0:11:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我画…嘴巴…给我画！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.67,0:12:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得赶紧离开这间屋子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.99,0:12:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我若继续待下去的话  那家伙又要…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.35,0:12:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君  出什么事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.57,0:12:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  不  没什么事情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.71,0:12:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妖怪很棘手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.22,0:12:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被它纠缠住还会吞噬我心智
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.55,0:12:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得赶紧…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.23,0:12:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.32,0:12:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过话说回来  你真长大了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.86,0:12:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很担心你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.21,0:12:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是叫藤原来着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.83,0:12:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是八竿子打不着的远亲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.36,0:12:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然出现就把带你走了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.12,0:12:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还担心膝下无儿女的夫妇的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.50,0:13:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许不太懂得照顾孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.23,0:13:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,画出来…画出来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.49,0:13:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君  仔细看看你瘦了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.54,0:13:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有好好在家吃饭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.96,0:13:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,画张嘴出来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.56,0:13:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,替我画出来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.27,0:13:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就帮你吃掉他们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.52,0:13:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那帮说坏话的家伙们都吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.48,0:13:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.82,0:13:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.09,0:13:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能够看见我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.09,0:13:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你给我画张嘴出来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.59,0:13:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若你想要忘掉的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.03,0:13:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛苦的回忆也好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.12,0:13:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愉悦的回忆也好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.85,0:13:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我全都替你吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.07,0:13:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我画张嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.04,0:14:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…什么…又想要说出什么奇怪的话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.13,0:14:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有谁来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.06,0:14:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  墙垣上的一只超级怪异的生物闯进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.76,0:14:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  野猫吗？ 是猫吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.60,0:14:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.16,0:14:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吗？ 脸被抓伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.39,0:14:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子她妈快拿医药箱来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.60,0:14:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.31,0:14:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.55,0:14:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.35,0:14:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差不多要走了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.23,0:14:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.01,0:14:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然间是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.43,0:14:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢您替我保管钥匙了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.83,0:14:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也顺便将这只猫带出去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.67,0:14:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少先喝口茶嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.13,0:15:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了  弄太晚回去会让他们担心的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.35,0:15:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感激不尽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.49,0:15:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.24,0:15:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤口没有关系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.33,0:15:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.49,0:15:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢  得救了  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.72,0:15:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  总是一不小心就被盯上了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.52,0:15:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师你知道那个妖怪吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.56,0:15:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候它还没有那么大
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.58,0:15:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计那是叫作虫食的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.23,0:15:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫食？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.59,0:15:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有嘴巴的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.67,0:15:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸收进入其寄居着的家里的虫子的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.31,0:15:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后不断长大的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.65,0:15:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是吃虫子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.73,0:15:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么放任不管也没有问题咯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.36,0:15:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是  至少两三年内应该是没有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.64,0:15:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是两三年？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.66,0:16:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也感觉到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.81,0:16:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都长成那么大了仅吃虫子肯定不够
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.54,0:16:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种妖怪是生长于人类的阴暗面下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.95,0:16:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进而吞噬其内心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.54,0:16:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  赶紧走人吧  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.33,0:16:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  给我等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.45,0:16:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那告别的方式到底算什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.82,0:16:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是一点都没有改变吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.35,0:16:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和过去一模一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.14,0:16:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸我妈明明那么善待你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.74,0:16:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么不满呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.29,0:16:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是做些莫名其妙的事情来吸引我父母注意
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.67,0:16:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们尽为了你的事情而担忧和烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.87,0:16:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是我的爸爸和妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.59,0:17:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我画…给我画张嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.13,0:17:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！ 想要我给你画的话就跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.46,0:17:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  我不会抢走你家人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.26,0:17:20.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  再见
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.66,0:17:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟上来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.04,0:17:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙为啥就不能少过问些是非呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.91,0:17:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一饭之恩连狗都不曾忘过呀  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.11,0:17:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你都不是旺财啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.85,0:18:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  到底想要本大爷跑马拉松跑多久啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.10,0:18:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明不过是个无名小卒  还得寸进尺
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.86,0:18:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敢对我的猎物出手  真让人不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.95,0:18:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我赶紧滚远点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.79,0:18:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢了  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.68,0:18:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.73,0:18:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.12,0:18:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是让我住进了他们家的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.02,0:18:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让我住进他们重要的家里的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.61,0:18:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要回去了  重要的家
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.24,0:18:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真像是找宝物一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.11,0:18:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.64,0:19:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一二一二一二一二…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.06,0:19:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被黑云追着跑迷路了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.86,0:19:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋！ 笨蛋！ 笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.24,0:19:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这张地图上的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.32,0:19:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去那里的话就沿着这直走
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.08,0:19:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在前面吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.48,0:19:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若耽搁太久的话就赶不上塔子的晚餐了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.48,0:19:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  那倒也是  赶紧的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.39,0:19:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该还有一大截呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.44,0:19:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会抢走你的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.59,0:19:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前不是会有那样的表情说出那些的话的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.92,0:19:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前吗…那也因为还是孩子嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.58,0:19:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是贵志君…我也是个孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.16,0:19:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.05,0:19:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.06,0:20:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  为什么那个孩子会来我们家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.71,0:20:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子  睡觉前爸爸给你讲好多好多的故事好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.82,0:20:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你呢  明天就要和贵志君一起去学校哟
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.42,0:20:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走得离我更远点
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.17,0:20:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你的家在哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.04,0:20:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真正的家呀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.12,0:20:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是真正的家？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.32,0:20:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就是你父母所住的家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.83,0:20:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得吗？ 你的爸爸和妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.35,0:20:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不记得我妈妈了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.42,0:20:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么爸爸呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.88,0:20:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸也…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.01,0:20:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是非常地非常的温柔！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.05,0:21:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.21,0:21:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明说是不记得但怎么又说得出口
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.20,0:21:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且那种口气算什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.34,0:21:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的爸爸才是最温柔的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.51,0:21:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说回老家…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.68,0:21:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那非常地非常温柔的爸爸的家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.59,0:21:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子　稍微帮个忙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.94,0:21:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.08,0:21:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想起来…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.46,0:21:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候曾有一次
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.41,0:21:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己独自一人想要回到那个家里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.16,0:21:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何我会忘掉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.62,0:21:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么那个时候你有…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.42,0:22:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.34,0:22:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？ 夏目！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.55,0:22:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定得…一定得回家！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.00,0:22:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目！ 夏目！ 夏目！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.96,0:22:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能听见老师的呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.26,0:22:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.75,0:22:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我的内心却仍在找寻着什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.88,0:22:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷失于遥远的记忆之中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.47,0:22:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定得回家！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.40,0:24:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定得回家
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.52,0:24:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的家里
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.69,0:24:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实有无数次地呼唤着
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.37,0:24:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里是我的家
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.23,0:24:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论怎样的呼喊着
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.46,0:24:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也仍旧遥不可及
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.82,0:24:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得赶紧回去  赶紧…赶紧…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.02,0:24:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  回家吧！
