[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.20,0:02:56.20,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1}年幼时光
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.96,0:24:15.96,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1\pos(258,296)}隐藏于屋中之物
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}なくした温もりを一つ一つ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色取り取りの君のカケラは　笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出の作り方も　まるでうまくならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れに　タダ身を任せて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこに行けばいい　この闇の先でまだ
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな　君のカケラ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}なくした温もりを一つ一つ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色取り取りの君のカケラは　笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出の作り方も　まるでうまくならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れに　タダ身を任せて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこに行けばいい　この闇の先でまだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな　君のカケラ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.95,0:01:48.47,Banner,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\b0}期中考试  最后一天  英语语法
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.50,0:02:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  西村
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.55,0:02:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别消沉了  考试结束后就都随我们的便了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.30,0:02:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪里玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.54,0:02:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  去钓鱼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.86,0:02:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错呢  夏目你呢  想去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.23,0:02:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想想
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.76,0:02:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边这边  要商量去哪玩的话也算上我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.41,0:02:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.79,0:02:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你们一样好东西啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.62,0:02:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.39,0:02:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲的熟人给我的  我们一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.17,0:02:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美术馆吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.00,0:02:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么反应啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.87,0:02:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个地方挺远的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.68,0:02:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系啦  反正考试都结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.50,0:02:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天又到来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.81,0:03:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.80,0:03:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.46,0:03:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来  贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.17,0:03:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吗  是同学会呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.25,0:03:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小学的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.24,0:03:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子阿姨的？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.31,0:03:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是令人怀念呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.33,0:03:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我都已经变成大婶了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.36,0:03:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家也已经是大叔大婶了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.12,0:03:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是怀念小时候呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.38,0:03:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实那个时候我有一件挺在意的事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.54,0:03:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能听我说吗  贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.86,0:03:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.65,0:03:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和一些关系亲密的朋友们交换过礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.25,0:04:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约好将各自手工制作的礼物放在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.59,0:04:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都一个劲的闹腾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.40,0:04:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绕成一圈唱着歌儿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.67,0:04:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传到我手里的是栗山的手工饼干
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.66,0:04:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,栗山拿到的正好是我做的干花书签
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.88,0:04:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但感觉她似乎很失望
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.25,0:04:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像在说自己才不要这种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.97,0:04:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子真狡猾  把饼干还给她
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.87,0:04:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时马上觉得脸红了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.72,0:04:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时我能跟她说声对不起该多好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.20,0:04:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然这种事连她也不会记得了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.99,0:04:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.06,0:04:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,栗山在那之后马上搬了家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.62,0:04:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直好想再见到她
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.14,0:04:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并非是想谈论那时的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.97,0:04:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只觉得若能看到她充满活力的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.89,0:05:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这令人介怀的事情就会马上消失掉一般
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.99,0:05:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍稍有些羡慕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.29,0:05:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并没有值得怀念的幼时回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.66,0:05:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.47,0:05:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去美术馆能干什么  真是搞不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.93,0:05:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有叫老师你去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.43,0:05:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.23,0:05:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田似乎说过那附近有一家美味的拉面店呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.07,0:05:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？拉面？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.17,0:05:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉面…拉面…拉面…拉面…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.31,0:05:38.08,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再擅自地钻进别人的行李包里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.52,0:05:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盯…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.71,0:05:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.23,0:05:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说过不让你去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.50,0:05:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去我要去我要去…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.09,0:05:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.77,0:05:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不带你去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.73,0:05:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉面…我要去…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.85,0:05:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我老实地看家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.29,0:05:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不要看家！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.91,0:05:57.86,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去…拉面…我要去！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.41,0:05:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今过着这般有些吵嚷日子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.89,0:06:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是安静呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.54,0:06:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是夏天到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.65,0:06:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…去那边抓吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.82,0:06:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样没用的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.39,0:06:17.15,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.15,0:06:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是夏天来了  也并非有什么大意义
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.35,0:06:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要找到那东西得花多大力气你们知道不
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.82,0:06:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到只大的了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.38,0:06:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.11,0:06:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  看不见我的那些人也真是白痴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.62,0:06:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和季节一样  人们也无非是擦身而过
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.74,0:06:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时似乎也是夏天
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.00,0:06:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.38,0:06:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看见我的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.36,0:07:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绿色真的很漂亮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.44,0:07:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.10,0:07:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.70,0:07:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  会被骂的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.90,0:07:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  谁也没看见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.45,0:07:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那枝干要拿去做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.17,0:07:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想折下来而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.63,0:07:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是差劲…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.91,0:07:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是何等的傲慢何等的无礼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.38,0:07:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然看不见高贵的我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.95,0:07:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这群迟钝的下等生物
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.03,0:07:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这群白痴  鼻毛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.18,0:07:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不愉快的一天
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.01,0:07:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么能令我爽快的事情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.88,0:07:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  骗子要来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.39,0:07:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢  有一个骗子在
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.20,0:07:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接近那家伙的话  骗子就会传染呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.11,0:07:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会传染呢  一边去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.20,0:07:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是丑陋  居然在这般年纪就欺负同类
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.08,0:07:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫你一边去啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.61,0:08:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  我什么都没做
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.28,0:08:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头是从天上掉下来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.15,0:08:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是老说这种谎话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.44,0:08:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.24,0:08:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一群烦人的小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.44,0:08:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.06,0:08:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  说话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.16,0:08:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么  毛毛虫…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.28,0:08:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是愉快  愉快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.22,0:08:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才…似乎朝我看了一眼…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.44,0:08:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  人类怎么会看到我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.65,0:08:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人类能够看到妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.76,0:08:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人能够注意我…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.45,0:08:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.54,0:09:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.33,0:09:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是何等无礼的小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.48,0:09:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.50,0:09:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自那之后我每天都这样地追着那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.85,0:09:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做埋伏
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.31,0:09:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓唬他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.75,0:09:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.85,0:09:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子便逃跑着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.92,0:09:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然尽是这些事情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.85,0:09:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但总觉得每天都十分开心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.86,0:09:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  今天那孩子在哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.60,0:09:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  那个人  是转学来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.65,0:09:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是一个讨人厌的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.22,0:09:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老是说些奇怪的谎话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.78,0:09:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谎话？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.82,0:09:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么能看见妖怪来吸引别人的注意
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.63,0:09:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说他没有了父母  被亲戚们相互推托才老是转学
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.43,0:10:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  所以才一直都是一个人待着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.52,0:10:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.32,0:10:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是因为能看见妖怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.75,0:10:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.20,0:10:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很危险哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.53,0:10:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天做了爸爸哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.31,0:10:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀好棒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.40,0:10:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有…还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.94,0:10:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓了一跳  吓了一跳了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.84,0:10:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.44,0:10:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次对我开口说话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.18,0:10:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要缠着我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.03,0:10:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很闲吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.16,0:10:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我…闲？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.41,0:10:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么胡话…只是碰巧走的是同一个方向…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.50,0:10:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我这样的要做的是可是很多的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.90,0:10:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有功夫缠着你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.00,0:10:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.38,0:10:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.98,0:11:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该说什么才好…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.56,0:11:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无…无礼的家伙  鼻毛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.76,0:11:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子有些饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.88,0:11:45.45,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就饿了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.55,0:11:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.22,0:11:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有带吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.11,0:11:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到哪了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.43,0:11:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看快看  真漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.58,0:11:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦…这附近是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.90,0:11:55.51,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.17,0:11:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经在这里住过
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.34,0:12:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别拉面拉面的  烦死了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.13,0:12:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.37,0:12:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发什么呆呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.79,0:12:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  连夏目也饿了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.93,0:12:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.76,0:12:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直生活在亲戚间相互推脱之中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.06,0:12:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都记不清楚去过哪些地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.73,0:12:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.44,0:12:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.29,0:12:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头疼的可是我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.27,0:12:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之下周得把这孩子给接走
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.94,0:12:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不都已经这么说好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.65,0:12:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.17,0:12:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么…已经回来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.83,0:12:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么…那个…果然
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.31,0:12:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然下周起你就要去我哥哥那住了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.39,0:12:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让今年我家那孩子要准备考试
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.22,0:12:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…啊  对了对了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.52,0:13:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件大衣送你了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.88,0:13:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许有些大
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.05,0:13:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吧…怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.44,0:13:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就别怪我了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.90,0:13:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这也有很多不便
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.28,0:13:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有灰尘的味道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.63,0:13:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得能说上句话了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.65,0:13:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本没打算说那些的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.81,0:13:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真让人不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.70,0:13:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何我要像人类那般心存顾虑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.47,0:13:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天继续像往常一样吓唬他玩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.61,0:13:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  吓唬他的话或许又会跟我说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.04,0:14:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  你这件外套是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.67,0:14:10.68,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.48,0:14:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是叔叔送我的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.85,0:14:15.91,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗…我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.80,0:14:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  趁现在…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.20,0:14:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.01,0:14:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.45,0:14:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都湿嗒嗒的了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.45,0:14:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要我怎么办啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.86,0:14:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了  闯祸了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.68,0:14:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对…对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.84,0:14:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只不过是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.07,0:14:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离我远点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.62,0:14:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离我远点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.14,0:14:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底都做什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.94,0:14:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么总是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.61,0:14:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最讨厌你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.29,0:15:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天之后那孩子就再也没有走过那条路
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.49,0:15:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是特意绕远路去上学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.10,0:15:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说的估计已经再也无法告诉他了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.59,0:15:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许不会再看到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.57,0:15:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.95,0:15:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他今天也是孤单一人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.33,0:15:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛  原来是猫咪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.31,0:16:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.51,0:16:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…有种很香的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.29,0:16:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然还能有这么温柔的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.94,0:16:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好温暖  就想这样一直在他身边…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.13,0:16:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.42,0:16:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想变成一个人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.60,0:16:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想一个人活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.44,0:16:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不过是个妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.46,0:16:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不懂人类的内心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.47,0:17:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是孤单一人是很悲哀的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.43,0:17:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只有这点我是明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.61,0:17:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只有这点我是知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.52,0:17:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数日后少年被接到很远的地方去了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.05,0:17:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么赶紧走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.02,0:17:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女人做什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.59,0:17:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴唇和指甲都那么血红
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.85,0:17:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有那男人的眼睛也在转个不停
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.73,0:17:28.22,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么今天起就要喊妈妈了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.47,0:17:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就带这家伙走了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.39,0:17:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家也有个和你一般大的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.57,0:17:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  很快就会习惯的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.03,0:17:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧  孩子他妈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.13,0:17:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.94,0:17:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家可是相当有趣的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.46,0:17:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.65,0:17:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后…就再也没有见到过那个孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.80,0:17:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人又怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.58,0:18:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人才更好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.51,0:18:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何人类总是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.12,0:18:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要相互偎依却又争执不休
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.21,0:18:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  多漂亮的花啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.60,0:18:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.91,0:18:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.74,0:18:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道啊  但觉得手指被什么给…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.01,0:18:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌  好恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.33,0:18:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少跟我闹变扭了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.86,0:18:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是少来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.14,0:18:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要我陪你老妈到什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.13,0:18:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  少说这个了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.90,0:18:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛  我已经受够了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.31,0:18:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫受够了…你…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.22,0:18:43.30,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是何等丑陋的扭曲的嘴脸
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.30,0:18:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让每次你都说有工作就往外逃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.44,0:18:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是讨厌啊  不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.75,0:18:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这无耻的人类混蛋们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.77,0:18:52.49,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可是你的老妈吧  你来照看她不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.68,0:18:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家全部都消失就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.66,0:19:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真是可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.01,0:19:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真是可恨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.94,0:19:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自私自利的丑陋的家伙们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.38,0:19:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家全部都消失就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.99,0:19:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说那颗树下很不吉利呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.00,0:19:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,具体不太清楚  但说是很恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.74,0:19:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.91,0:19:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.44,0:19:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真吵
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.60,0:19:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫啊  讨厌  一边去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.09,0:19:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没啥眷念  没啥好想的了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.72,0:19:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的时间已经停下了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.83,0:20:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个孩子到底怎样了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.90,0:20:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那温馨的笑脸和悲伤的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.77,0:20:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子现在是否还在笑着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.29,0:20:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.85,0:20:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还留在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.95,0:20:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知已有多少春夏秋冬交叠更替
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.18,0:20:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却从未能忘却过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.91,0:20:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直刻印在记忆中
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.00,0:20:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直很在意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.85,0:20:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为用如此奇怪的方式分别
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.44,0:20:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你这么有精神真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.91,0:20:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候只能找个人发脾气
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.70,0:20:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的话  我能够理解你的温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.05,0:20:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是遇见某个善良的人了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.27,0:20:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让他露出如此的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.82,0:21:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是让人怀念的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.09,0:21:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是夏目贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.51,0:21:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能告诉我你的名字吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.99,0:21:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.33,0:21:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.95,0:21:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.52,0:21:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.75,0:21:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到面了？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.09,0:21:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  贵志呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.01,0:21:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩得开心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.50,0:21:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.44,0:21:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.30,0:21:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有了…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.92,0:21:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然间怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.70,0:21:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是要顺路去哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.10,0:21:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  有个想见的人  曾经的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.26,0:21:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道还能不能见到
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.61,0:21:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.92,0:21:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就先回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.23,0:21:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是  那么就回头见了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.23,0:22:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头见
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.51,0:22:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快啦快啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.56,0:22:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.44,0:22:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩得高兴点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.29,0:22:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.20,0:22:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜咯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.02,0:22:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多加小心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.45,0:22:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的话我懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.71,0:22:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若有想见面的人在的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.35,0:22:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一定不再是孤单一人了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.32,0:24:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这间屋子里有认识祖父的妖怪们在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.43,0:24:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.44,0:24:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家回忆起爷爷的事情就都聚到一起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.56,0:24:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖父他…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.48,0:24:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然到最后都未能实现亲眼见见妖怪的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.48,0:24:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些家伙不是你想看就能看到的
