[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.20,0:03:01.20,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur2\shad2\bord1}除妖人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.92,0:24:15.96,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1\pos(243,296)}小狐狸的手表
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.50,0:01:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  为什么要跟着我呢  小猫咪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.84,0:01:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  比平时看到的景色要好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.27,0:01:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人  请不要将猫带入馆内
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.91,0:01:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是呢  请仔细看看  这只是布偶而已啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.15,0:01:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头很大对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.91,0:01:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  那么关于的场一族你了解到什么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.18,0:02:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没  但还是先做好心理准备
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.02,0:02:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是为了自己的目的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.94,0:02:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不惜差使危险的妖怪的可怕的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.61,0:02:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么一说  曾经一只有乌鸦被他们当做诱饵用呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.01,0:02:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会手下留情的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.44,0:02:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论那是谁的式神
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.70,0:02:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才丢下她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.57,0:02:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？你指的是什么事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.81,0:02:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指你的式神啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.20,0:02:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并没有什么特殊的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.03,0:02:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在反而有些后悔没有带她过来…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.32,0:02:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,符被…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.48,0:02:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出去的时候弄破了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.01,0:02:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想用这东西来阻止妖怪的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.97,0:02:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.55,0:02:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有谁进去了该怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.33,0:02:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是贴上这种连猫咪都可以轻松弄破的符的你不对
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.22,0:02:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你在一起的时候真是万事不顺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.70,0:02:51.29,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这符真是有够破
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.70,0:02:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.88,0:02:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.92,0:03:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饶不了你们…饶不了你们…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.41,0:03:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然…竟然！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.63,0:03:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.15,0:03:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有意思对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.26,0:03:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那张纸  普通人是看不见的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.95,0:03:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.86,0:03:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这张纸的话  名取家比我清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.62,0:03:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去问他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.59,0:03:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟打算干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.49,0:03:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做出这种事来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.79,0:03:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想做什么  只是吩咐它们「抓住你」而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.68,0:03:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的借口说不通呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.39,0:03:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟你也看得见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.78,0:03:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你动粗真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.78,0:03:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙还在教育中
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.35,0:03:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是都怪你逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.19,0:03:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明说了有话要问你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.35,0:03:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了什么目的要收集妖怪的血？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.19,0:04:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪的血是用于解除封印或召唤强大妖怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.17,0:04:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简而言之  就是食饵一般的作用
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.00,0:04:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这森林里沉睡着一只十分强大的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.70,0:04:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了那只妖怪而来的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.09,0:04:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用自己的血
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.43,0:04:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夺取那些无辜妖怪们的血…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.30,0:04:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样继续下去的话  我不会饶恕你的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.87,0:04:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不饶恕我？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.99,0:04:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是能看见妖怪的你能做到什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.17,0:04:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.30,0:04:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这个而不能很好地把控好距离呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.14,0:04:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼睛…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.23,0:04:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看得见哦  但这东西是必须的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.41,0:04:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为会被吃掉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.69,0:04:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从前有人为了让妖怪帮忙而许诺把右眼给它
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.24,0:04:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但终究还是没有给它
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.23,0:05:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后代代的场一族的当家的右眼都被它盯上了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.89,0:05:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然眼珠还在这里  但脸上却留着很大的伤疤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.45,0:05:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得有机会  要看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.42,0:05:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.01,0:05:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.87,0:05:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着他
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.79,0:05:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管原委是什么  但不要再牵连那些无辜的妖怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.19,0:05:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不住手的话  我会阻止你的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.30,0:05:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是为了保护人类才去得到那些强大的妖怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.59,0:05:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此被人怨恨或付出代价都是无可奈何的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.31,0:05:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一样…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.81,0:05:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人明明也是除妖人  却和名取先生完全不同
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.78,0:05:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就回来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.64,0:05:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果闹腾起来的话就马上让你变得安分
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.38,0:05:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果逃走的话就马上让你变得不能动弹
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.28,0:05:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请安分地等我回来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.55,0:06:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的事情被那个人知道了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.96,0:06:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一击毙命吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.02,0:06:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为他只不过是能看见妖怪而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.13,0:06:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要追吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.10,0:06:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你们就不用管了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.73,0:06:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好危险
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.70,0:06:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场先生的式神吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.26,0:07:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那个森林里沉睡着强大的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.78,0:07:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不得不保护那些仅存的伙伴们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.73,0:07:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食饵一般的作用…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.16,0:07:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的话或许还能阻止他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.92,0:07:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  不能去那个森林
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.48,0:07:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.64,0:07:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西方传来了一种极为不详的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.11,0:07:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西方？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.37,0:07:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人他们在的那个方向吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.65,0:07:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那气息究竟是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.08,0:07:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼睛…如果和那家伙对上眼的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.02,0:07:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会被吃掉…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.72,0:07:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一定会被吃掉的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.24,0:07:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你要去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.57,0:07:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去救他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.23,0:07:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能将夏目大人卷进来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.72,0:07:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有关系  夏目会自己判断的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.45,0:07:58.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还有我的主人跟馒头猫咪跟着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.53,0:07:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.44,0:08:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你这副身体去了又能做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.39,0:08:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.07,0:08:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.69,0:08:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不呼唤我…名取
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.80,0:08:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会飞去你那里的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.70,0:08:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场先生的话刚刚退了旅馆了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.66,0:08:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.52,0:08:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  一切都变得乱七八糟了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.09,0:08:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直以来都是一个可疑的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.39,0:08:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天却派不上用场  派不上用场的名取
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.37,0:08:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个除妖人！派不上用场的周一！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.83,0:08:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么  你这个白猪馒头
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.38,0:08:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挠！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.08,0:08:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人  这只果然是猫吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.91,0:08:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.47,0:08:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.06,0:08:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让的场先生肆意妄为
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.70,0:09:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须找到那个强大的妖怪并阻止他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.54,0:09:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里…应该能感觉到的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.85,0:09:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.53,0:09:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.26,0:09:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这边
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.86,0:09:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概…从这一带
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.10,0:09:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.00,0:09:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洞窟？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.51,0:09:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了  在这深处
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.90,0:09:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处乱窜  真是一个烦人的小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.35,0:09:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是来捣乱的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.15,0:10:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场的式神吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.94,0:10:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很可怜  但还是把你做成祭品吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.43,0:10:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能再慢吞吞地等下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.87,0:10:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…这个声音…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.02,0:10:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那个家伙来之前
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.26,0:10:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那个家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.05,0:10:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.83,0:10:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.30,0:10:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请退下  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.81,0:10:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.82,0:10:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的光居然对那家伙无效
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.30,0:10:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个声音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.57,0:10:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.72,0:10:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只纸面的妖怪的碎片中涌来的恶意
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.91,0:10:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有那时梦中的声音…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.23,0:10:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难道是人类？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.35,0:10:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.55,0:10:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  你是侍奉的场一族的咒术师
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.89,0:10:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.21,0:10:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  她的式神被的场当做成了诱饵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.37,0:11:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说那之后就隐退了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.90,0:11:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式神…被当成诱饵？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.31,0:11:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕…的场一族…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.11,0:11:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要吃掉那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.23,0:11:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.88,0:11:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要让这只能吃掉的场的妖怪苏醒过来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.12,0:11:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.37,0:11:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来还没有苏醒过来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.66,0:11:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.46,0:11:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以这家伙为中心已经画下了唤醒阵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.82,0:11:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些壶里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.85,0:11:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  肯定是收集来的血液
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.65,0:12:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找寻能令贪婪的的场感兴趣的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.40,0:12:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四处散播谣言
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.98,0:12:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是为了把他给引到这里后吃掉他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.30,0:12:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了被吃掉的式神复仇吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.98,0:12:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.05,0:12:18.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然我们在从事着这份工作  那些妖怪也就…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.27,0:12:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如同道具一般的存在？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.93,0:12:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可从来没有这么想过
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.97,0:12:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是什么道具
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.36,0:12:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是那样…你做这种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.65,0:12:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为除妖人的你不理解我也无妨
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.46,0:12:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最需要的是血
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.50,0:12:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血还不足够  我来找你们讨了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.83,0:12:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为就那些么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.12,0:12:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切  真是没完没了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.46,0:12:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真难吃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.16,0:12:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些纸人一口气给你全了结了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.52,0:13:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.81,0:13:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.27,0:13:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎哟  失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.97,0:13:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看妖怪们争执不休的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.34,0:13:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不知道哪些是哪些了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.11,0:13:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是无心对那孩子动手的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.99,0:13:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.43,0:13:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了找到这里不知道费了多大劲呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.23,0:13:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次发生事件便立马赶去现场调查妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.61,0:13:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还让式神多次在这森林搜索都未能找到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.79,0:13:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而就只是稍微靠你一下  就立马找到这里来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.65,0:13:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.34,0:13:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.80,0:14:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不自量力的家伙  做好心理准备吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.86,0:14:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.14,0:14:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.72,0:14:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太激动了  伤势会加深的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.43,0:14:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.65,0:14:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有关系  反而是老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.20,0:14:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.19,0:14:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.28,0:14:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捡了条命啊  叫的场的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.40,0:14:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛  真是无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.36,0:14:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  你流血了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.53,0:14:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是一滴两滴血而已  少大惊小怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.83,0:15:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种程度舔舔就好…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.67,0:15:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你的伤口呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.78,0:15:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是擦伤而已  血也止住了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.50,0:15:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.70,0:15:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师果然是妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.60,0:15:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  就算是我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.84,0:15:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果全身流的都是那种充满活力的东西的话  可是相当恐怖的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.99,0:15:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咒语
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.05,0:15:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看  那壶里的血也…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.98,0:15:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.45,0:16:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪的血妖力太强大了  让他苏醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.85,0:16:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.46,0:16:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说之前那箭一开始就是瞄准老师
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.77,0:16:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特意为了试探这只妖怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.47,0:16:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快离开  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.74,0:16:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不太妙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.25,0:16:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剧毒在扩散
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.45,0:16:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说  为了你收集血液解开咒印的正是我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.35,0:16:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了我吃掉那个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.97,0:16:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  就是在那  就是那个男人…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.40,0:16:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.94,0:16:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.15,0:16:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.34,0:16:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是老样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.36,0:17:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.34,0:17:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让那家伙到地面上去可就麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.24,0:17:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是难看
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.84,0:17:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做着除妖人的工作却还对妖怪产生感情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.22,0:17:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到还盲目做些不切实际的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.94,0:17:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终落得这幅下场么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.52,0:17:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.47,0:17:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妖怪用不了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.54,0:17:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我撤退了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.11,0:17:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.73,0:17:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别激动  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.78,0:17:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里很危险先出去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.82,0:17:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.00,0:17:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.49,0:17:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试试封印他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.87,0:17:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目带着大家先出去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.20,0:17:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么行  我也要帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.63,0:17:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.44,0:17:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起一个人来  两个人更方便
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.33,0:17:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.16,0:17:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师就陪着那个女人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.22,0:18:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.92,0:18:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  是能用的妖怪吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.82,0:18:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  不能回话就无法缔结契约
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.57,0:18:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力量太强大了  无法用术式进行控制
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.19,0:18:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,且还加上那毒气
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.16,0:18:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.33,0:18:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看他们还没有出来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.46,0:18:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计名取他回去封印去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.86,0:18:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.07,0:18:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微跟他开了个玩笑就立马飞过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.83,0:18:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个逞强的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.24,0:18:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.47,0:18:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当初首领不辞劳苦四处找寻
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.53,0:18:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到是那样的妖怪真是徒劳一场
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.24,0:18:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并非如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.23,0:18:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妖怪虽派不上用场
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.40,0:18:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男孩和猫有点意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.85,0:18:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  跟我走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.09,0:18:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.55,0:19:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来  还差一点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.45,0:19:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.32,0:19:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉眠地底  以情现形
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.96,0:19:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谓之争斗不可免
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.47,0:19:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非人之物  回归尘土吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.77,0:19:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.62,0:19:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.52,0:19:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险的妖怪  就少费功夫直接让它消失了就好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.92,0:19:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这妖怪也好那女人也罢都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.89,0:19:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来很有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.88,0:19:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能再会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.20,0:19:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后  请多多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.94,0:20:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除妖人  的场一族
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.61,0:20:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.23,0:20:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场…不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.38,0:20:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已经这样了  已经没有办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.00,0:20:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘记一切吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.16,0:20:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们能够忘掉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.44,0:20:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能忘掉…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.13,0:20:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  他是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.46,0:20:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  夏目贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.33,0:20:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个夏目玲子的孙子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.46,0:20:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  就是他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.40,0:21:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到越来越有意思的家伙了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.52,0:21:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这件事就交给我们名取家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.84,0:21:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.09,0:21:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.25,0:21:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了  柊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.19,0:21:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.33,0:21:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生气了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.63,0:21:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么能让我生气的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.40,0:21:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是主人的侍从
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.49,0:21:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些人是否看不见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.50,0:21:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为保护伙伴四处奔走的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.57,0:21:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去的如同心碎一般
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.23,0:21:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟妖怪们有着羁绊的人的痛楚
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.66,0:21:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是为了达到目的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.60,0:21:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫不顾忌的伤害他人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.50,0:21:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.41,0:22:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有必要为那些家伙伤神
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.43,0:22:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种家伙也还是存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.97,0:22:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.64,0:22:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我还有老师
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.25,0:22:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有名取和柊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.31,0:22:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…和那些人不同
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.29,0:24:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.43,0:24:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了  夏目又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.46,0:24:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到比过去成长了不少的我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.63,0:24:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目会不会替我开心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.20,0:24:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岩神尽说些难以理解的话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.08,0:24:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但哪怕是一点点我也想能为夏目做些什么
