[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,1
Style: OP_jp,方正楷体_GBK,33,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,45,1
Style: OP_ch,方正楷体_GBK,36,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,5,1
Style: ED_jp,方正楷体_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,45,1
Style: ED_ch,方正楷体_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,5,1
Style: bt,方正楷体_GBK,55,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H32A8D0C8,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,33,&H00E8EEF4,&HF0000000,&H1E23384E,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text



Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.19,0:01:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来下 贵志 你看看这些
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.96,0:01:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.94,0:01:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买了好多哦 零食
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.73,0:01:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 真的好多啊 塔子婶婶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.53,0:01:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都带去作业合宿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.86,0:01:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.92,0:01:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.44,0:01:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后包薯片塞不进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.69,0:02:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.90,0:02:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这里吃掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.59,0:02:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你体谅人的方式还真是笨拙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.91,0:02:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生你也来帮忙吃点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.07,0:02:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 净给人添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.12,0:02:21.00,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永生的思念
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.16,0:02:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好晚啊 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.69,0:02:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.44,0:02:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜哇 你那包是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.46,0:02:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面都装了些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.22,0:02:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬请期待吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.37,0:02:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 敬请期待?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.25,0:02:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 只是些...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.72,0:02:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个景色优美的地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.99,0:03:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个池塘看上去好深
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.99,0:03:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面都是水藻 掉下去会溺死人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.71,0:03:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.75,0:03:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜哇!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.31,0:03:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.28,0:03:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在水里游!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.86,0:03:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人? 哪里啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.45,0:03:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要掉下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.92,0:03:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要掉下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.55,0:03:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 这不是什么都没有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.23,0:03:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 什么什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.13,0:03:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是我看错了吧 走吧走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.89,0:03:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了啊 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.86,0:03:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.01,0:03:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打搅了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.54,0:03:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打搅了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.52,0:03:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没反应呢 会不会不在家啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.13,0:03:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们比预定的时间早到了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.91,0:03:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 门没锁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.43,0:03:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问有人在吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.15,0:04:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就这样随便进来合适吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.68,0:04:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.50,0:04:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,池塘...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.90,0:04:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来这个院子里也有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.22,0:04:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然 这片土地可是流传着人鱼的传说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.01,0:04:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处都可以看到池塘和沼泽之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.55,0:04:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人鱼...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.71,0:04:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 哇!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.13,0:04:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么先生会在包里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.70,0:04:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪不得我想怎么这么重 你这 你这...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.75,0:04:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 原来是夏目家的猫
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.47,0:04:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然偷偷带来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.03,0:04:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 我以为还要过会才来的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.55,0:04:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微出去办了点事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.47,0:04:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在抱歉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.29,0:04:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 我们才是 未经允许就进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.10,0:04:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快快 进房吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.80,0:04:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.61,0:04:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.09,0:04:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫坂中千津 你们好好休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.06,0:05:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 这题该怎么弄啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.19,0:05:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个 我也不会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.41,0:05:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.80,0:05:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那第3题不会就先空着了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.43,0:05:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 这个好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.30,0:05:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得 那边应该先代入α...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.34,0:05:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说啦 饭都要吃不下了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.09,0:05:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.31,0:05:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.05,0:05:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子合宿还真有趣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.00,0:05:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 你看是鲫鱼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.70,0:05:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别一条鲫鱼就大惊小怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.18,0:05:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇! 鱼竟然眨眼睛了!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.95,0:05:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快闪开 夏目!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.69,0:06:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说有眼睑的鱼都是妖怪的化身 你会被吃掉的!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.02,0:06:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 看到我心生畏惧就逃跑了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.52,0:06:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来即使在妖怪看来 也是张可怕的脸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.31,0:06:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是就是 即使在妖怪来看 也是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.80,0:06:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说清楚谁长着可怕的脸啊!?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.47,0:06:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是白天在大池子里看到的妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.31,0:06:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 或许是因为发觉是你夏目才跟来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.77,0:06:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是那样的话 那这妖怪就是冲友人帐而来的了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.61,0:06:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.15,0:06:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.14,0:06:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把友人帐交出来!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.08,0:06:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.94,0:07:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 把友人帐...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.06,0:07:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.75,0:07:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊这个 真硬啊 真硬
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.71,0:07:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 狸猫 被狸猫给...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.86,0:07:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是狸猫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.14,0:07:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 是埋伏陷阱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.76,0:07:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说不能相信人类啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.23,0:07:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦不 应该说正因为这样才让人想要欺负吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.29,0:07:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.07,0:07:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不是人类可以拥有的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.65,0:07:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 都这么晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.23,0:07:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 有点睡不着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.66,0:07:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要给你做点暖身的东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.08,0:07:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.95,0:08:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.33,0:08:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉呢 因为你感觉很像我在找的一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.29,0:08:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找的人?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.82,0:08:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 想要偿还也还不清的一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.55,0:08:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偿还吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.27,0:08:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道人鱼的传说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.88,0:08:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说吃下人鱼的血肉的人类将会得到永生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.53,0:08:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 听过的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.25,0:08:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊 以前在前面那池塘里看见过一次人鱼的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.22,0:08:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是小时候的关系 也许只是一场梦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.75,0:08:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经把从人鱼那里拿到的血让那个人喝下了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.71,0:08:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是在找那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.95,0:09:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承蒙您的照顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.44,0:09:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.29,0:09:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是哦 多谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.85,0:09:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真开心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.13,0:09:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 很棒的一次合宿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.03,0:09:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你一直都在吃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.78,0:09:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没那回事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.31,0:09:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 回去的时候就散步到车站 然后再坐火车回去怎么样?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.90,0:09:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真是好主意呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.47,0:09:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来那里的虾真好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.97,0:09:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还想着吃啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.16,0:09:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 小心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.59,0:09:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么办吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.12,0:09:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我忘了点东西 你们先走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.54,0:09:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.91,0:09:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把友人帐留下!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.91,0:09:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 抱歉 因为你一下子蹿出来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.76,0:10:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.75,0:10:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么名字?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.45,0:10:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区人类不配知道我的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.17,0:10:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底像我这样稀少美丽的人鱼...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.98,0:10:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把人家的话听完啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.41,0:10:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这人类要无礼到什么程度啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.51,0:10:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千津婆婆遇到的人鱼 是你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.88,0:10:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢? 我可没有必要告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.48,0:10:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.29,0:10:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思了 友人帐是不会给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.17,0:10:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再追过来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.85,0:10:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人鱼是极度厌恶人类的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.96,0:10:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为人类想要他们的肉而惨遭捕杀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.03,0:10:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸存下来的已经不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.25,0:10:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜呢 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.55,0:11:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来有机会吃下人鱼肉不老不死的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.03,0:11:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵 如果我那么做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.16,0:11:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生就一辈子都得不到友人帐了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.96,0:11:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.86,0:11:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.01,0:11:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千津婆婆
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.97,0:11:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.04,0:11:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.59,0:11:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不好意思呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.41,0:11:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有认识的人说 在这间车站看到过像萤一哥哥的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.08,0:11:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我以为一定是萤一哥哥了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.20,0:11:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您昨天外出也是为这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.46,0:11:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 来了这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.52,0:11:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位萤一哥哥 是个怎样的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.41,0:11:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信我上次说的话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.21,0:12:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.13,0:12:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的父母都要工作 我又没有兄弟姐妹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.58,0:12:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候经常一个人在家门前的池塘边玩耍
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.86,0:12:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为可怜这样的我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.92,0:12:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隔壁的萤一哥哥就开始陪我一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.23,0:12:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和现在的你差不多年纪 是个很温柔的人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.94,0:12:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢他了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.68,0:12:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他的身体很虚弱
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.78,0:12:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一个暴风雨的夜晚 病情突然恶化
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.59,0:12:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这时 我想起了这个池塘里住着人鱼的传说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.84,0:12:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跑去了池塘边
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.70,0:12:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 我看到了有着温柔眼神的人鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.69,0:12:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人鱼把它珍贵的血分给了我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.61,0:12:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 我把血滴入了那个人的口中
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.82,0:13:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他喝下去了吗 人鱼的血
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.71,0:13:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大人们都说我是在做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.05,0:13:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渐渐地连我自己也搞糊涂了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.30,0:13:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.12,0:13:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤一哥哥转去了远方的医院 保住了性命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.08,0:13:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这一去却再也没有回来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.10,0:13:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这场别离使我深受打击
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.13,0:13:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将人鱼血的事情忘得一干二净
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.92,0:13:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很过份吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.05,0:13:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.64,0:13:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而就在去年我丈夫去世
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.89,0:13:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也自觉将不久于人世的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.24,0:13:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我突然想起来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.85,0:13:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一切真的是梦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.47,0:13:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那不是梦的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.31,0:13:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤一哥哥他现在不就是不老不死地活着吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.41,0:13:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果因为我那轻率的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.69,0:13:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而让那个人至今受着折磨的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.31,0:14:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该如何是好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.72,0:14:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目送着深爱的人一个个离去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.50,0:14:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而自己则独自一人永远地活着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.17,0:14:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生一定经历过很多次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.27,0:14:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说 铃子外婆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.11,0:14:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 总有一天...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.55,0:14:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要去抓抓看人鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.77,0:14:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.04,0:14:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定它知道些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.05,0:14:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又要做这种无聊的事了 我绝对不会帮忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.16,0:14:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去的路上 给你买七辻屋的馒头吃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.68,0:14:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是帮你抓住它哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.26,0:14:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.67,0:14:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 人鱼 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.10,0:15:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话对你说 请你出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.32,0:15:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 太阳快落山了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.83,0:15:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.03,0:15:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你讨厌人类吗 一个人不寂寞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.15,0:15:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有过不是一个人的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.99,0:15:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我什么事 小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.29,0:15:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想干什么 放手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.21,0:15:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话要问你 你不回答我就不放手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.96,0:15:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荒唐 你以为在水中能赢得过我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.77,0:15:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想日后因为当时没有去做力所能及的事而后悔
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.49,0:15:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我 从前你有没有把自己的血给过一个小女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.15,0:15:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.02,0:15:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她正在为把这血给重要的人喝下而痛苦不已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.42,0:15:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你知道有什么办法可以解除不老不死的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.26,0:16:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个个嘴里都说着什么不老不死 血啊肉啊的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.17,0:16:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错 那孩子经常到这里来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.18,0:16:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不知道我是人鱼 一直和我玩耍
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.05,0:16:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我才对很久不见的她现出原形
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.08,0:16:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说想要血于是就破例分了她一点
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.83,0:16:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 她后悔给别人喝了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.09,0:16:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼看自己到了风烛残年而伤脑筋了么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.30,0:16:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可怜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.83,0:16:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么为了让她不再痛苦 让我去吃了她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.89,0:16:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.36,0:16:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 被它逃走了吗 可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.55,0:16:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你去哪里 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.48,0:16:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,适得其反了 明明想为她做点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.53,0:16:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不能顺利进行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.47,0:16:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是这样 千津婆婆也是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.02,0:17:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.56,0:17:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人 萤一哥哥他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.57,0:17:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依旧是当年的样子 我到底都做了些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.46,0:17:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤一哥哥 萤一哥哥 等等我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.22,0:17:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤一哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.71,0:17:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可怜 累了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.89,0:17:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这声音 是人鱼小姐?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.34,0:17:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说 人鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.89,0:17:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千津婆婆那时候还只是个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.99,0:17:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是个不懂得你的孤独与创伤的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.66,0:18:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说你是个有着温柔眼神的人鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.20,0:18:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有反应 你的名字在友人帐上吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.58,0:18:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才想要友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.28,0:18:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了打发时间
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.04,0:18:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抢夺友人帐也好 和夏目铃子比试也好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.20,0:18:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把血给那个孩子也好 都是为了打发时间而已
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.70,0:18:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子的外孙么 很好吃的样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.07,0:18:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.22,0:18:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹舟
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.50,0:18:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归还汝名 请收下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.77,0:18:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 在这种暴风雨的夜里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.76,0:18:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明都好几个月没来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.28,0:18:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子又来看我了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.18,0:19:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试着和她说话 做个朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.41,0:19:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可别吓到她 我能露出温柔的微笑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.00,0:19:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人鱼小姐 人鱼小姐 请给我你的血
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.40,0:19:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.94,0:19:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然你的目的也是这个么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.25,0:19:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.74,0:19:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到我的内心了吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.96,0:19:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我对她很失望
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.27,0:19:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我就使坏把装有葡萄汁的小瓶子给了她
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.22,0:19:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果那孩子含着眼泪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.23,0:19:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑着对我说谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.11,0:19:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一刻 我对自己也失望了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.39,0:19:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹舟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.25,0:19:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 这样也好 这样就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.65,0:19:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请替我转告她
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.81,0:19:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请替我对她说「捉弄了你 我很抱歉」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.40,0:20:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 笹舟 你自己 你自己去说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.79,0:20:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千津婆婆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.37,0:20:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 人鱼小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.51,0:20:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保重
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.61,0:20:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到了吗 千津婆婆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.18,0:20:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 和那个时候一样温柔的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.07,0:20:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 原来是他的孙子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.94,0:20:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 因为去上补习班 有时会经过这个车站
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.87,0:20:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤一先生好像是三年前去世的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.57,0:20:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说他这一生都很幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.19,0:21:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和您给我的照片上简直一模一样 他的孙子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.46,0:21:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是想听听他爷爷的故事 他来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.05,0:21:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 初次见面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.07,0:21:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹舟 千津婆婆说她还会再来的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.30,0:21:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别以为每次都能得救哦 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.72,0:21:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类无法做到的事情太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.93,0:21:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你们总是很容易就忘记了这一点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.41,0:21:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我现在是深感自己力量微薄
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.38,0:21:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 正因为这样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.04,0:21:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要留在你身边 想要留你在身边
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.80,0:22:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们一边祈祷这些愿望的实现
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.06,0:22:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边细细体会其中的弥足珍贵
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.18,0:23:51.00,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(384,554)}{\fs52}樱树林中的他
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.10,0:23:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在跳蚤市场得到了一幅画
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.39,0:23:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁啊 每天晚上把花撒得到处都是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.02,0:23:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这幅画中 住着八坂大人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.52,0:23:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了啊 你这低级妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.13,0:23:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么撒花
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.08,0:23:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为八坂大人还是人类的时候很喜欢花

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 少しだけ大人の色に染まる指先
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 指尖稍露成年的沧桑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 照れくさそうに そっと隠して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 你就害羞得将它悄悄收起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 頬杖ついた君 見つめてる視線の先に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 手托下巴的你将视线投向
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 小さな蕾が ゆらゆら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 那随风轻曳的小小花蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} ねぇ 僕なんて いまも迷いばかりで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 喂 现在的我仍迷茫依旧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} あの日贈った言葉 今さら思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 这才回想起 那日你的临别赠言
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「君色に未来染めて...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「将我的未来染成你的颜色...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ 聞いていてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 听我倾诉好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ わがままいいですか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 让我任性好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手に入れた途端に消えてしまいそう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}拥有的瞬间仿佛就会消散
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}言葉をくれませんか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不说点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あなたがいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}因为有你在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}それだけで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう世界が変わってしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我的世界就会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}モノトーンの景色が ほら 鮮やかに映る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}映入眼眸的单调景色也会光鲜亮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}いつのまにか 離れていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不知何时却已离开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手を繋いで歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}牵着手 向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}上手く愛せているかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}能够好好去爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あの空に聞いてみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}天空也许会回答
