[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.50,0:03:01.50,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}给过去的你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.09,0:24:15.98,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\pos(228,296)}玻璃的对面
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.52,0:02:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  又是不及格  该找什么借口跟老妈交待呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.47,0:02:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  由莉子仍旧是个冒失鬼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.48,0:02:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说出车祸了  惊慌失措地赶过来一看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.32,0:02:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么嘛  不过是扭伤了而已嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.77,0:02:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽惹是生非的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.41,0:02:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是颜面无存
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.65,0:02:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是为何要去参拜神社呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.58,0:02:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.27,0:02:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子一旦考试不及格就会去那里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.46,0:02:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.94,0:02:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.59,0:02:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中学起就那样了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.47,0:02:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么！ 驱邪吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.21,0:02:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  那个时候也是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.40,0:02:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是在那遇见了夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.86,0:03:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕  不管怎么看都让人发笑
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.24,0:03:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于不及格了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.11,0:03:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个家伙貌似是转校生…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.90,0:03:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.24,0:03:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然踢开身为女生的我？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.59,0:03:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.59,0:03:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  由莉子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.25,0:03:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说那转校生就住这附近来着？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.75,0:04:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？ 嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.55,0:04:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个怎样的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.00,0:04:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个什么样的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.68,0:04:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是夏目贵志  请多多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.81,0:04:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据传言所说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.27,0:04:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被亲戚们推来攘去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.50,0:04:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次是住在一间破旧公寓里的夫妇收留了他
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.85,0:04:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说他冷峻而又恬静
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.04,0:04:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教室里的女生们吵得沸沸扬扬
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.35,0:04:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷峻而又恬静
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.89,0:04:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.98,0:04:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  我听说了一些
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.32,0:04:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说他从小就尽撒谎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.23,0:04:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行为举止诡异
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.49,0:04:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤害周围亲友
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.22,0:04:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可千万别和那孩子走太近了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.44,0:04:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是有个万一…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.58,0:04:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈我就要心跳停止了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.12,0:04:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.89,0:05:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢说谎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.94,0:05:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行为确实有些诡异
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.88,0:05:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.01,0:05:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天你还真够狠啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.10,0:05:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.65,0:05:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同班的绪方由莉子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.13,0:05:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说忘记了昨天在神社被你所踢倒的那个女生了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.37,0:05:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神社？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.81,0:05:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那是你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.01,0:05:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候做了个噩梦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.94,0:05:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒来时只见眼前有一个像怪物的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.75,0:05:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…是说我长得像怪物吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.96,0:05:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵  差不多吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.51,0:05:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡迷糊了  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.58,0:05:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.41,0:05:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思了  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.31,0:05:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你稍微该剪下头发了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.35,0:06:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  差不多准备剪了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.26,0:06:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说你打算自己剪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.60,0:06:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向他们要理发钱…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.19,0:06:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失陪了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.00,0:06:19.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他吞进肚子里的话语估计是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.18,0:06:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「你认为我会向他们要理发钱吗」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.51,0:06:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是说了不该说的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.65,0:06:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有机会去道歉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.28,0:06:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看他总是一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.08,0:06:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得很难找他搭话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.73,0:06:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是就这样看着也发觉了一些端倪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.94,0:06:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君他确实有些奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.60,0:07:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然跑起来  什么都没有还摔跤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.66,0:07:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别靠近  给我消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.58,0:07:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉就像是在驱赶着什么似的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.25,0:07:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说不要靠近了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.00,0:07:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒来时只见眼前有一个像怪物的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.31,0:07:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说夏目君他看见我背后有些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.30,0:07:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想从它们手中保护我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.67,0:07:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有没有…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.27,0:07:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我要那样胡思乱想呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.21,0:07:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  下起雨来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.53,0:07:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天要去体育馆呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.87,0:07:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  由莉子  我们还有社团活动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.83,0:07:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天再见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.22,0:07:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  再见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.96,0:07:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.16,0:07:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一起撑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.39,0:08:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.20,0:08:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这之前对不起了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.24,0:08:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.24,0:08:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君  夏目君你…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.93,0:08:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你能看见什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.40,0:08:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真这样问了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.78,0:08:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许他再也不会搭理我了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.16,0:08:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是什么都没说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.53,0:08:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.79,0:08:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这雨突然就下起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.87,0:08:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说由莉子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.79,0:08:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚你是不是和那孩子共撑一把伞了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.06,0:08:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是都说过不行了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.02,0:08:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈可是很担心呐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.65,0:08:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.12,0:09:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.55,0:09:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君不计较我那些无心的话还替我撑伞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.19,0:09:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很善良吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.70,0:09:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.85,0:09:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽会羞涩但当夏目变得主动向我打招呼的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.90,0:09:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事件就发生了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.75,0:09:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.62,0:09:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  没受伤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.49,0:09:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  怎么又是你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.34,0:09:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近总会有窗户被打碎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.84,0:09:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而夏目君总是在那附近
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.45,0:09:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.20,0:09:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这已经是第几次了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.89,0:09:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何要这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.48,0:09:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我去趟办公室
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.36,0:09:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先等等
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.80,0:09:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由莉子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.09,0:09:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是这很奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.25,0:09:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  这些玻璃碎片都落在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.87,0:10:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种碎法也很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.11,0:10:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先好好调查一下  不会是夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.03,0:10:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说夏目君怎么会做这种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.79,0:10:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绪方…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.41,0:10:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  绪方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.64,0:10:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.31,0:10:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家仔细看清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.21,0:10:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道就看不清吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.58,0:10:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看看夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.55,0:10:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁来…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.09,0:10:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由莉子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.48,0:10:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,监护人被叫到学校来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.04,0:10:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君被满身酒气的女子带回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.63,0:10:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后很快夏目君又要转校了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.30,0:10:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是因为那件事情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.62,0:10:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明不是夏目君的错
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.82,0:10:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲戚工作上进展不顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.03,0:10:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有时间照看我这样的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.65,0:11:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次一定会是户好人家
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.72,0:11:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止都是善良的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.08,0:11:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过无论我到哪都会被人讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.52,0:11:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是人  还是它们…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.38,0:11:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我同夏目君的相识与别离
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.29,0:11:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  由莉子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.89,0:11:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得夏目君吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.40,0:11:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是中学的时候转校过来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.69,0:11:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短时间同过班的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.65,0:11:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  那个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.50,0:11:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君他怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.61,0:11:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近丰松说他见过夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.08,0:11:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰松就是去了中央高中的书呆子来着？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.97,0:11:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他加入了轻骑俱乐部变得很可靠了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.84,0:11:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人  真不可置信
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.87,0:11:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那俱乐部就在这之前的连休时组织了远行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.37,0:11:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就偶然…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.62,0:12:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有打招呼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.85,0:12:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说…谁让我没有同他说过话嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.17,0:12:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先告诉你一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.92,0:12:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.01,0:12:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁不知道你们关系好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.27,0:12:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢过他的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.54,0:12:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑！ 才没有那回事！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.68,0:12:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不承认
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.26,0:12:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如实招了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.80,0:12:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…真的不是那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.17,0:12:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.93,0:12:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.98,0:12:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又带回来一些奇奇怪怪的东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.50,0:12:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.25,0:12:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来的路上有一行人骑着自行车对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.17,0:12:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.08,0:12:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到它本来依附在其中一人的身上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.14,0:12:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来擦肩而过的时候跳到你身上来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.89,0:12:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候就应该告诉我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.77,0:13:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我满脑子都是丸子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.38,0:13:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有时间管这些杂碎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.47,0:13:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.60,0:13:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静下来  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.42,0:13:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个叫巢猫  没有什么危害的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.77,0:13:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为很弱小  所以会像这样附在人的身上来保护自己
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.83,0:13:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我叫它跟屁虫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.37,0:13:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前见过它吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.17,0:13:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是之前还没来这里的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.68,0:13:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在住过一段时间的镇上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.27,0:13:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是同一个吧  这里还留下了疤痕
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.69,0:13:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突如其来的访客啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.54,0:13:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我想起了苦涩的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.54,0:13:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫夏目贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.98,0:13:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请大家多多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.82,0:13:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兴趣是？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.54,0:13:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢什么类型的女生？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.63,0:13:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决定了要参加什么社团活动了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.66,0:13:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下问那么多  夏目君会很困扰的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.05,0:13:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.57,0:13:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.68,0:13:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.30,0:14:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙  快松开
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.51,0:14:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那件事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.38,0:14:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始处处关照我的同学们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.80,0:14:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过了几天  再也没有任何人跟我搭话了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.19,0:14:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候  那样反而更轻松
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.58,0:14:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个  我更在意当时被我扔到地上的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.10,0:14:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是让它受伤了  我会感觉很内疚的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.49,0:14:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀着这样的心情我就跑去看了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.72,0:14:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  你还在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.53,0:14:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.17,0:15:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你啊  人类的孩子  真是狂妄
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.21,0:15:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.69,0:15:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  依靠人类而生存的弱者
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.83,0:15:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妨碍了我  所以将会受到惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.98,0:15:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要诅咒你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.85,0:15:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你或者你周围的人会死的诅咒
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.30,0:15:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和周围的人完全没有关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.39,0:15:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才叫诅咒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.11,0:15:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是在将来的三十天内
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.72,0:16:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是能逃出我的五指山  我就给你解开诅咒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.97,0:16:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三十天？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.65,0:16:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要记住一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.18,0:16:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是逃到别的镇上去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.01,0:16:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个镇上就会有某人代替你去死
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.96,0:16:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后  那个黑镰刀的妖怪会经常出现
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.78,0:16:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直追着我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.79,0:16:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃到神社的我松懈下来就睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.89,0:16:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  对了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.75,0:16:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟那时被我踢倒的女孩子的关系拉近了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.89,0:17:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天你真够狠的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.38,0:17:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别过来  给我消失
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.68,0:17:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别过来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.52,0:17:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这之后  黑镰刀也一直追着我跑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.32,0:17:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我开始怀疑这家伙不是真心要追杀我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.43,0:17:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是在享受着和我之间的追赶游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.98,0:17:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也很高兴啊  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.14,0:17:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我适可而止啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.64,0:17:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么总是缠着我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.25,0:17:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明明那么讨厌你这种家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.61,0:17:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别自以为是了  人类
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.26,0:17:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是享受和你这种食物追赶的乐趣而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.15,0:17:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只妖怪也是食物吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.08,0:17:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙明明是妖怪  却要依附在人类身上保护自己
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.29,0:17:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法原谅这一点
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.68,0:17:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算如此…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.07,0:17:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得我给你下的诅咒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.24,0:18:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你或者你周围的人会死
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.63,0:18:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.10,0:18:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小宏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.69,0:18:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  好了  好了  不哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.27,0:18:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.05,0:18:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后黑镰刀终于追到了学校
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.00,0:18:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这已经是第几次了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.98,0:18:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何要这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.74,0:18:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我去趟办公室
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.50,0:18:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先等等
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.40,0:18:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由莉子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.18,0:18:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是这很奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.42,0:18:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  这些玻璃碎片都落在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.94,0:18:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种碎法也很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.87,0:18:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先好好调查一下  不会是夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.83,0:18:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说夏目君怎么会做这种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.48,0:18:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绪方…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.25,0:19:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  绪方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.37,0:19:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.66,0:19:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这件事  我的监护人被叫到了学校
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.30,0:19:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又被其他亲戚收留了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.13,0:19:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了  将诅咒解开吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.81,0:19:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就要离开这个城镇了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.77,0:19:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下来的人和我没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.16,0:19:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.61,0:19:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  你要离开这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.99,0:19:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是要逃跑  是没办法的事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.66,0:19:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗你的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.59,0:19:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诅咒什么的是骗你的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.70,0:19:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是在逗你玩而已
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.77,0:19:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法杀害人类
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.38,0:19:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这把镰刀对人类也不起作用
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.65,0:19:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原本就是被侍奉在这里的神灵
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.58,0:20:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为人类驱邪造福才是我的使命
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.16,0:20:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会去诅咒人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.71,0:20:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么你要撒谎呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.21,0:20:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我最讨厌你了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.15,0:20:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你给我消失掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.06,0:20:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论我去哪里都会被讨厌啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.65,0:20:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类也好  它们也罢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.75,0:20:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家没有讨厌夏目君哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.14,0:20:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.78,0:20:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认真关注过夏目君哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.22,0:20:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  绪方
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.33,0:20:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里我很开心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.04,0:20:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.87,0:21:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的哦  绪方
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.35,0:21:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也觉得很开心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.15,0:21:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  然后  前几天丰松说他看到夏目君了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.44,0:21:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.72,0:21:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.77,0:21:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟着一位看着很温柔的女士一起提着东西回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.80,0:21:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  丰松  要走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.33,0:21:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛  是那样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.65,0:21:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君被善良的人家收留了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.69,0:21:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我不知道夏目君在这个镇上看到了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.67,0:21:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不是与他有关的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.00,0:21:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将我从卡车下救了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.59,0:21:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这样胡思乱想着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.85,0:22:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后的几天  巢猫一直粘着我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.10,0:22:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某天突然离开不知道去了哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.15,0:22:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能又粘着其他人去了别的城镇了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.66,0:22:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许某天会再回到那个镇上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.36,0:22:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是那样的话  希望它告诉他们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.41,0:22:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我在那个镇上遇到的妖怪和人们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.99,0:22:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在过得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.45,0:24:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  夏目  你竟然跑进瓶子里  还真是不小心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.74,0:24:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被困住了  救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.76,0:24:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能让你被御柱干掉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.95,0:24:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.46,0:24:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是那么可靠啊  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.37,0:24:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.20,0:24:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
