[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.62,0:03:36.62,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur2\shad2\bord1}秋风来袭
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.92,0:24:15.96,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1\pos(191,296)}破碎的镜子
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.51,0:01:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就到文化祭了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.72,0:01:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们班打算做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.77,0:01:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天决定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.31,0:01:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我个人希望开个兔女郎咖啡店
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.14,0:01:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兔女郎应该没戏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.97,0:01:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要妖精什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.00,0:01:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖精?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.37,0:01:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.96,0:01:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.86,0:01:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在干什么啊  那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.56,0:02:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爬到那种地方  很危险…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.86,0:02:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.61,0:02:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.61,0:02:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.49,0:02:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.93,0:02:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.32,0:02:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西村
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.31,0:02:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北本
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.88,0:02:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被妖怪缠上了  这种话说不出口啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.28,0:02:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别穿着制服玩跳水啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.43,0:02:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要玩的话  起码把包放下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.53,0:02:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.68,0:02:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.52,0:02:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…这样下去的话会感冒的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.74,0:02:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先去我家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.93,0:02:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.23,0:02:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.31,0:02:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.45,0:02:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然到访  不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.63,0:02:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.84,0:02:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.45,0:03:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点洗个澡  洗个澡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.33,0:03:02.69,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.37,0:03:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.79,0:03:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久没有来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.08,0:03:05.68,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  不要太闹腾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.00,0:03:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  塔子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.60,0:03:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人都因为我才…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.03,0:03:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是爱添麻烦的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.45,0:03:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个城镇上我所遇到的都是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.71,0:03:25.51,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.52,0:03:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心地善良的人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.15,0:03:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要跟他们保密能看到妖怪的事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.85,0:03:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又在睡觉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.89,0:03:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太安静的话总觉得很没有干劲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.80,0:03:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点好起来哦  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.37,0:03:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.13,0:03:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掉到河里的时候  混进来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.38,0:04:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘…秘…秘密…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.58,0:04:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  那块石头
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.95,0:04:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是一如既往那么容易被奇怪的家伙盯上啊  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.57,0:04:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.75,0:04:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很感激  但是在屋子里穿着木屐...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.19,0:04:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来探望猫咪不倒翁的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.38,0:04:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样了?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.17,0:04:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  不知道为什么一直在睡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.25,0:04:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个好兆头
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.57,0:04:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为真疼起来的时候  睡也睡不着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.00,0:04:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一点点地恢复中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.29,0:04:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.47,0:05:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.48,0:05:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又来探病了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.99,0:05:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.63,0:05:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再通宵喝酒了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.24,0:05:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明天也要去学校
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.05,0:05:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别那么见外啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.89,0:05:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见外 见外
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.46,0:05:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒味好重啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.00,0:05:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经在喝了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.02,0:05:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了解除宿醉状态而喝酒  真是绝妙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.19,0:05:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小胡子什么时候也…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.91,0:05:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚我们也吵吵闹闹地保护你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.14,0:05:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.35,0:05:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说刚刚的石头
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.04,0:05:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给人一种讨厌的感觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.19,0:05:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  暂时小心点为妙哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.63,0:05:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是通宵了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.12,0:05:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  这次要做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.04,0:05:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女装咖啡店
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.29,0:05:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种尽是男生吃苦而且无聊的提案  反对
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.52,0:05:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兔女郎  兔女郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.97,0:05:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饮食店很难啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.12,0:06:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想当天到处去转转  展示类的比较好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.53,0:06:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说搞义卖吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.26,0:06:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赞成…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.94,0:06:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里也很热闹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.92,0:06:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持安静  举手一个个说意见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.67,0:06:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.11,0:06:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从每人的家里拿一些不用的东西来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.92,0:06:21.42,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是义卖吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.42,0:06:23.14,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是挺好的嘛  义卖
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.63,0:06:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我不怎么喜欢热闹
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.51,0:06:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过最近像这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.16,0:06:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着大家的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.37,0:06:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很安心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.38,0:06:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在看什么那么入神
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.61,0:06:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么掉到地上了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.32,0:06:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君  你在乱看什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.42,0:06:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.55,0:06:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  夏目就负责销售
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.02,0:06:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.51,0:06:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真不错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.26,0:06:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是挺好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.96,0:06:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.08,0:06:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…我可不善于接待客…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.78,0:07:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目负责销售啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.87,0:07:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别笑了  多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.43,0:07:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  二班搞义卖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.74,0:07:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼君你们班呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.68,0:07:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是话剧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.16,0:07:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话剧?  好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.10,0:07:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼君也出演吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.86,0:07:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我负责灯光
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.01,0:07:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨你们班呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.59,0:07:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男女互换咖啡店
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.06,0:07:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…直到去年为止都还不怎么和别人说话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.02,0:07:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候真是够呛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.77,0:07:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨被妖怪诅咒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.82,0:07:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次的文化祭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.83,0:07:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想尽情地享受
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.23,0:07:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.81,0:07:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然三个人都不怎么适应文化祭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.25,0:07:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过还是加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.74,0:07:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们班话剧的主角在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.56,0:07:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主角是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.46,0:08:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北本?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.62,0:08:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.81,0:08:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.75,0:08:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  西村
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.26,0:08:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  最近和多轨感情很不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.99,0:08:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好狡猾啊  好狡猾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.35,0:08:13.29,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.65,0:08:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感情好好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.78,0:08:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.09,0:08:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…夏目君他对感情好的朋友…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.58,0:08:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不会说出妖怪的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.49,0:08:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是对我们也不是什么都说的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.10,0:08:31.84,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都没机会和她说话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.10,0:08:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨同学是我的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.56,0:08:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  不是的  都说了不是那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.65,0:08:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北本是主角啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.55,0:08:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抽签抽出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.05,0:08:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要演什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.15,0:08:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎士比亚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.18,0:08:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白色紧身裤啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.68,0:08:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不会穿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.71,0:08:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要去看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.29,0:08:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.23,0:08:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是负责销售的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.76,0:08:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.13,0:08:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要微笑还要动作利落哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.86,0:09:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.11,0:09:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.17,0:09:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪的？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.04,0:09:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.17,0:09:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.42,0:09:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.36,0:09:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.44,0:09:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不小心打翻油漆罐了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.07,0:09:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心不要踩到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.31,0:09:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  油漆啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.71,0:09:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.46,0:09:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸色不太好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.64,0:09:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.46,0:09:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.86,0:09:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个班级已经开始制作道具了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.82,0:09:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是急性子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.63,0:09:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那是妖怪的血的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.62,0:09:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办呢…在学校里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.19,0:09:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.16,0:09:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.98,0:09:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.36,0:09:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个女生是刚才在庭院里看着地面的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.84,0:10:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  弄丢了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.83,0:10:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  我在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.02,0:10:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再…再见
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.22,0:10:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这块石头  操纵了那个女孩子了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.74,0:10:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力量这么强的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.05,0:10:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.30,0:10:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扔掉它…如果伤害到周围的人的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.85,0:10:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这时候  果然该打碎他或者烧一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.89,0:10:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.64,0:10:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘…秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.11,0:10:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.99,0:10:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.96,0:10:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.78,0:11:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.95,0:11:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.99,0:11:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  怎么了夏目同学
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.18,0:11:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.78,0:11:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.28,0:11:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发烧了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.04,0:11:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去医务室吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.37,0:11:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.34,0:11:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是回去的话  我送你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.79,0:11:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.55,0:11:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.34,0:11:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.28,0:11:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  吓我一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.28,0:11:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好  糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.75,0:11:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又变成了普通的石头
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.59,0:11:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实体到哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.81,0:11:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缠上你了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.18,0:11:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来封印着一只不一般的妖怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.44,0:11:55.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目的是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.48,0:11:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来是附身类的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.30,0:12:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕是想要附身到有着强大妖力的你身上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.51,0:12:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然目的是我的话  别人是否就没有危险了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.64,0:12:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  像那样偷偷附身在谁的身上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.09,0:12:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是为了能够接近你的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.54,0:12:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校的事物和人们或许引起这石子妖怪的好奇心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.96,0:12:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇心？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.55,0:12:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于长年沉睡在了河底
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.65,0:12:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自然会非常想要知道周遭的事物吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.45,0:12:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在和你接触的时候也是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.55,0:12:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它在吸取了你的力量的同时
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.34,0:12:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也应该想要窥视你的心灵才对
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.43,0:12:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.15,0:12:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密究竟是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.81,0:12:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密…我的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.01,0:12:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.62,0:12:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要露出破绽  不要掉以轻心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.84,0:12:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.74,0:12:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不久你的猫咪不倒翁保镖便会痊愈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.25,0:12:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前一定要努力哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.27,0:12:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  丙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.41,0:13:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石子妖怪想知道的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.10,0:13:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.41,0:13:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师  好好休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.23,0:13:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  这次学校要举办文化祭了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.46,0:13:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当了义卖会上的店员了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.45,0:13:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想尽情地享受…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.86,0:13:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起努力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.73,0:13:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有着很多的展品和店铺
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.06,0:13:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会很有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.69,0:13:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃的东西也有很多哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.64,0:13:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望一切顺利啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.09,0:13:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须找到那只妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.50,0:13:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能因为我而给学校里的大家带来灾祸
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.69,0:13:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.13,0:14:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西村  北本
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.86,0:14:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.81,0:14:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.56,0:14:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在来有什么事…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.48,0:14:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像那样偷偷附身在谁的身上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.12,0:14:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是为了能够接近你的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.30,0:14:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.52,0:14:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样盯我们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.82,0:14:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.10,0:14:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你是不是很不喜欢担任销售一职？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.06,0:14:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.13,0:14:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你今天的脸色很差啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.40,0:14:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.59,0:14:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你原本就个经常顾忌这个顾忌那个的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.82,0:14:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要管我们  难得的机会  你能高兴就好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.94,0:14:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不喜欢的话  就说出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.66,0:14:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会代替你做的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.59,0:14:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.01,0:14:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.42,0:15:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是真的…真的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.17,0:15:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分期待
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.80,0:15:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.22,0:15:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么办才好啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.57,0:15:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是负责销售的  多多关照啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.54,0:15:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  这是夏目的份
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.18,0:15:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  这是辻君你的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.41,0:15:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也终究沦落成销售人员了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.52,0:15:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？围裙？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.64,0:15:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  销售人员全都要穿这个哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.63,0:15:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个蝴蝶结也得各自缝上哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.23,0:16:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎并没有什么奇特的事情发生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.94,0:16:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要露出破绽  不要掉以轻心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.34,0:16:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.34,0:16:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这边帮个忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.77,0:16:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  这就来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.67,0:16:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我眼前的是短剑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.16,0:16:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剑柄正对着我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.66,0:16:23.78,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.26,0:16:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我做不到  尽管如此  我还是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.08,0:16:27.97,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.97,0:16:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊  这么多的台词怎么记得住啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.44,0:16:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们看起来好像变得憔悴了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.65,0:16:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  拿到那边去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.74,0:16:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.78,0:16:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然过着不可掉以轻心的每一日
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.15,0:16:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那只妖怪却完完全全消匿了气息
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.29,0:16:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于  到了文化祭当日
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.01,0:17:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是适合你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.83,0:17:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临  请拿起来仔细看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.82,0:17:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢…欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.82,0:17:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  能拍个照吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.79,0:17:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？照相？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.55,0:17:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉店员先生  这个能附送给我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.86,0:17:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.06,0:17:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  受欢迎的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.85,0:17:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.04,0:17:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是男装吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.49,0:17:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  这个要多少？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.39,0:17:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.13,0:17:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个那个…店员先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.91,0:17:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.68,0:17:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比当初想象的还要令人头疼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.96,0:17:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目辛苦了  去休息一会儿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.57,0:17:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  多谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.25,0:17:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.65,0:17:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是没办法的事吧  快点快点…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.15,0:18:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密…究竟是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.88,0:18:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是朋友  却要保密吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.98,0:18:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟想知道什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.55,0:18:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那女孩没有关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.28,0:18:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.21,0:18:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的目标是我对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.85,0:18:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是危险啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.57,0:18:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须抓住它…都是因为我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.27,0:18:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.64,0:18:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.00,0:18:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.93,0:18:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那女生还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.54,0:18:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.37,0:19:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.53,0:19:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  听说有好吃的才来的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.75,0:19:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退下  小石子！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.19,0:19:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这弱小的家伙哟！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.16,0:19:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.20,0:19:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.34,0:19:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密…究竟是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.91,0:19:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便有秘密不说  但依旧还是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.35,0:19:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在保护什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.54,0:19:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能保护住他们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.22,0:19:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.86,0:19:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  转校生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.53,0:19:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.39,0:19:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是时候去问塔子阿姨要一部自行车啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.04,0:19:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不然不能一起上学了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.49,0:19:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  不用在意我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.01,0:20:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实不会骑自行车
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.26,0:20:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.47,0:20:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.84,0:20:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.75,0:20:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果后面没有人扶着的话我就骑不了的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.30,0:20:14.75,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.91,0:20:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所想保护的只是平凡的日常
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.84,0:20:15.71,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好很好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.47,0:20:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及那些陪伴着我的朋友们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.05,0:20:18.10,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脚不要停下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.10,0:20:19.65,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不要放手哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.08,0:20:21.07,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.28,0:20:22.46,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好很不错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.68,0:20:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次这般能够陪伴着我的人们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.81,0:20:27.19,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉真好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.11,0:20:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说是非常珍贵的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.73,0:20:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我究竟该怎么办才好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.88,0:20:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好很好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.55,0:20:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些珍贵的友人愈多  我便愈加不安
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.11,0:20:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽是些我所不懂的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.39,0:20:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好重…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.43,0:20:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.61,0:20:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  你来救我了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.01,0:21:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  那种妖怪连封印都不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.50,0:21:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赶走它了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.85,0:21:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师  太好了  变得这么有精神
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.69,0:21:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都没能做到
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.02,0:21:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一个人什么都没能做到
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.84,0:21:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人就是那样的生物吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.02,0:21:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.16,0:21:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我似乎看到了一些东西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.86,0:21:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令我勇气倍加的东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.88,0:21:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你终于醒了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.68,0:21:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟在做些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.01,0:21:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽做些危险的事情  老是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.13,0:21:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟在想些什么  你这个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.74,0:21:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说夏目倒下了？没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.78,0:21:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  夏目这么有精神
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.20,0:21:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  哎呀  大家都在了…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.87,0:22:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.82,0:22:04.26,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.95,0:22:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我想保护的人们保护着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.28,0:22:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我便将这些我生疏的事务一点点积聚起来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.32,0:22:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续前行着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.65,0:22:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束了呢  文化祭
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.50,0:22:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  去不去钓鱼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.10,0:22:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑着自行车来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.63,0:22:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.46,0:22:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便微小  只要一步步积累起来…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.28,0:24:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近感觉田沼在躲着我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.81,0:24:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太在意别人的脸色了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.42,0:24:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.59,0:24:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果发生了什么的话  希望他能告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.15,0:24:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.27,0:24:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想要隐瞒的…只是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.29,0:24:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了  把我的镜子还给我
