[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.09,0:03:09.09,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0002,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}月分祭
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.97,0:24:16.02,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\pos(238,296)}被供奉的神灵
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだうしろ姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}やさしさで胸がいたくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々がいとおしくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音(ね)に　夕闇に　懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも一緒だよ、と　叶わぬことくり返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}ぬくもりはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}あざやかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来にかえながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだうしろ姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}やさしさで胸がいたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々がいとおしくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音(ね)に　夕闇に　懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも一緒だよ、と　叶わぬことくり返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}ぬくもりはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}あざやかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来にかえながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下  回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离  辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下  回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离  辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.11,0:01:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君  吃中饭了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.86,0:01:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.72,0:01:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮我把客厅里的信拿来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.69,0:01:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.49,0:02:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.54,0:02:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  最近这妖怪可是「自由行」啊  猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.19,0:02:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要怪到我头上来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.57,0:02:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是自作自受  白痴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.86,0:02:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为你乱管闲事才在妖怪里出名了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.31,0:02:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得好奇跑过来围观你的家伙也越来越多
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.86,0:02:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是得不偿失
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.86,0:02:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点给我更多的馒头
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.45,0:02:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有馒头就罢工  馒头罢工
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.05,0:02:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要我供奉您馒头的话  就给我好好干活啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.21,0:02:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么?!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.48,0:02:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  有青蛙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.11,0:02:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为回暖就误以为是春天了吧…这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.21,0:02:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去抓它了哦夏目  站住站住
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.56,0:02:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.45,0:03:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风变得柔和了  马上就到春天了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.46,0:03:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.77,0:03:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一定是夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.80,0:03:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.89,0:03:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么怎么做  总之去问一下话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.42,0:03:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪的声音…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.87,0:03:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  他会听我们说话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.01,0:03:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒也是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.97,0:03:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  抓住他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.50,0:03:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  我会听你们说话的  冷静下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.34,0:03:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  请觉悟吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.29,0:03:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  请觉悟吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.33,0:03:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.74,0:03:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  请稍等
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.77,0:03:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有想要拜托于你之事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.26,0:04:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好久不见了  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.95,0:04:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能主动来探望我  真是开心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.83,0:04:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  CUT！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.87,0:04:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了  今天的摄影到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.17,0:04:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个  名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.83,0:04:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和您一起工作十分荣幸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.39,0:04:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了  头发上有花瓣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.63,0:04:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是觉得很荣幸  那么下次见
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.70,0:04:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吗  那个神秘的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.97,0:04:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然分不清到底是好青年还是纨绔子弟
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.27,0:04:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那种神秘感真是让人受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.66,0:04:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  现在哪有花瓣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.81,0:04:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取  特地让你过来抱歉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.93,0:05:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.00,0:05:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就单刀直入了  是关于工作的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.61,0:05:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三隅地区的某位土地所有人向我哭诉受到妖怪纠缠
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.68,0:05:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道月分祭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.37,0:05:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.82,0:05:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是各地都会举办的庆祝丰收的祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.56,0:05:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,象征丰收的丰月神
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.43,0:05:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及象征地涸的不月神
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.53,0:05:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这两根神柱被点燃后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.80,0:05:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村民们进行对决的十年一度的祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.13,0:05:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说来  听说是很古老的祭典  现在已不再盛行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.35,0:05:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.08,0:05:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是妖怪们却很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.03,0:05:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎那两个神明会十年一度聚集起来  反复进行对决
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.28,0:05:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而今年就正好是第十年
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.84,0:05:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还真是狂欢呐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.19,0:05:58.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得真悠闲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.62,0:06:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过了吧  是丰收时期的祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.95,0:06:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不月神获胜的话  三隅的山会枯竭的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.90,0:06:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是胜负只能靠运气
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.04,0:06:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们真能进行比试那也无妨
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.23,0:06:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往常的话妖怪们会跑到祭典上来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.93,0:06:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但今年的状况很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.65,0:06:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎丰月神没有出现
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.07,0:06:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我调查了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.51,0:06:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是被某个除妖人当做异形封印于某处
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.55,0:06:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不分青红皂白
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.15,0:06:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若丰月神不战而败的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.35,0:06:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三隅地方接下来数年就会变成不毛之地了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.25,0:06:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以名取  我想让你在祭典结束前找出丰月神
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.19,0:06:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  何时开始祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.72,0:06:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.51,0:06:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是明天啊  明天？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.82,0:07:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若未能及时找着的话…采取最终手段也无妨
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.53,0:07:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之过来看看  接下来该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.97,0:07:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就替我从这附近的妖怪那收集些情报过来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.95,0:07:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我则前去举办祭典的三隅原附近看看
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.69,0:07:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.82,0:07:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能留主人独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.23,0:07:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊就留你负责守护
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.68,0:07:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.77,0:07:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有关系  去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.47,0:07:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该说过让你走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.10,0:07:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.18,0:07:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不听从我的吩咐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.31,0:08:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让路  让路  让路…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.39,0:08:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.60,0:08:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不月大人的随从
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.17,0:08:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不月大人来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.73,0:08:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不月
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.54,0:08:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.17,0:08:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是不月…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.07,0:08:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.91,0:08:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月神的缺席会暴露不过是时间的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.29,0:08:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阔别十年再度一睹其尊容
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.79,0:08:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远都是如此的美丽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.84,0:08:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样两位于三隅原就位之际祭典就开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.44,0:08:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是没见着丰月神的身影呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.79,0:08:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真令人担心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.68,0:08:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.06,0:08:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月神差不多该驾到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.16,0:08:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月神被封印一说是谣传吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.27,0:08:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦…那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.35,0:08:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月大人驾到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.86,0:08:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是丰月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.18,0:08:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月大人是何等的美丽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.96,0:08:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是惊艳四座
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.07,0:09:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫色头纱下配上白色的面具
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.69,0:09:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.48,0:09:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是…丰月…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.05,0:09:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.30,0:09:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.55,0:09:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚同夏目一模一样的妖怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.51,0:09:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对…那正是夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.77,0:09:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只肥猫也在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.36,0:09:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得去问个清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.07,0:09:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主子是驱妖人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.82,0:09:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若说是的话又怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.89,0:09:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决不允许阻挠丰月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.60,0:09:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种地方有丰月神的侍从们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.96,0:09:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在这偷偷摸摸地做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.81,0:09:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.65,0:10:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论你们这样的小喽啰们做什么手脚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.85,0:10:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对是我们不月大人取胜
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.26,0:10:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传言你们丰月大人还未露面
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.08,0:10:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不是因为厌烦你们和这座山而逃离这里了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.57,0:10:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.88,0:10:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月大人才不是那样的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.92,0:10:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是就是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.04,0:10:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,定是丰月大人忙于准备
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.83,0:10:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在刚刚的队列中有见到本人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.64,0:10:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.88,0:10:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会是看错了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.81,0:10:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.24,0:10:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧给我滚回去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.94,0:10:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了  给我闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.74,0:10:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月是逃跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.56,0:10:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是在的话就现身来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.38,0:10:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里胡作非为可真不给我面子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.99,0:10:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心  丰月就在此
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.35,0:10:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月大人  是丰月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.70,0:10:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑衫之众…你们只需返回静待祭典开始即可
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.75,0:11:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  没有穿帮
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.79,0:11:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个了不起的虚张声势  夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.53,0:11:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.71,0:11:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  又见面了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.30,0:11:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在这里…做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.56,0:11:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那正是…我想要问你的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.49,0:11:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种地方打扮得如此花枝招展的是干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.99,0:11:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是我想要弄得这么华丽的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.53,0:11:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…丰月大人  您认识这位驱妖人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.25,0:11:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.77,0:11:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是受那些白笠所托假扮丰月神来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.36,0:11:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.37,0:11:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个圆圆的生物不是保镖来着的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.37,0:12:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  要保护这孱弱的家伙是何等的艰辛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.81,0:12:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且在这座山上有座泉涌美酒的古井
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.53,0:12:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎能坐等其干涸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.30,0:12:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过若这座山枯竭的话苦恼的不仅是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.72,0:12:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想试试看
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.40,0:12:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生能否助我一臂之力？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.83,0:12:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能同你合作正是我最感激的了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.91,0:12:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  原本真觉得只身一人无路可投了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.22,0:12:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我说清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.02,0:12:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并非只是前来解除丰月的封印
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.98,0:12:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了人类我必须保护这座山
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.70,0:12:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若未能找到丰月而不月得胜的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.97,0:12:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我则必须要驱除掉他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.45,0:12:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连危及到你的安危之时也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.99,0:12:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.06,0:13:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有关丰月神的消息得多向他们打听打听
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.73,0:13:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.26,0:13:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.61,0:13:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉你变得有些直率了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.62,0:13:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知名取他会否有一天也能变成这样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.42,0:13:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祭典要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.68,0:13:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了  夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.17,0:13:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  是丰月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.93,0:13:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请上座神轿
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.53,0:13:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来比赛是什么样的较量呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.97,0:13:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也尚未被告知
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.22,0:13:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有过赛跑  有过寻物
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.86,0:13:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次经由占卜来做决定
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.60,0:13:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掉以轻心了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.08,0:13:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岂不是没法想对策了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.70,0:13:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是  怎么想也无济于事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.17,0:13:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上路吧  丰月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.09,0:13:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.84,0:14:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  肥猫你也要好好工作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.66,0:14:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.02,0:14:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  上路了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.96,0:14:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让路  让路
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.91,0:14:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月大人驾到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.92,0:14:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若不想让他们驱妖的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.73,0:14:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就努力不要让事情走到那一步
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.58,0:14:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若没有那般决心的话是无法成功的哟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.14,0:14:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是丰月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.30,0:14:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月大人驾到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.86,0:14:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若在这里暴露出我是人类的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.42,0:14:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生他们会没关系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.31,0:14:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会吗？ 老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.17,0:14:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月大人的膝上有只圆圆的小猪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.17,0:14:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只白白的像年糕一样的珍兽是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.40,0:15:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有那般奇兽相伴身边  不愧是丰月大人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.00,0:15:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  就是那里了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.20,0:15:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不月大人同其随从黑衫众
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.64,0:15:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太慢了  你们白笠
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.60,0:15:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧上前
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.44,0:15:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  就因之前你们搅局
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.46,0:15:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们身边太危险  谁敢过去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.23,0:15:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.77,0:15:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位神…欢迎驾临三隅山中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.80,0:15:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本次也以胜负来定夺管制本山之尊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.09,0:15:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据占卜来看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.54,0:15:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本次的比赛为…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.04,0:15:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狩猎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.63,0:15:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狩猎？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.03,0:15:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,率先擒拿住从该壶中跑出的怪物的一方为优胜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.21,0:15:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么准备好了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.60,0:16:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,月分祭典开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.72,0:16:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.22,0:16:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟紧不月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.99,0:16:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要输了哦  丰月殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.31,0:16:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不月大人领先一步
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.25,0:16:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真就像风一般
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.01,0:16:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连从壶里跑出啥东西来都没能看清
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.44,0:16:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.45,0:16:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.64,0:16:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然办不到
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.53,0:16:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  帮不上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.97,0:16:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有  若不是夏目大人您愿做替身的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.52,0:16:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在铃响之际就已注定我们输了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.51,0:16:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会想办法找出野兽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.03,0:17:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时请夏目大人找出丰月神大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.42,0:17:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.53,0:17:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.88,0:17:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有逞强就好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.15,0:17:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.28,0:17:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先去看看被封印的地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.00,0:17:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么东西在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.14,0:17:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了  怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.25,0:17:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.67,0:17:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.95,0:17:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.89,0:17:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追逐着像龙一样的野兽？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.75,0:17:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  夏目  你又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.59,0:17:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.43,0:18:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就靠白笠他们自己又可以走到哪一步呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.51,0:18:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来不月神又占了上风了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.65,0:18:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么回事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.32,0:18:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是我的错觉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.16,0:18:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才一瞬间  我感觉名取先生有点犹豫祛除不月神
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.76,0:18:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  就算是错觉也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.08,0:18:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生  我们不光只有白笠他们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.19,0:18:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师和柊都在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.72,0:18:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论怎么样  一起找出丰月神吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.98,0:18:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是一个人  如果是两个人的话  总会有办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.61,0:18:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.85,0:18:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退下  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.85,0:18:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.06,0:18:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.66,0:19:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.65,0:19:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  柊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.07,0:19:08.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.22,0:19:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.55,0:19:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为自己死定了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.61,0:19:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.87,0:19:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  你才是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.51,0:19:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长得像棵豆芽  却意外地结实啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.57,0:19:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野兽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.94,0:19:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你扫落下去就逃走了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.79,0:19:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  要赶紧回去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.19,0:19:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生他们会担心的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.03,0:19:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.91,0:19:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的  赶快
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.32,0:19:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静下来  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.07,0:19:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取大人知道怎么保护自己
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.52,0:19:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且那边有肥猫在
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.05,0:19:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先你先调整好气息
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.85,0:20:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把手伸出来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.05,0:20:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够安抚心理的咒术
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.40,0:20:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以反弹一次野兽的攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.92,0:20:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来应该是画在心脏那里的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.54,0:20:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.16,0:20:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么柊你也来画一个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.21,0:20:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,画在妖怪身上也没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.37,0:20:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.40,0:20:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那快点
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.84,0:20:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.14,0:20:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆流而上的话  应该可以和他们汇合的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.80,0:20:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生他们也一定会往那里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.08,0:20:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.52,0:20:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是个很难完成的半吊子委托啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.54,0:20:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许找丰月神只是表面文章
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.68,0:20:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的目的是让我们采取最终手段吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.48,0:21:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了解除十年一次的隐忧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.83,0:21:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会是把祛除神明这种危险的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.90,0:21:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强加给名取的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.01,0:21:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祛除神明？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.66,0:21:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就非做不可了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.34,0:21:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能做的事  尽量做出来给他们看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.25,0:21:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们被冲得相当远啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.83,0:21:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不快点的话就会被黑衫众们抢先了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.10,0:21:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑衫众们
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.81,0:21:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.04,0:21:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.89,0:21:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  中陷阱了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.34,0:21:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于抓到野兽了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.60,0:21:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧去叫不月神吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.49,0:21:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.86,0:21:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是野兽  那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.22,0:22:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  怎么会这样  那不是丰月神大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.54,0:22:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  到底怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.85,0:22:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  等等  有点奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.83,0:22:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个真的是丰月神吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.65,0:22:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹿角假面  应该没错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.69,0:22:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  有点人类孩子的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.30,0:22:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.50,0:22:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道  人类的孩子在暗算我们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.55,0:24:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的是丰月吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.70,0:24:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是被祛除了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.54,0:24:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被发现了  到此为止了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.27,0:24:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.55,0:24:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去找丰月神了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.80,0:24:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  老师和名取先生你们在的话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.50,0:24:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会成功的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.29,0:24:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要感谢的话就奉上馒头吧
