[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.33,0:02:44.29,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1}妖怪之名
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.88,0:24:15.94,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1}浮春之乡
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}なくした温もりを一つ一つ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色取り取りの君のカケラは　笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出の作り方も　まるでうまくならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れに　タダ身を任せて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこに行けばいい　この闇の先でまだ
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな　君のカケラ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}なくした温もりを一つ一つ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色取り取りの君のカケラは　笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出の作り方も　まるでうまくならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れに　タダ身を任せて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこに行けばいい　この闇の先でまだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな　君のカケラ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.01,0:01:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从小时候开始就时常能看见一些奇妙的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.43,0:01:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  今天也没有钓到
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.56,0:01:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真饿啊  还是弄些通草吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.52,0:01:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.97,0:01:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才有没有在这一带看见人类的小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.13,0:02:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的持有者
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.88,0:02:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目玲子的孙子应该逃往了这里才对
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.20,0:02:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他藏起来的话就连你们也吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.91,0:02:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都不知道啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.17,0:02:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.10,0:02:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶…那混蛋跑去哪里了…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.25,0:02:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙看起来很好吃啊  夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.44,0:02:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.99,0:02:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.04,0:02:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎别人都看不见
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.88,0:02:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.20,0:02:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就是所谓的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.40,0:02:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖母的遗物  友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.34,0:02:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有强大妖力的祖母玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.04,0:02:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她对遇见过的所有妖怪都发出了挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.41,0:02:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打败后便将它们收为小弟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.64,0:02:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并让他们写下自己的名字作为证据
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.70,0:03:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被叫了名字之后便不能违背命令
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.45,0:03:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个契约书便是友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.62,0:03:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从继承了这本书之后
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.17,0:03:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被妖怪们追赶成了家常便饭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.07,0:03:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要调整好呼吸再进去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.29,0:03:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茶碗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.29,0:03:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.60,0:03:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  快点出来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.41,0:03:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要擅自跑进别人家的下面
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.41,0:03:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.50,0:03:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.93,0:03:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.31,0:03:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.74,0:03:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买东西回来晚了  没事吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.67,0:03:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.57,0:03:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.68,0:03:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  看见了一只老鼠
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.98,0:03:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是错觉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.23,0:03:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事呢  我们家还有一只小猫呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.89,0:03:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.08,0:04:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看呢  搞得这么脏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.59,0:04:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  今天就吃牛肉火锅吧  贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.08,0:04:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.45,0:04:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是危险啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.12,0:04:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要避免做出奇怪的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.40,0:04:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真的有老鼠的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.18,0:04:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得去买个老鼠夹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.23,0:04:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  大概是我看错了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.22,0:04:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是邻居家的小狗跑进来了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.80,0:04:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志  再吃一碗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.82,0:04:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.39,0:04:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双亲早逝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.52,0:04:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在亲戚的互相推托中收养了我的是藤原一家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.32,0:04:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是我最重要的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.37,0:04:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是叫影茶碗的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.14,0:04:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经在地板下面住了两星期了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.69,0:04:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都住了两星期…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.09,0:05:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  你是保镖吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.28,0:05:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点  呆子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.78,0:05:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中了哦  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.90,0:05:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去再拿一根过来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.62,0:05:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.82,0:05:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名匠做的茶碗被丢弃以后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.23,0:05:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸取了大地的力量  就变成了妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.39,0:05:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于爱慕人类  就常常住进旧民宅的地板下面
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.38,0:05:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱慕人类…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.12,0:05:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当那户人家将要遭遇灾难的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.80,0:05:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会在房子里到处乱跑以传达这个信息
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.79,0:05:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定还会一时冲动代替那户人家来承受这份灾难
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.97,0:05:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有…危害吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.09,0:05:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样子啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.39,0:05:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待腻了之后便会离开  不要理它
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.15,0:05:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.54,0:05:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了我做这个保镖也只是和你约好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.48,0:05:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你死后我可以得到友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.14,0:05:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前从那些意在夺取友人帐的家伙手中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.45,0:05:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护好你的安危
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.25,0:05:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.01,0:05:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是夏目大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.08,0:05:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是前来请求您归还我的名字的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.13,0:06:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继承了友人帐的我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.27,0:06:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代替祖母将名字还给了妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.90,0:06:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先要想象对方的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.46,0:06:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后念道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.75,0:06:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「护吾之人  显其名」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.94,0:06:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送还名字所需要的条件是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.49,0:06:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与玲子拥有相同血脉之人的唾液和气息
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.88,0:06:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太感谢您了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.55,0:06:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归还了名字之后就会觉得很累
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.27,0:06:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个混蛋  友人帐又变薄了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.76,0:06:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在想什么啊  你知道吗  混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.33,0:06:44.15,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擅自地前来  擅自地离去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.62,0:06:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不被这些东西所左右
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.52,0:06:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知何时  我才能那么坚强呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.73,0:06:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么声音
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.22,0:06:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是脚步声
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.60,0:07:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当那户人家将要遭遇灾难的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.07,0:07:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会在房子里到处乱跑以传达这个信息
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.30,0:07:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的在到处跑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.34,0:07:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.30,0:07:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.99,0:07:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我的错吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.37,0:07:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说不久就会有灾难降临我的家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.59,0:07:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.31,0:07:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于开始为情所困了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.40,0:07:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是那样子的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.68,0:07:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有些睡眠不足
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.88,0:07:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是半夜在看色情书刊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.97,0:07:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.24,0:07:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么什么  夏目君怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.66,0:07:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和女生无关的事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.57,0:07:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  小气鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.02,0:07:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我有什么关系嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.08,0:07:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来到这个小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.30,0:07:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结交到了许多朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.90,0:07:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖母她…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.10,0:08:00.20,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.20,0:08:01.10,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.41,0:08:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子似乎没有人类的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.90,0:08:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以她从一开始便尽找妖怪们打架吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.71,0:08:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.98,0:08:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  拐杖…拐杖…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.56,0:08:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧  拐杖在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.48,0:08:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能站起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.58,0:08:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  真体贴
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.73,0:08:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小哥你能看见我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.96,0:08:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了  是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.10,0:08:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂小哥  你有着很不得了的力量呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.94,0:08:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.10,0:08:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好  我的眼睛不好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.91,0:08:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小哥  帮婆婆我做点事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.33,0:08:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久以前
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.16,0:08:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这附近向一个十分强大的妖怪借了镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.25,0:08:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道名字
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.28,0:08:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她似乎因为会招来巨大的灾难
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.51,0:08:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而被其他妖怪们所畏惧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.62,0:08:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果是小哥你这样有实力的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.56,0:08:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定能找到她
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.82,0:09:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我  不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.77,0:09:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我不能帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.04,0:09:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小哥  这可不行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.22,0:09:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得见妖怪的话就应该知道的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.42,0:09:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拒绝妖怪们的要求的话会怎么样…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.66,0:09:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之我不想卷进麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.66,0:09:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那种招来灾难的妖怪扯上关系的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.30,0:09:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是招惹到什么进藤原家的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.20,0:09:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很可怜  但我看中你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.54,0:09:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不帮忙的话  就诅咒你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.59,0:09:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.39,0:09:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天也在这里等着你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.31,0:09:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不来的话…杀了你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.12,0:09:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.37,0:09:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.19,0:09:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惨了  遇到了一个怪家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.46,0:09:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你被诅咒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.16,0:09:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然对我的猎物出手  究竟是何方妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.74,0:09:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老…老婆婆…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.72,0:09:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆婆？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.16,0:09:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉有些可怕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.74,0:10:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  振作一点  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.15,0:10:03.13,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.62,0:10:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.85,0:10:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉老婆婆说的事情让人很在意
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.95,0:10:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,影茶碗还在乱跑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.12,0:10:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我将灾难招来了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.14,0:10:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年也不开花吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.26,0:10:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样枯萎下去的话就要失去兴致变得寂寞了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.93,0:10:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  老婆婆我来帮助你吧  等着我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.33,0:10:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.02,0:10:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说是那老婆婆妖怪的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.54,0:10:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.54,0:10:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.01,0:10:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说等到明天的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.15,0:10:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵  我等不及了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.94,0:10:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易见到个可以找到那家伙的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.28,0:10:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被跑掉了的话太可惜了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.44,0:11:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆婆我可是非常没耐心的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.64,0:11:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是帮我呢  还是不帮我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.40,0:11:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  帮你就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.29,0:11:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之不要进这家里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.55,0:11:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个老婆婆
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.70,0:11:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是连老师您也无法驱除掉的强力妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.13,0:11:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个大概是曾掌管神社  拥有神格的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.94,0:11:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就另当别论了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.28,0:11:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是小妖怪撞上的话就该遭报应了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.46,0:11:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么厉害吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.91,0:11:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真伤脑筋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.42,0:11:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过事到如今
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.55,0:11:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的神
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.50,0:11:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概也都稍显不足而且力量衰弱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.86,0:11:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她眼睛看东西都模模糊糊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.22,0:11:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便陪她找找赶紧了结了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.22,0:11:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小角色无法轻易接近
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.39,0:11:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.74,0:11:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才会飞奔到能看到妖怪的我的身边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.24,0:11:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法同妖怪和人类交往的神
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.72,0:12:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.98,0:12:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个味道  在这边  小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.15,0:12:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的来了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.68,0:12:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有选择的余地啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.73,0:12:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.55,0:12:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很香吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.95,0:12:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了炫耀一番就戴上了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.73,0:12:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实…很香呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.53,0:12:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.99,0:12:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧…就是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.79,0:12:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  往这边走  小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.80,0:12:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这前方的森林里同她相遇了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.70,0:12:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请别叫我小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.18,0:12:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.76,0:12:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同妖怪们接触得少
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.80,0:12:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才不知道友人帐的夏目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.35,0:12:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么走着都要迷路了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.70,0:12:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边哟  往这边
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.77,0:12:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  就在这附近跟那孩子相遇了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.07,0:12:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.11,0:12:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说会招致劫难的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.75,0:12:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个什么样的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.98,0:13:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然看得也不是相当的清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.72,0:13:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个相当小的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.28,0:13:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小的？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.76,0:13:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽全力的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.21,0:13:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和老师多少应该能应付得了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.57,0:13:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  婆婆不是说过向它借了镜子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.16,0:13:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是那么危险的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.40,0:13:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  那个时候觉得在意的就是这个了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.57,0:13:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和我聊天的对象很少
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.88,0:13:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最疼爱的是在住处附近的一棵开花老树
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.57,0:13:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是被强势的恶灵所侵蚀了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.79,0:13:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老树…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.09,0:13:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来那个梦是这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.98,0:13:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因此那棵树枯萎了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.11,0:13:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要驱除恶灵需要镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.20,0:13:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四处奔波找寻的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.58,0:13:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个拿着镜子的家伙就坐在那了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.96,0:13:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想着要去抢过来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.62,0:13:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是自己却吃了亏
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.89,0:13:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是个不中用的神
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.35,0:13:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是告诉它无论如何都想要镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.65,0:13:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.31,0:13:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是让人害怕的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.32,0:14:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是个相当好的家伙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.44,0:14:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.87,0:14:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是其他妖怪总是远离她惧怕着她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.43,0:14:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙自己也这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.24,0:14:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己会招致灾厄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.13,0:14:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且自己不喜欢人类
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.03,0:14:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然得到了镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.57,0:14:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我自己没能成功驱除
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.98,0:14:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是想去把镜子还给她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.55,0:14:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果她却说讨厌照镜子  于是不肯收下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.66,0:14:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就约好偶尔见面聊天
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.96,0:14:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样仔细看来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.20,0:14:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这边有些伤痕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.05,0:14:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被妖怪们惧怕成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.67,0:14:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却是像被人类留下的伤痕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.55,0:14:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不禁觉得她很可爱便将她带至住处
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.89,0:14:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到我的屋子之后
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.19,0:14:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知为何有些失落
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.77,0:15:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那以后道明情况之后
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.34,0:15:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她便帮我驱除了老树上的恶灵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.65,0:15:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  这朵花就是那棵树上的花
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.08,0:15:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但说起来  这是为何呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.92,0:15:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的味道和她很相近
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.51,0:15:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细看起来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.99,0:15:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的相貌也是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.34,0:15:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.91,0:15:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也请让我好好看看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.49,0:15:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从刚才起就能微弱的感受到
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.50,0:15:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的热量
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.21,0:15:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆婆
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.38,0:15:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆婆所找的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.84,0:15:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.59,0:15:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.69,0:15:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次绝对不让你逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.66,0:15:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.91,0:15:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这之前的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.79,0:15:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左肩快要…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.00,0:15:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.27,0:16:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我滚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.50,0:16:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.39,0:16:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振作些 你这软弱的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.25,0:16:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.70,0:16:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小哥  太好了  肩膀没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.01,0:16:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为会被吃掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.13,0:16:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  没有骨折
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.04,0:16:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直以为那个大馒头  是小哥的保镖
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.21,0:16:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不管用
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.91,0:16:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.85,0:16:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是我赶走那妖怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.69,0:16:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来也是这家伙太不注意了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.32,0:16:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.77,0:16:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不变得更加谨慎的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.21,0:16:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经和以前不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.82,0:16:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.26,0:16:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本上这家伙的肩膀手臂少一只两只都无所谓的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.51,0:16:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要友人帐没事就行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.58,0:16:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  友人帐没有关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.46,0:16:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆婆
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.45,0:16:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐里面有您的名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.83,0:17:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.08,0:17:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  说起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.50,0:17:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实好像是在什么东西上写下了名字
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.69,0:17:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之后也不知为何她就不再来这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.03,0:17:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆婆  您应该怎样也找不到她的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.26,0:17:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那应该是人类的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.17,0:17:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫做夏目玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.34,0:17:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的祖母
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.78,0:17:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护吾之人  显其名
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.49,0:17:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还汝之名
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.90,0:17:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请收下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.89,0:17:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青梔子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.34,0:17:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.56,0:17:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欣赏那棵树上的花是我唯一的乐趣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.49,0:17:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.64,0:17:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有镜子的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.62,0:17:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.05,0:17:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  那个…坐在那的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.75,0:17:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  那家伙是灾难的源头
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.15,0:18:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说比神还恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.53,0:18:02.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要太靠近了  绕远路吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.46,0:18:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.80,0:18:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.66,0:18:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那散发着人类味道的家伙竟然是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.40,0:18:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还是收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.91,0:18:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛痛痛痛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.59,0:18:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕  掉以轻心了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.70,0:18:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拐杖  拐杖呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.12,0:18:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.80,0:18:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拐杖的话在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.58,0:18:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能站起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.04,0:18:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能否将你的镜子给我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.37,0:18:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我唯一所珍爱着的朋友需要镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.83,0:18:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镜子的话在不远处的店铺里…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.39,0:18:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能借我一段时间就好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.72,0:18:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.84,0:18:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.66,0:18:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.68,0:18:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着也没药敷上去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.34,0:18:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  受伤了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.74,0:18:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.87,0:18:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我好好瞧瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.25,0:18:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真痒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.96,0:19:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.82,0:19:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也在  真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.21,0:19:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来还镜子了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.03,0:19:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不需要那个了  送您了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.90,0:19:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.28,0:19:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌…照镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.87,0:19:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最近经常来到这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.62,0:19:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实很想去更远的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.10,0:19:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当相当地远
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.36,0:19:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都不知道的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.89,0:19:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要不要去我家玩玩
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.02,0:19:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.59,0:19:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在虽然破旧着
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.74,0:19:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却是在能开出美丽的花的老树的旁边哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.66,0:19:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.13,0:19:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.69,0:19:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神社
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.02,0:19:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  那棵树…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.68,0:19:54.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  也是啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.90,0:19:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还觉得奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.46,0:19:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能会接近我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.78,0:20:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婆婆是妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.30,0:20:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  你的名字如何称呼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.25,0:20:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.45,0:20:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.88,0:20:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要和我玩个游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.11,0:20:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是你赢了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.52,0:20:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么我都照做
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.45,0:20:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕是把我吃了都行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.03,0:20:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果我赢了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.81,0:20:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把你的名字…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.01,0:20:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.68,0:20:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输了游戏的我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.25,0:20:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在纸上写下了名字
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.29,0:20:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而那家伙最后还是没有道出姓名
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.72,0:20:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.70,0:20:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫玲子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.43,0:20:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个孩子的名字是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.22,0:20:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.20,0:20:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说  玲子已经不在这个世上了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.04,0:20:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  所以请收下那面镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.14,0:20:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.71,0:20:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承蒙关照了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.17,0:20:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子的孙子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.79,0:20:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺着这条小路走下去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.56,0:20:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以看到村庄了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.17,0:20:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.59,0:21:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那条路笔直走下去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.61,0:21:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再会了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.57,0:21:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像老婆婆把玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.04,0:21:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,错当成了妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.15,0:21:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子把老婆婆当作人一样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.97,0:21:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原以为交上了人类朋友的她
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.67,0:21:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是多么的开心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.72,0:21:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就觉得奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.94,0:21:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子没有因为这件事情而讨厌妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.05,0:21:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  快看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.67,0:21:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些花
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.80,0:21:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆婆的…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.42,0:21:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说玲子替她驱散了恶灵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.49,0:21:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是人类还这么乱来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.12,0:21:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.77,0:21:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子替这棵树驱散恶灵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.56,0:21:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是在知道老婆婆是妖怪之后
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.57,0:21:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.65,0:21:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子阿姨  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.85,0:21:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志  快来看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.56,0:21:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陌生的茶杯掉在这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.23,0:22:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是谁的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.41,0:22:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定还会一时冲动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.22,0:22:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代替那户人家来承受这份灾难
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.85,0:22:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.19,0:22:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的杯子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.49,0:22:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当重要的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.81,0:22:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擅自闯来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.47,0:22:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后擅自离去的家伙们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.95,0:22:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  只要有一次接触之后
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.56,0:22:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便未能被谁所察觉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.80,0:22:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但却是能一直温暖着内心的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.18,0:22:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最珍贵的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.55,0:24:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浮春之乡?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.73,0:24:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝非现世的东西  是梦幻之乡
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.83,0:24:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么那两人是怎样来这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.70,0:24:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是被那祭典上的乐声和鱿鱼烧所吸引过来的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.83,0:24:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要回去
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.34,0:24:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.90,0:24:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传达至友人…
