[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,1
Style: Default-1,方正隶变_GBK,40,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,15,15,10,1
Style: OP_jp,方正楷体_GBK,33,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,45,1
Style: OP_ch,方正楷体_GBK,36,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,5,1
Style: ED_jp,方正楷体_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,45,1
Style: ED_ch,方正楷体_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,5,1
Style: bt,方正楷体_GBK,55,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H32A8D0C8,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,33,&H00E8EEF4,&HF0000000,&H1E23384E,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,10,1
Style: zhu-1,方正隶变_GBK,33,&H00E8EEF4,&HF0000000,&H1E23384E,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,-90.00,1,2,2,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text



Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.48,0:01:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我与不可思议的少年櫂相遇了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.14,0:01:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他正被什么人追赶着
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.62,0:01:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要保护櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.76,0:01:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 追着櫂的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.35,0:01:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不只是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.38,0:01:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劝你不要接近那孩子为好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.29,0:01:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子 是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.08,0:02:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有着能够装作普通人也难以被发现的强大力量
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.54,0:02:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了驱除他而来的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.09,0:02:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱除...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.53,0:02:13.52,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人与妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.74,0:02:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.76,0:02:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.56,0:02:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 太好了 你没事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.06,0:02:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.99,0:02:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂说想去追你 都不听劝的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.48,0:02:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说有猫咪在 但他说你有危险
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.70,0:02:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是很努力地阻止他了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.45,0:02:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 我担心夏目啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.12,0:02:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.47,0:03:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.95,0:03:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.11,0:03:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.53,0:03:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没没
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.78,0:03:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.44,0:03:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂是妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.17,0:03:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是该被驱除的存在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.55,0:03:17.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么跟多轨说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.97,0:03:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是 不要再见櫂比较好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.21,0:03:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小鬼竟然是妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.41,0:03:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备怎么做?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.50,0:03:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正 是你的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.76,0:03:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后总是扯上关系然后变得麻烦起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.96,0:03:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真啰嗦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.38,0:03:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啰嗦啊 这可是在担心你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.23,0:03:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果先生你早点发觉的话 事情就不会变成这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.75,0:03:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 我这是闻惯了你那难闻的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.54,0:03:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼻子变得不灵敏了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.83,0:03:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难闻是什么意思!?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.78,0:03:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难闻就是难闻
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.98,0:03:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说难闻!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.83,0:03:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次我要买车了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.29,0:04:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很便宜 但是省油且结实
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.78,0:04:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想和你一起去看看海呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.07,0:04:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噗!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.43,0:04:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想载上所珍惜的人 横田VIVACE
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.88,0:04:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然这么笑人家 真是过分啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.86,0:04:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔 名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.07,0:04:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 亏这广告你们和好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.53,0:04:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为你会自己一个人在那边苦恼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.26,0:04:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是对不起呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.62,0:04:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非 你在拿我取乐?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.40,0:04:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.18,0:04:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好过分的人啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.52,0:04:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个恶魔!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.59,0:04:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 再说一次看我怎么收拾你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.41,0:04:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 柊 是什么时候...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.83,0:04:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不容你对主人暴言相向
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.23,0:04:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 柊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.75,0:04:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目是特别的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.34,0:04:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.84,0:04:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是有想问我的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.93,0:04:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么一定要驱除他呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.98,0:04:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前那幢洋房附近似乎会吸引妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.19,0:05:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一片有一口封印着曾经到处作乱的恶鬼们的井
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.19,0:05:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说是那些想从封印中解放的恶鬼们在呼唤妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.42,0:05:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说櫂是被恶鬼呼唤而来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.39,0:05:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小喽啰的妖怪是没办法解除封印的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.88,0:05:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是如果是拥有他那种程度的力量的话恐怕就...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.19,0:05:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那口井在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.59,0:05:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.77,0:05:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 櫂会来到洋房是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.53,0:05:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在找那口井啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.09,0:05:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人收到了要驱除他的委托
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.67,0:05:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别来妨碍我们 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.53,0:05:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁下了这种委托?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.29,0:05:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 又是和的场一门有关吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.79,0:05:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不能告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.52,0:05:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是我的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.34,0:05:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在连櫂会不会去解除封印还不知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.19,0:05:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只因为一点可能性竟然就要被驱除...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.56,0:05:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果等到事情发生 那就太晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.91,0:05:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.21,0:05:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我不会要你帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.35,0:05:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 不要来妨碍我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.95,0:06:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我的朋友 怎么可能坐视不理
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.56,0:06:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 是时候该做个决断了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.05,0:06:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说 重要的是人 还是妖怪?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.76,0:06:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是就算不去干涉妖怪的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.69,0:06:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也已经有了关心你注视你的人了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.23,0:06:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真是个麻烦的家伙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.35,0:06:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你还算是保镖的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.69,0:06:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就别让他插手危险的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.53,0:06:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 对你这种满不在乎的人来说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.78,0:06:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不会理解我们的心情的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.23,0:06:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满不在乎 吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.59,0:06:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连主人的心情都不清楚就乱说话 那只大丑猫
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.23,0:06:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是拒绝在夏目身边的工作就可以了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.24,0:06:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是这样说
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.41,0:07:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.68,0:07:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目同学
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.23,0:07:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是多轨啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.12,0:07:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎么了 表情比往常还要阴郁哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.38,0:07:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 就是有点...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.04,0:07:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂没和你在一起吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.77,0:07:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为櫂说没吃过曲奇 我烤了些带给他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.67,0:07:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个奇怪的孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.86,0:07:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在家里么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.69,0:07:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.85,0:07:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂他...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.93,0:07:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.43,0:07:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂他不在家哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.20,0:07:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.28,0:07:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 我有件事想拜托你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.58,0:07:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.43,0:07:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那幢洋房周围 似乎有口古井
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.85,0:07:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能帮忙调查下那口井的所在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.82,0:07:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.68,0:07:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过很急吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.82,0:07:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽可能快一点的好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.05,0:07:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些饼干就由我来交给櫂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.82,0:07:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.08,0:07:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我家的古文书上或许会有记载
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.71,0:08:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去查下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.08,0:08:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.99,0:08:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我跟櫂问好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.56,0:08:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后也要跟我好好说说缘由哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.70,0:08:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.17,0:08:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.80,0:08:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.76,0:08:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.75,0:08:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼 你有看到櫂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.15,0:08:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是前阵子那孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.21,0:08:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我看到他往那边去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.55,0:08:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.09,0:08:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 喂 找人的话要我帮忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.12,0:08:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.95,0:08:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.43,0:08:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个不值得交的朋友吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.54,0:08:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔 喵喵先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.75,0:08:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得只要都由自己承担了 就不会给人添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.16,0:08:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真是个笨蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.05,0:09:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂是来找井的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.65,0:09:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 名取先生?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.66,0:09:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 也有可能是櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.74,0:09:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.61,0:09:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.47,0:09:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.10,0:09:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.86,0:09:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 原来是先生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.71,0:09:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「什么啊」是什么意思!?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.20,0:09:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是我这保镖这么称职地过来保护你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.73,0:09:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.25,0:09:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好香的味道呢 那边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.23,0:09:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么保镖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.19,0:09:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个房间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.64,0:09:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动 动不了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.99,0:10:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.92,0:10:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.52,0:10:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.82,0:10:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂...是妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.09,0:10:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目你 讨厌妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.92,0:10:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢櫂哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.86,0:10:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是那个做作男做的陷阱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.46,0:11:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂是在找井吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.20,0:11:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.25,0:11:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是想要救被关着的同伴们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.38,0:11:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果看到夏目进来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.16,0:11:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了真好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.78,0:11:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.72,0:11:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.10,0:11:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 盯着我的那个驱妖人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.91,0:11:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然让夏目身处危险
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.45,0:11:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可原谅 那个可恶的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.75,0:11:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里还有他的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.30,0:11:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要追着这味道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.78,0:11:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.33,0:11:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.52,0:11:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种家伙 我去收拾
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.92,0:11:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.23,0:11:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果正面交锋的话 名取可没胜算
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.45,0:11:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候该做个决断了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.40,0:11:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说 重要的是人 还是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.72,0:11:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.64,0:11:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.30,0:12:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陷阱...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.77,0:12:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被破了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.37,0:12:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比预想还要强大的力量啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.74,0:12:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.55,0:12:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.68,0:12:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还使役着妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.83,0:12:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙要让人不爽到什么程度才甘心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.17,0:12:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.64,0:12:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.31,0:12:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要贸然动手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.77,0:12:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 逃也没用
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.35,0:12:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊 停下!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.16,0:12:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有保护主人你的义务
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.40,0:12:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算逃走也会马上被追上的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.10,0:12:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到咯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.40,0:12:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了啊 你这怪物!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.88,0:13:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.90,0:13:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.96,0:13:05.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.77,0:13:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我没能阻止櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.26,0:13:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂现在正追着你 快逃远一点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.55,0:13:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里才危险 快点回去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.98,0:13:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要再和櫂谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.97,0:13:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谈一谈 让他住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.92,0:13:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.21,0:13:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪一边我都无法选择
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.83,0:13:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂和名取先生 对我来说都很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.79,0:13:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道櫂的真正身份了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.84,0:13:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.27,0:13:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是住在山里的水神一类
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.08,0:13:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦对他的贡品有所拖延就会隔断水源
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.00,0:13:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等人们再来进贡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.66,0:13:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是现在这种习俗也被人们所遗忘
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.43,0:13:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寂寞不已的他倾听着世间的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.28,0:13:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果听到了被封印在古井中的恶鬼们的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.54,0:13:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会想要解开封印来增加伙伴而下山
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.98,0:13:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.92,0:14:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此他才会趁虚进入人类社会的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.33,0:14:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是在为找井混在人类之间的过程中
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.90,0:14:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他倒变得快乐起来 渐渐再听不见恶鬼们的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.90,0:14:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且 遇到了你还有多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.18,0:14:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 我会收手的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.89,0:14:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.56,0:14:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过古井我还是要找到再次封印的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.90,0:14:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让恶鬼们连声音都无法传出
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.58,0:14:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.69,0:14:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是这样的话 你能帮忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.21,0:14:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.64,0:14:33.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.87,0:14:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.10,0:14:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.72,0:14:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会和驱妖人在一起?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.91,0:14:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.89,0:14:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.53,0:14:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.76,0:14:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂 我有重要的事要告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.55,0:14:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来夏目也是这家伙的同伴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.72,0:14:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.17,0:14:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是骗我的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.81,0:14:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.86,0:15:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂 听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.82,0:15:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有这么妨碍到你们的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.46,0:15:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要对我说让我回到山上不就好了!?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.30,0:15:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要夏目这么希望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.31,0:15:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这么做也无所谓啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.59,0:15:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了 我受够人类了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.98,0:15:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.80,0:15:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.55,0:15:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是发呆的时候吗 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.04,0:15:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要怎么做 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.56,0:15:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.26,0:15:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.25,0:15:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.89,0:15:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被关在棺材里的櫂不是因为害怕而哭的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.76,0:15:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为被当作是要被驱除的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.52,0:15:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被认为不应该在这里所以悲伤而哭的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.04,0:15:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱哭的神在山上一直都是独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.70,0:15:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好不容易才找到他想留下的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.01,0:16:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.40,0:16:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跑哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.86,0:16:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我把话好好说完
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.73,0:16:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.49,0:16:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.90,0:16:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,井在哪里?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.94,0:16:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.01,0:16:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.02,0:16:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是古井里的恶鬼们的同伴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.82,0:16:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会追来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.72,0:16:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 带我去井的所在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.28,0:16:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边 那口古井似乎是在洋房北边的洼地
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.70,0:16:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.97,0:16:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是田沼同学找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.62,0:16:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.86,0:16:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半途遇到的 跟他说了下缘由就帮忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.76,0:16:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然其实他说要对你保密的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.27,0:16:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.97,0:16:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点 不要乱来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.82,0:17:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是在这种地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.40,0:17:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉我来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.50,0:17:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就放你们出来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.36,0:17:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.73,0:17:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.95,0:17:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以解除封印
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.83,0:17:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先好好听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.55,0:17:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要过来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.02,0:17:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想看到你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.81,0:17:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 把碍事的人解决掉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.89,0:17:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我回山上去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.50,0:17:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎很美味啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.33,0:17:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.82,0:17:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救了我们非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.04,0:17:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为谢礼 看我们把你吃掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.19,0:18:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你往哪儿跑
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.84,0:18:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.56,0:18:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.55,0:18:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.01,0:19:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是那个夏目铃子的...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.28,0:19:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 就当作是骗了我的报复
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.16,0:19:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这个藏起来让你困扰吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.93,0:19:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.30,0:19:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 还是不想让夏目困扰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.48,0:19:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我醒来的时候 櫂已经不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.05,0:19:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫂 原来是妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.40,0:19:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.57,0:19:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子 又变成独自一人了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.88,0:19:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生说是在山上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.65,0:20:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要查查是哪里的山呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.79,0:20:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.93,0:20:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.55,0:20:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去见他吧 去见櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.98,0:20:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.67,0:20:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你那是第2个了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.68,0:20:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 要遵守规则啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.97,0:20:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这世界就是弱肉强食啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.76,0:20:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不懂你什么意思!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.52,0:20:25.54,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没看过礼仪指南吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.54,0:20:27.27,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊对啊 回去好好看看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.11,0:20:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是一个人躲在一边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.27,0:20:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个麻烦的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.94,0:20:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.78,0:20:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过还真是个不厌烦的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.47,0:20:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.77,0:20:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道铃子死后 我还以为友人帐会交给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.56,0:20:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为没想到会有人收下她的遗物
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.98,0:20:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 或许这样也好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.33,0:20:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.89,0:20:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你陪在我身边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.25,0:20:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白痴 别说肉麻话啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.49,0:20:59.06,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来来 新菜做好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.09,0:21:02.79,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 看起来好好吃 谢谢 我们开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.27,0:21:05.31,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 要遵守规则啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.70,0:21:25.84,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八原双妖就此加入开吃咯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.94,0:21:30.77,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.64,0:21:33.61,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果就这么吃下去变胖了怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.03,0:21:37.71,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果汁 笹田帮忙递下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.91,0:21:38.43,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.64,0:21:39.57,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那边 嗯 还有那边的煎蛋卷
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.39,0:21:42.26,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是我做的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.28,0:21:42.95,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.24,0:21:44.29,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才不是有吃到么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.48,0:21:45.32,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你们猜拳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.51,0:21:47.24,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么还要决胜负了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.92,0:21:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我也...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.00,0:21:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一起吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.40,0:21:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.60,0:21:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要吃我要吃
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.80,0:21:12.92,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要吃 我要吃
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.54,0:21:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人 妖怪 不是该拘泥于这些区分的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.87,0:21:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正该明白的 是对自己来说究竟重不重要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.80,0:21:23.21,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给櫂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.76,0:21:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将那一瞬间的心意 幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.03,0:21:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由衷地 直接地 毫不犹豫去感受才是最好的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.27,0:21:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.64,0:21:34.26,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 田沼同学 这个很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.26,0:21:35.11,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.11,0:21:36.00,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.46,0:21:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志 风铃的垂条 你原本没弄上去对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.66,0:21:43.77,zhu-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(1270,350)}{\fs26}{\fn@方正隶变_GBK}译注:风铃下的垂条如果不挂一般是不会出声音的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.77,0:21:45.17,Default-1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再给我再给我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.50,0:21:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.30,0:21:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子婶婶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.72,0:21:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好听的音色呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.94,0:21:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.96,0:21:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 少しだけ大人の色に染まる指先
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 指尖稍露成年的沧桑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 照れくさそうに そっと隠して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 你就害羞得将它悄悄收起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 頬杖ついた君 見つめてる視線の先に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 手托下巴的你将视线投向
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 小さな蕾が ゆらゆら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 那随风轻曳的小小花蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} ねぇ 僕なんて いまも迷いばかりで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 喂 现在的我仍迷茫依旧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} あの日贈った言葉 今さら思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 这才回想起 那日你的临别赠言
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「君色に未来染めて...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「将我的未来染成你的颜色...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ 聞いていてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 听我倾诉好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ わがままいいですか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 让我任性好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手に入れた途端に消えてしまいそう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}拥有的瞬间仿佛就会消散
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}言葉をくれませんか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不说点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あなたがいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}因为有你在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}それだけで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう世界が変わってしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我的世界就会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}モノトーンの景色が ほら 鮮やかに映る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}映入眼眸的单调景色也会光鲜亮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}いつのまにか 離れていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不知何时却已离开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手を繋いで歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}牵着手 向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}上手く愛せているかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}能够好好去爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あの空に聞いてみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}天空也许会回答
