[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.74,0:01:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在铃子的遗物里翻来翻去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.93,0:01:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.48,0:01:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.21,0:01:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.85,0:01:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「不知不觉」?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.97,0:01:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙还是一如既往地让人费解啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.30,0:01:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粘到了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.28,0:01:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.14,0:01:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西瓜子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.03,0:02:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴角边上 两粒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.64,0:02:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用介意 不过是「不知不觉」而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.35,0:02:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不懂你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.37,0:02:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次将名字归还给妖怪们时
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.52,0:02:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对铃子的回忆也日渐增强
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.43,0:02:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢地汇成思念流入我的体内的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.60,0:02:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子外婆的点点滴滴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.18,0:02:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从图书馆借的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.29,0:02:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计是忘了还回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.60,0:02:36.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车票?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.30,0:02:41.30,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心色的车票
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.37,0:02:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.37,0:02:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说啊 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.32,0:02:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得谁错了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.40,0:02:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.97,0:02:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙说狐狸乌冬面要先吃狐狸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.97,0:03:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,45)}{\fs23}译注:狐狸乌冬面即浇了油炸豆腐皮和葱花的清乌冬面\N因炸好的豆腐皮颜色很像狐狸皮而得名 也有一说是因油炸豆腐皮为狐狸的最爱
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.31,0:02:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能相信么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.76,0:02:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然得先吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.98,0:03:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么蠢话 狐狸要浸在汤汁里到最后吃才好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.11,0:03:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说是吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.45,0:03:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 不能让狐狸的甜味被汤汁冲淡 直接吃才好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.88,0:03:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.14,0:03:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我倒觉得哪一种都行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.47,0:03:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会行!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.61,0:03:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狐狸要最后吃!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.78,0:03:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狐狸要最先吃!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.97,0:03:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说...你们确定那个是叫「狐狸」么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.00,0:03:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.34,0:03:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事完全无关紧要吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.61,0:03:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.48,0:03:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.41,0:03:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最先
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.55,0:03:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.89,0:03:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝交了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.82,0:03:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 正合我意
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.31,0:03:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.95,0:03:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.97,0:03:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好无聊的争吵啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.01,0:03:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 这是你掉的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.94,0:03:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.46,0:03:47.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是以前的车票吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.03,0:03:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.94,0:03:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.75,0:03:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和夏目你有什么联系呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.65,0:03:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似有隐情嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.61,0:03:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是你想的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.42,0:04:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我早上上学时在路上捡到的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.13,0:04:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的谎撒得真烂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.06,0:04:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了没什么的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.32,0:04:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待会再慢慢听你解释吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.09,0:04:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏～目～君～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.67,0:04:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想逃跑也是没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.23,0:04:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.10,0:04:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.39,0:04:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有哪儿 当然是回家咯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.52,0:04:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是要去车票上的那个车站吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.95,0:04:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.13,0:04:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.85,0:04:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车站是在哪儿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.47,0:04:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才没看仔细 想不起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.73,0:04:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很近吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.94,0:04:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田...你为什么这么积极...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.68,0:04:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶...那...那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.95,0:04:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 因为在上次的试胆大会上我真的很想见到他
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.96,0:04:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.72,0:04:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么见到谁啊 真讨厌 当然是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.65,0:04:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 巴士来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.20,0:04:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们坐上去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.53,0:04:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 掉东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.44,0:04:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.15,0:05:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掉什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.76,0:05:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是什么都没有嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.63,0:05:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.97,0:05:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.12,0:05:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.19,0:05:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.89,0:05:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.59,0:05:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.87,0:05:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开走了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.78,0:05:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底想说我掉了什...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.27,0:05:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.09,0:05:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于来了 慢死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.73,0:05:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.58,0:05:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志 美雪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.00,0:05:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿已经被废弃了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.65,0:06:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 听说这条线路很早前就停运了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.64,0:06:06.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是荒凉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.73,0:06:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾沼站是在对面吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.90,0:06:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但铃子她为什么...喵
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.09,0:06:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.28,0:06:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么热还睡得着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.07,0:06:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.20,0:06:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.37,0:06:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你终于来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.55,0:06:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...我是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.28,0:06:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别搞错了 这家伙才不是铃子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.88,0:06:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.13,0:06:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是铃子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.53,0:06:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.53,0:06:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是铃子啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.26,0:06:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 你快说点什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.23,0:06:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在说什么都没用了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.48,0:07:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是什么坏家伙 你就陪他玩会儿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.18,0:07:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.60,0:07:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.23,0:07:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.82,0:07:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 铃子已经死了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.50,0:07:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能明白就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.38,0:07:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 他是她的孙子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.12,0:07:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以味道相似也没什么好奇怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.80,0:07:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不用再闻了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.16,0:07:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛绒怪 你说你在等铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.04,0:07:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和她有过什么约定么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.59,0:07:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 她说要陪我一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.50,0:07:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.56,0:07:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.41,0:07:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾沼么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.12,0:07:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子说过要陪你一起去雾沼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.75,0:07:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 雾沼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.52,0:07:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.67,0:07:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 又难看又臭 不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.38,0:08:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是铃子说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.31,0:08:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 那么就...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.37,0:08:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让这家伙来说明 看来是有点困难
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.92,0:08:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定友人帐上有他的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.92,0:08:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把名字还给他的话也许能让他回忆起什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.89,0:08:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.03,0:08:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字是?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.91,0:08:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.96,0:08:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫三斗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.60,0:08:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三斗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.22,0:08:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「守护吾者 显现汝名」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.07,0:08:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...吵架了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.23,0:08:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 虽然生气的只有三棱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.35,0:08:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢那个叫做三棱的妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.09,0:08:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢三棱了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.30,0:08:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是三棱却说讨厌我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.80,0:09:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说再也不想见到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.08,0:09:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了什么错事么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.17,0:09:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有印象了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.38,0:09:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那三棱又是为了什么而生你的气呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.98,0:09:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差不多能了解三棱为什么会生你的气了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.41,0:09:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.83,0:09:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱现在在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.98,0:09:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾沼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.53,0:09:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾沼?下一站么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.28,0:09:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.67,0:09:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 那我陪你一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.35,0:09:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.22,0:09:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但今天天已经晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.31,0:09:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天你就在这儿等我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.10,0:09:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子 太谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.01,0:09:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.96,0:09:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 三斗 真是的...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.47,0:10:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 终究还是没能遵守约定么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.10,0:10:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子一定有她来不了的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.45,0:10:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算去么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.27,0:10:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对方可能已经没在等你了哟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.34,0:10:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去看看的话怎么知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.08,0:10:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.46,0:10:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子没有完成的约定
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.36,0:10:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想替她完成
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.29,0:10:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但今天天色也晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.16,0:10:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天放学后我会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.01,0:10:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.34,0:10:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 还是现在就动身吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.79,0:10:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.90,0:10:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么轻易就答应别人了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.69,0:10:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾沼那地方可是坐巴士都到不了的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.60,0:10:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,步行的话你知道要花多少时间么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.21,0:11:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走到那里 太阳肯定都落山了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.87,0:11:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是白说了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.77,0:11:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 三斗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.40,0:11:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算铃子没来 你不会自己去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.51,0:11:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么还要一直等着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.28,0:11:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 因为我们说好了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.35,0:11:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我傻了竟然问你这种问题
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.82,0:11:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些变冷了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.30,0:11:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是山风刮过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.45,0:11:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 三斗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.36,0:12:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.64,0:12:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 说这家伙「可爱」好还是「可恨」好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.53,0:12:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三斗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.68,0:12:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.79,0:12:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到三棱后你准备说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.55,0:12:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 没想过么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.84,0:12:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要和好的话 必须得说点什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.93,0:12:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.82,0:12:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不见面比较好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.42,0:12:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定见了面反而更麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.72,0:12:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.97,0:12:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三斗 到达前你好好想想要说些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.48,0:12:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了...给
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.74,0:12:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.74,0:12:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.96,0:12:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地鸣么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.96,0:12:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,45)}{\fs23}译注:地震前兆 伴随地震而生的地鸣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.36,0:12:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怨念
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.92,0:13:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怨念?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.40,0:13:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三斗!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.64,0:13:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕 不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.31,0:13:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.11,0:13:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.02,0:13:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓稳了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.26,0:13:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 刚刚那个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.11,0:13:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是冲着三斗来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.76,0:13:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.89,0:13:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱看来被地灵给附身了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.94,0:13:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地灵?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.05,0:13:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地灵最喜欢愤怒与憎恨
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.65,0:13:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三～棱～～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.41,0:13:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱竟然对三斗这么...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.29,0:13:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是别见面比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.41,0:14:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.44,0:14:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.02,0:14:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.16,0:14:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会发生什么我可不管
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.79,0:14:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上吧 猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.74,0:14:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是傻得不要命
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.56,0:14:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷啊 好像都已经不是夏天了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.93,0:14:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像是山风
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.84,0:14:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为怨念的关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.31,0:14:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱 出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.95,0:14:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱 我有话对你说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.58,0:14:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三斗 三棱长什么模样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.97,0:14:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...小小的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.25,0:15:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小小的是... 大概多大?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.00,0:15:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么小么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.47,0:15:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么大?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.17,0:15:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在可不是开玩笑的时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.78,0:15:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来了 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.12,0:15:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.26,0:15:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我现出真身来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.32,0:15:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲶...鲶鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.16,0:16:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.92,0:16:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是三棱? 大得也太离谱了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.02,0:16:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.47,0:16:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备说服他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.15,0:16:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我是谁啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.49,0:16:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.03,0:16:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙就是夏木铃子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.56,0:16:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来得正好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.40,0:16:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.34,0:16:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来友人帐在那里面啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.85,0:16:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这笨蛋想干什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.13,0:16:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是铃子的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.19,0:16:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我 蠢货
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.12,0:17:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱 三棱是我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.08,0:17:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是三斗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.35,0:17:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我不好 所以拜托你快醒醒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.05,0:17:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变回原来的三棱吧 求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.16,0:17:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三斗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.39,0:17:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把友人帐交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.44,0:17:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不交
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.79,0:17:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.07,0:17:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.00,0:17:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.71,0:17:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.00,0:17:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.07,0:17:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.55,0:17:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.22,0:18:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有点对不住 不过已经和地灵一起消失在沼泽底了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.30,0:18:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三斗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.73,0:18:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 到底什么事嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.22,0:18:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 三斗!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.95,0:18:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.74,0:18:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.73,0:18:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你这个笨蛋想干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.76,0:18:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.46,0:18:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.08,0:18:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.56,0:18:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让你住手啊 好恶心 快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.68,0:18:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.77,0:18:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.57,0:18:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为铃子吵的架?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.26,0:18:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呐 就是那个夏目铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.83,0:18:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.30,0:18:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是名字
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.56,0:18:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个笨蛋把自己重要的名字交给了铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.08,0:18:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才玩完的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.07,0:18:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为妖怪你难道没有一点自尊么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.44,0:18:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个大笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.71,0:18:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本就不想再看到你这张脸了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.51,0:18:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还乐呵呵地厚着脸皮出现
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.73,0:18:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个呆子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.11,0:18:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.69,0:19:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.74,0:19:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打你踢你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.78,0:19:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用说的这么过分吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.79,0:19:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为三斗他喜欢你 所以一直在烦恼着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.43,0:19:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是他笨的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.11,0:19:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是想道歉的话就快点过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.24,0:19:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是这么悠悠闲闲的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.32,0:19:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭家伙 臭家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.79,0:19:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.14,0:19:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 三棱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.48,0:19:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目你仔细看看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.04,0:19:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有在听吗 你这个毛绒怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.95,0:19:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在和你说话呢 和你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.03,0:19:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.70,0:19:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经和好如初了 这两个家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.29,0:19:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三棱 我们回山里去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.00,0:19:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不说我也要回去 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.34,0:19:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 真的太感谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.99,0:19:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 不许向人类低头
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.06,0:19:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是人家都把名字还给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.45,0:19:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.80,0:19:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了不许低头的 你这
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.06,0:19:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢～货～～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.13,0:20:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 又是「不知不觉」?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.72,0:20:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把它放回原位
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.34,0:20:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过铃子没能守约是因为有特殊原因的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.55,0:20:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太偏袒她了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.45,0:20:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.19,0:20:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是稀里糊涂就忘记了罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.56,0:20:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子就是那种人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.96,0:20:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么说也太过分了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.98,0:20:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这本书怎么解释呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.91,0:20:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借来后不就一直没还么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.50,0:20:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.60,0:20:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.37,0:20:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 看来她忘了不少啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.31,0:20:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来有不少「特殊原因」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.27,0:20:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子外婆～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.55,0:20:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.46,0:20:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早...上好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.55,0:20:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看他们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.55,0:20:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.21,0:20:55.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经和好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.86,0:20:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.68,0:21:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天那个算什么啊 真是搞不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.45,0:21:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就叫做好朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.17,0:21:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 昨天怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.87,0:21:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我想起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.20,0:21:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 这个稍微帮我拿一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.63,0:21:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.53,0:21:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.07,0:21:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.33,0:21:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天妇罗面里的炸虾 你是先吃还是后吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.94,0:21:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一种
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.88,0:21:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事随便哪种都好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.16,0:21:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.06,0:21:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.78,0:21:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.24,0:21:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你好像很为难嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.98,0:23:50.60,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,540)}水底之燕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.73,0:23:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉在大坝底下的村子露出了真容
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.86,0:23:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居住在那里的妖怪们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.49,0:23:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了拿回名字而找到我这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.15,0:23:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 别缠着夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.66,0:23:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个想要见到的人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.40,0:23:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段时间就承蒙您关照了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.82,0:23:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要见的...人么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.02,0:22:12.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.02,0:22:12.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.96,0:22:19.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.96,0:22:19.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.92,0:22:26.39,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.92,0:22:26.39,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.39,0:22:33.32,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.39,0:22:33.32,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.08,0:22:44.37,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.08,0:22:44.37,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.37,0:22:48.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.37,0:22:48.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.76,0:22:58.22,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.76,0:22:58.22,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.22,0:23:05.86,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.22,0:23:05.86,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.86,0:23:12.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.86,0:23:12.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.92,0:23:20.28,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.92,0:23:20.28,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.28,0:23:28.00,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.28,0:23:28.00,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
