[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.26,0:02:30.26,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1}隐藏于库中之物
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.89,0:24:15.94,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1\pos(228,296)}人非人
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}なくした温もりを一つ一つ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色取り取りの君のカケラは　笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出の作り方も　まるでうまくならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れに　タダ身を任せて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこに行けばいい　この闇の先でまだ
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな　君のカケラ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}なくした温もりを一つ一つ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色取り取りの君のカケラは　笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出の作り方も　まるでうまくならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れに　タダ身を任せて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこに行けばいい　この闇の先でまだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな　君のカケラ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.91,0:01:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然就下雨了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.28,0:01:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  在那边的屋檐下避避雨吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.62,0:01:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说起来  这宅子真是气派啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.92,0:01:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是所谓的名门望族吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.52,0:01:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.65,0:01:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  我并不想靠近这种有着妖怪气息的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.41,0:02:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.11,0:02:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才听到里面传出了奇怪的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.76,0:02:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.66,0:02:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.39,0:02:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.12,0:02:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了  这里果然有妖怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.28,0:02:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  这不是夏目和田沼吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.93,0:02:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.32,0:02:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有猫咪老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.41,0:02:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里原来是多轨的家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.54,0:02:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是间大宅子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.32,0:02:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是又旧又难清扫呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.06,0:02:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  为什么喵咪老师会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.49,0:02:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然就下雨了  我便到外面看下情况
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.95,0:02:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛茸茸毛茸茸的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.07,0:02:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等反应过来的时候就已经把它抱在怀里了…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.94,0:02:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.07,0:02:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.01,0:03:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姑娘你究竟什么时候才能学会把握一下分寸
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.48,0:03:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别以为用这小小的羊羹就能让我原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.78,0:03:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来我把老师的惨叫听成了妖怪的叫声啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.49,0:03:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以吗？  帮我整理仓库
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.05,0:03:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  这算是让我们避雨的谢礼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.51,0:03:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.63,0:03:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  真是帮了大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.07,0:03:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师  有感到什么妖怪的气息吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.15,0:03:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许因为是古宅  这里有着很多种妖怪的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.04,0:03:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但暂且没有什么特别的妖气
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.20,0:03:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.00,0:03:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  吃完羊羹就回去喽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.78,0:03:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.80,0:03:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木…木…木偶…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.29,0:04:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起呢  那个木偶是用来辟邪的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.99,0:04:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候也很怕那个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.76,0:04:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何止辟邪…小偷看见也会跑的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.33,0:04:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来多轨家曾经是做阴阳师的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.77,0:04:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那都是很久以前的事情了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.94,0:04:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖父虽然看不见  但一直做着一些关于妖怪的研究
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.79,0:04:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我小时候  在这个仓库里教了我很多东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.12,0:04:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是父母对这些都很反感
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.55,0:04:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有我经常来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.59,0:05:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.75,0:05:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是河童吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.74,0:05:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然想去了解妖怪  真是个怪人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.54,0:05:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算能看见妖怪  也不会有什么好事…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.43,0:05:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.42,0:05:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开个窗户要花多久啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.70,0:05:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.86,0:05:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓死我了  是和服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.78,0:05:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一时还以为有谁站在那里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.88,0:05:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那个啊  抱歉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.75,0:05:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是用来辟邪的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.48,0:06:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个怪人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.88,0:06:18.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干完了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.61,0:06:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.19,0:06:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉呢  没想到整理仓库居然会这样费力
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.28,0:06:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么大不了的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.87,0:06:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵  请你们吃炒面吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.39,0:06:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为帮我整理了仓库的谢礼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.15,0:06:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太感谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.41,0:06:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.68,0:06:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨  这里用来辟邪的和服你收起了一件吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.43,0:06:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.78,0:06:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和刚才一样一直是两件啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.16,0:06:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.79,0:06:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那两个人稍微有些像呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.95,0:07:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确呢  关系超好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.55,0:07:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音也有些像
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.84,0:07:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.42,0:07:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.24,0:07:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…我去上个厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.45,0:07:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然  是我记错了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.23,0:07:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是什么大不了的事情  犯不着让他们担心…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.10,0:07:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混账
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.57,0:07:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.11,0:08:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  视线对上了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.77,0:08:05.62,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.19,0:08:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,视线对上了…视线对上了…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.92,0:08:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,视线对上了…视线对上了…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.72,0:08:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.32,0:08:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没见过的小鬼呢  你能看见妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.39,0:08:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀  这真是有趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.64,0:08:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是那个和服妖怪的同伙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.76,0:08:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是时隔许久过来玩玩而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.03,0:08:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慎一郎在世的时候我经常来这里玩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.70,0:08:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慎一郎？莫非是多轨的爷爷吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.65,0:08:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他应该看不见妖怪才对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.85,0:08:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是看不见  直至最后都是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.98,0:08:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个和服妖怪究竟是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.08,0:08:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把倒挂着的那幅画弄下来了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.01,0:08:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如同颠倒的佛像  颠倒摆放的东西是不能随意触碰的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.47,0:08:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一种叫做「逆向封印」的法术
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.82,0:09:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慎一郎曾一边对照着资料一边自己做出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.35,0:09:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然他本人并不知道  但他实际上成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.92,0:09:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将这里的一个恶灵成功地封印住了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.94,0:09:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一个古老的人偶妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.83,0:09:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被封印的那一瞬它的身体变得四分五裂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.88,0:09:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部散落在这个宅邸里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.60,0:09:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被封印在仓库里的是它的身体和左手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.43,0:09:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它为了收集自己七零八落的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.24,0:09:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这宅邸里四处寻找
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.59,0:09:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果它夺回了身体的所有部位
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.45,0:09:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么事情就会变得很麻烦的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.99,0:09:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来在你的正下方正好藏着它的右脚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.62,0:09:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.35,0:09:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？这个气味？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.41,0:10:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.55,0:10:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屋底下有什么奇怪的东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.39,0:10:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和服的妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.88,0:10:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是被祖父封印的？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.98,0:10:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.12,0:10:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  慎一郎的孙女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.66,0:10:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了  夏目  有什么东西在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.59,0:10:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是告诉我有关和服妖怪的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.20,0:10:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有妖怪在吗  就在那？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.18,0:11:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说  慎一郎多少有点资质但是看不到自己
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.45,0:11:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.21,0:11:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.76,0:11:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有听见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.26,0:11:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚二楼…似乎有东西在动
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.42,0:11:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.10,0:11:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.63,0:11:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目他…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.88,0:11:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所作所为看起来真的很奇怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.61,0:11:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.47,0:11:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是知道实情的话就明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.24,0:11:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目现在是为了保护我们还有这个家而在努力
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.08,0:11:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪  到底在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.75,0:11:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是老样子嘛  有这么多采光微妙的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.43,0:11:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在别人肩上闹腾了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.16,0:11:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会趁着慎一郎先生看不见你们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.44,0:11:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就肆无忌惮的欺负他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.99,0:11:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个你说呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.00,0:11:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.33,0:12:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让他是真的什么都看不到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.88,0:12:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  那个窗户
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.29,0:12:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慎一郎从很小的时候开始
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.46,0:12:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一直看画着妖怪的画轴和记载了妖怪信息的书籍
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.03,0:12:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如同是在津津有味地读着图书一般
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.41,0:12:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.10,0:12:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕就一次也好  真想看看
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.11,0:12:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明明就在他身边
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.22,0:12:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却未能觉察到的样子真是太好玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.99,0:12:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真怀念
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.34,0:12:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.50,0:12:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.67,0:12:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能上去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.71,0:12:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.02,0:12:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  不过这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.91,0:12:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实有什么东西在
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.15,0:13:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在右边深处
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.55,0:13:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不妙  那家伙也来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.30,0:13:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.38,0:13:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.96,0:13:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  突然把你们拉下来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.86,0:13:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  多亏了多轨  得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.90,0:13:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.71,0:13:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.71,0:13:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在想都这么久了  又从这屋子里传出了奇妙的妖气
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.51,0:14:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是封印被打破了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.15,0:14:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.18,0:14:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为慎一郎回来了又要做些什么怪事了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.81,0:14:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.78,0:14:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慎一郎不是早就辞世了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.67,0:14:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类是不可能随便就复活的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.07,0:14:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是吗  真无聊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.12,0:14:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.28,0:14:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对不对  慎一郎他还在呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.50,0:14:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦  这是叫做孙女的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.74,0:14:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就是那个在慎一郎葬礼的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.41,0:14:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直哭哭啼啼的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.10,0:14:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  对了哦  真是无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.37,0:14:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  在那边的妖怪们都是什么样的妖怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.66,0:14:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是认识多轨爷爷的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.31,0:14:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且看来他们相当喜欢你爷爷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.62,0:14:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛  好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.59,0:14:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少乱说  明明他都从来没有见过我们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.98,0:15:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慎一郎那家伙只不过是我们的玩具而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.62,0:15:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子  你能看到我们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.58,0:15:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  真少见呢  和慎一郎完全不一样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.36,0:15:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么人类的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.06,0:15:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就看在这一面之缘上奉劝你一句
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.95,0:15:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据墙垣上的妖怪们所述
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.10,0:15:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那穿着和服的妖怪叫做神乐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.95,0:15:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经取回了双脚和左手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.23,0:15:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右手已折断腐朽掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.31,0:15:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来最后就只剩下头了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.89,0:15:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个就在后院里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.01,0:15:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.71,0:15:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往这边
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.47,0:15:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.75,0:15:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.11,0:15:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为你又要说在这里等着
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.91,0:15:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者让我一个人先回去之类的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.98,0:15:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有像这样听我说话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.15,0:15:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还愿意留下来陪我的伙伴…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.59,0:16:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.69,0:16:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.66,0:16:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.72,0:16:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.76,0:16:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是被妖怪给抓走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.21,0:16:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不见的家伙怎样才能找到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.72,0:16:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  有阵
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.95,0:16:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个阵…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.88,0:16:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是进入那个圈里的妖怪能显形的对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.71,0:16:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.53,0:16:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果使用那个的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.75,0:16:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许能够求助同夏目谈话的那些妖怪们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.31,0:16:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.52,0:16:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是个人类  竟然能看到我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.66,0:16:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来很喜欢你的爷爷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.39,0:16:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你在哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.55,0:16:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.74,0:16:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胖太  那是我要说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.33,0:17:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看他这么晚还没回家就赶回来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.55,0:17:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 夏目怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.47,0:17:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪大人  拜托你们帮帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.32,0:17:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请告诉我夏目到底去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.56,0:17:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.03,0:17:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.58,0:17:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求…求求你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.53,0:17:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.03,0:17:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胖太  它赶来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.50,0:17:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去后庭看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.05,0:17:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.30,0:17:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不到阵里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.75,0:17:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有那样做的义务
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.49,0:17:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同人类惹上关系的都没什么好下场
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.21,0:17:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.13,0:17:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子  再不起来你的右手就要被砍掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.53,0:18:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.73,0:18:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后院  快看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.38,0:18:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅单手拔不出那东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.31,0:18:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.43,0:18:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会想要吸收你的妖力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.57,0:18:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取下你的手臂据为己用
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.87,0:18:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少对我的甜点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.10,0:18:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.34,0:18:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.44,0:18:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.15,0:18:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这屋子搞什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.23,0:18:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处都是不着调的结界
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.27,0:18:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.82,0:18:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是那个叫慎一郎的家伙边学边弄的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.01,0:18:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我就讨厌那些半吊子家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.77,0:18:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.79,0:19:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险  别过来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.27,0:19:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你往哪跑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.85,0:19:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.15,0:19:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀  真是看不下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.46,0:19:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.18,0:19:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  就这样抓稳它
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.36,0:19:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  等等…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.93,0:19:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.35,0:19:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近慎一郎他都不读书了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.00,0:19:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不画些奇怪的画了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.70,0:19:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是染上什么疾病了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.45,0:19:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.74,0:19:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  那个叫做医生的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.73,0:19:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用根绳子一样的东西接到耳朵上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.38,0:19:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,触碰慎一郎的身体作治疗呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.41,0:19:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢噢  做得真像呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.62,0:19:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种东西能治好他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.63,0:20:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类都办得到的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.59,0:20:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不可能不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.54,0:20:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点康复吧  慎一郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.65,0:20:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是脆弱的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.83,0:20:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点康复
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.14,0:20:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点康复吧  慎一郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.14,0:20:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去太无聊了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.83,0:20:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你说想要见到我们的么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.98,0:20:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点康复吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.23,0:20:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点康复
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.84,0:20:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快些康复
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.62,0:20:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷  爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.98,0:20:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁在哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.92,0:20:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在哭
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.79,0:20:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和小多轨一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.56,0:20:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.44,0:20:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  终于醒过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.80,0:20:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.28,0:20:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神乐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.21,0:20:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我咬着它把它扔到远处去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.65,0:20:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.66,0:20:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经要走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.30,0:20:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.67,0:20:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会再来这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.71,0:20:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被卷进这麻烦事里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.26,0:21:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那墙垣上的妖怪们帮了很多忙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.13,0:21:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.95,0:21:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.19,0:21:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主要是看这里有有趣的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.75,0:21:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是因为这是慎一郎的家…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.55,0:21:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.18,0:21:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能来看我爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.43,0:21:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.14,0:21:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永别了  慎一郎的孙女
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.71,0:21:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多保重
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.24,0:21:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个味道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.53,0:21:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么花吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.55,0:21:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.34,0:21:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为祖父的去世而哭哭啼啼的时候也闻到了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.65,0:21:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个善良温柔如花般的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.54,0:21:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是否察觉到了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.26,0:21:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从未看到过自己的那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.22,0:21:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己曾是如此倾心地呼唤过他
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.71,0:22:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看见就说明是相遇了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.43,0:22:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  如果可以的话能告诉我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.47,0:22:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目所遇见的妖怪们的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.76,0:22:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反复交替的相遇和别离
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.98,0:22:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.00,0:22:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾觉得如同秘密一般的沉重
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.81,0:22:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦能够对外倾诉便闪耀无比
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.42,0:22:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而无法用只言片语来表达
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.11,0:24:02.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您是…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.43,0:24:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鄙人叫做的场
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.90,0:24:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷盗妖怪的血液打算做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.28,0:24:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有种不祥的预感
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.61,0:24:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是别牵扯上关系为妙
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.24,0:24:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见了啊  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.12,0:24:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是这般耀眼真是不好意思了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.74,0:24:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预感应验了
