[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.17,0:02:34.17,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur2\shad2\bord1}小狐狸的手表
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.92,0:24:15.96,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1\pos(213,296)}秋风来袭
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.85,0:01:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捉到了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.98,0:01:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.33,0:01:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.97,0:01:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追得上的话就来追追看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.27,0:02:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.61,0:02:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙真是嚣张
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.11,0:02:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我记着！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.44,0:02:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母亲大人  我变强了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.65,0:02:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人也可以生活下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.97,0:02:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的话肯定能够帮上夏目的忙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.52,0:02:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.53,0:02:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和滋叔叔去旅行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.08,0:02:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  还记得在雁羽温泉做陶瓷的安井先生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.65,0:02:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾让贵志你去取过这个茶碗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.55,0:02:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…对  是在夏季合宿那附近的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.88,0:02:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实在那之后我和安井先生也时常有些来往
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.03,0:02:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正逢陶艺体验教室落成而受邀请去参观
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.76,0:02:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子阿姨呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.88,0:03:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天和几个朋友约好去购物
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.47,0:03:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不要挂心  两个人尽管去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.82,0:03:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是陶艺教室
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.18,0:03:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不过是同熟人和邻家小朋友们一起交流玩乐而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.94,0:03:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得不方便的话可以拒绝哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.09,0:03:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.18,0:03:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟朋友有约了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.49,0:03:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我想去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.72,0:03:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.42,0:03:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.55,0:03:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.24,0:03:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.50,0:03:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么…刚才好像听到老师在呻吟…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.61,0:03:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你睡傻了吗  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.05,0:03:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还疼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.25,0:04:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种伤口舔几下马上就会好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.39,0:04:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原想在去温泉的那段期间让中级妖怪来照顾你…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.48,0:04:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么！你说温泉？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.40,0:04:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你居然瞒着我要去温泉…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.50,0:04:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  还是不要乱动的好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.52,0:04:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雁羽的温泉对妖怪的伤口可是没有功效的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.60,0:04:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丙  不要说那些多余的废话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.07,0:04:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你受伤就过来探望  你这算是招呼吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.33,0:04:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.97,0:04:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你中了带咒符的箭了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.29,0:04:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这伤可会拖很久的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.13,0:04:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.44,0:04:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师说马上就能好…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.08,0:04:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也并不是瞎说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.43,0:04:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是对我们来说  这点时间不过一转眼的功夫
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.50,0:04:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽如此
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.60,0:04:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像斑这样的大妖怪的话要取回妖力可是很费力的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.62,0:04:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次看来流了很多的血呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.95,0:04:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么果然不能去旅行了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.86,0:05:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去向滋先生道个歉  然后就…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.05,0:05:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.72,0:05:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.13,0:05:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说那一带长着胧草
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.36,0:05:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胧草？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.80,0:05:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一种普通人看不见的妖怪药草
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.13,0:05:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寄生于树龄数十载的枯树上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.25,0:05:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将它碾碎涂在伤口上的话可以治疗妖怪的伤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.82,0:05:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说我不需要那种东西  但得带我去温泉啊  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.22,0:05:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.54,0:05:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说我也想去旅行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.58,0:05:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.00,0:05:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑大人  我们来探望你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.56,0:05:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探望探望
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.51,0:05:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说白色肥猫受伤了就过来参观参观
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.23,0:05:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是丙大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.95,0:05:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  喝上一杯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.61,0:05:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.62,0:05:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  不要在这半夜吵闹
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.55,0:05:56.94,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们太吵了…疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.44,0:05:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来把它留在这里对伤势更不利呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.44,0:06:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很困呢  贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.42,0:06:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  昨晚因为整理了行李而有些困
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.49,0:06:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝咖啡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.75,0:06:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  好的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.80,0:06:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不客气了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.35,0:06:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在停靠的站头有很好吃的车站便当
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.43,0:06:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中饭就吃那个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.79,0:06:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.65,0:06:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和父亲一起的旅行就是这种感觉的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.22,0:06:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有些含羞  但还是觉得很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.90,0:06:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是一旦这样面对面坐着
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.72,0:06:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便不知道该说些什么好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.92,0:06:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年轻人对陶艺没有兴趣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.05,0:06:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬让你配合我的兴趣  有些对不住呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.89,0:06:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.58,0:06:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢去年拿到的那个茶碗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.54,0:06:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直很喜欢烧制东西时的那种手感
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.11,0:06:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乍看之下很冰冷
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.50,0:07:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是从某处总会渗出一种温热的泥土的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.08,0:07:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.47,0:07:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以很久以前就想自己烧制一个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.83,0:07:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和滋先生的这种对话很是新鲜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.21,0:07:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…是戴在人类的手臂上的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.85,0:07:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.40,0:07:57.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.02,0:08:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你经常来这里眺望人类的交通工具呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.98,0:08:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.46,0:08:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是你站着的这个岩石
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.47,0:08:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.58,0:08:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像岩石的化身一般的东西啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.24,0:08:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经被称为道祖神
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.33,0:08:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道祖神？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.69,0:08:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道祖神是神明大人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.00,0:08:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是人类擅自拜祭我而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.27,0:08:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你经常来这里看列车
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.35,0:08:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的那么有意思吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.75,0:08:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我一想到夏目有可能回来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.56,0:08:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便不禁会过来瞧瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.89,0:08:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然夏目没来的时候很失望
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.59,0:08:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是会这样过来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.17,0:08:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目？那是你的朋友吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.89,0:08:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友？嗯  夏目是我的朋友！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.40,0:08:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？你戴着的是手表呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.74,0:08:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手表？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.92,0:08:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类制造的用来记录时间的工具
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.37,0:09:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！刚才明明还是停着的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.02,0:09:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴着这种东西  你难道想成为人类吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.09,0:09:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为人类？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.74,0:09:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我想成为像我妈妈那般伟大的狐狸呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.12,0:09:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么这就不是你所需要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.52,0:09:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是记录人类的时间的工具
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.55,0:09:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的时间？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.65,0:09:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是夏目！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.46,0:09:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.71,0:09:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.99,0:09:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目又来见我了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.84,0:09:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不再是以前那个胆小鬼了哦  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.50,0:09:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  令人心情舒畅的风呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.32,0:09:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.56,0:09:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.64,0:09:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经一年没来了啊  那家伙还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.12,0:09:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.21,0:09:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人是…？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.67,0:10:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和夏目一起生活着的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.91,0:10:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  藤原先生  欢迎到来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.12,0:10:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承蒙关照
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.74,0:10:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是贵志吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.79,0:10:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年来取那套茶碗的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.59,0:10:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  好久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.75,0:10:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么请吧  我带你们参观一下工房
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.79,0:10:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目快注意到我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.98,0:10:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.66,0:10:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙拿着人类的东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.38,0:10:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野兽居然想装成人类吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.29,0:10:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连变身都做不到  真是嚣张呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.92,0:10:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.20,0:10:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  传球
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.52,0:10:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.79,0:10:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来接住哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.02,0:10:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天可不能像上次那样了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.64,0:10:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！给我啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.38,0:10:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我还给我！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.11,0:10:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起了  对不起还给你就是了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.13,0:11:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才讨厌野兽的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.35,0:11:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是一座不错的窑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.69,0:11:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里是妈妈说过绝对不能接近的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.72,0:11:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天在陶艺教室制作好的作品要在这里烧制
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.10,0:11:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后天就能烧好带回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.18,0:11:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还真是值得期待呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.21,0:11:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天都累了吧  里面有温泉  请好好地放松吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.43,0:11:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.09,0:11:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这样的话就不能接近夏目了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.16,0:12:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  换我来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.93,0:12:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.16,0:12:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是长大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.24,0:12:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起刚来我家的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.80,0:12:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家依旧还是笑我弱不禁风呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.30,0:12:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得硬朗了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.37,0:12:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起生活着  所以很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.34,0:12:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个不错的温泉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.65,0:12:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目去那种可怕的地方做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.29,0:12:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是来见我的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.26,0:12:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.90,0:13:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  这东西只有在我跑动的时候才会走啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.49,0:13:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意不要让空气进入粘土里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.99,0:13:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.94,0:13:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瘦哥哥  把我给拉起来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.43,0:13:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.62,0:13:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瘦哥哥真软弱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.50,0:13:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还能再长大些吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.07,0:13:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要开始素烧了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.12,0:13:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君能否去窑里帮帮忙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.70,0:13:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.46,0:13:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪兽之子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.54,0:14:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不可去见人类
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.71,0:14:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.74,0:14:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为见面后总有一方会留下悲伤的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.85,0:14:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.13,0:14:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世上的生物们都是遵循各自的时间生活着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.38,0:14:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那绝非一致
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.03,0:14:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人有人的  妖有妖的  兽亦有兽的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.06,0:14:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听不懂啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.22,0:14:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说夏目的时间和你的是不一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.44,0:14:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可得赶紧的了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.17,0:14:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来得去跟配偶养育后代
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.52,0:14:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得像你母亲一样将智慧传授予子女
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.10,0:14:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这便是生活在兽的时间之中
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.15,0:14:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同样夏目也有他生活的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.07,0:14:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而那同你的时间完全不同
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.84,0:15:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道祖神您也有您自己的时间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.27,0:15:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我则是以这岩石的时间活过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.02,0:15:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早在人类与妖怪诞生之前就已经在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.51,0:15:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是在这以后
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.10,0:15:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在时间突然停止之前仍旧一直坐在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.90,0:15:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.70,0:15:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果离开这里  我也就要消失了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.28,0:15:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是那样的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.78,0:15:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是孤零零的不寂寞吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.19,0:15:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的时间之中并非如此长久
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.31,0:15:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亦非短暂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.62,0:15:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样停封住粘土的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.90,0:15:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来粘土就会变硬烧制成我们所捏制的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.49,0:15:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就在成品之前暂为休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.02,0:15:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志你要怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.98,0:15:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和安井约好去参观他的作品
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.18,0:16:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.55,0:16:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得来到这里  想要到处走走看看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.47,0:16:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为能够简单就能见到面
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.77,0:16:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来想得太简单了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.56,0:16:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙也有他自己的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.07,0:16:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们记得是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.61,0:16:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎哟  这可不是夏目大人么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.87,0:16:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是许久不见了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.13,0:16:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  你们知道小狐狸怎样了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.40,0:16:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  那家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.29,0:16:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙可惹不起咯  大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.23,0:16:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他完全变成了不良少年
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.05,0:16:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不良少年？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.00,0:16:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  让我们头痛不已呐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.65,0:16:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请看看这伤口
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.86,0:16:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会是你们又欺负他了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.77,0:16:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝无此事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.23,0:16:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.09,0:16:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有件事想问问
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.45,0:16:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  我不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.61,0:17:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只不过想要一直和夏目在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.37,0:17:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  别这么紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.42,0:17:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人来了  我们怎敢轻举妄动
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.63,0:17:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到夏目了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.98,0:17:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当想见你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.98,0:17:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.99,0:17:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.41,0:17:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过夏目大人看起来也很忙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.27,0:17:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像也是来这找什么药草来着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.09,0:17:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,药草？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.13,0:17:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  叫做胧草说是生在这附近的枯树上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.26,0:17:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胧草
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.54,0:17:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志  要开始上色咯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.25,0:17:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.01,0:18:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  要说到我能为夏目做的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.39,0:18:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来继续烧制十二小时就能完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.83,0:18:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天辛苦大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.94,0:18:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.05,0:18:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  有点事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.54,0:18:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行啊老师  不进去躺着
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.10,0:18:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴风雨就要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.75,0:18:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过随他去也没什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.10,0:19:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.88,0:19:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给夏目…要把那个给夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.62,0:19:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就差一点了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.61,0:19:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.95,0:20:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.65,0:20:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…夏目夏目！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.17,0:20:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.54,0:20:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在替我找这个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.87,0:20:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.28,0:20:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  那个是道祖神救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.17,0:20:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.10,0:20:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦我离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.22,0:20:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也就该消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.68,0:20:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正是那样的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.30,0:20:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道祖神让我不要再去见夏目了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.91,0:20:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说  因为会有一方伤心难过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.58,0:20:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…但是不一样  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.23,0:20:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候这只手表虽已坏掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.63,0:20:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是确实还是有在走呀  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.56,0:20:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得这事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.23,0:21:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同道祖神相遇  交谈  得到救助也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.96,0:21:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我同夏目也一定…一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.82,0:21:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狐狸对我倾诉着的那些话语
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.11,0:21:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽未能全部理解
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.67,0:21:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我理解了道祖神这一妖怪曾存在过的意义
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.68,0:21:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平安无事真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.49,0:21:24.35,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.60,0:21:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生活在不同时间下的生物们
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.50,0:21:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.49,0:21:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许比谁都要看得更久
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.52,0:21:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  再见
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.46,0:22:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔  画的是喵五郎的标志啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.72,0:22:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.70,0:22:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个好容器
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.66,0:22:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了呢  喵五郎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.84,0:22:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短暂的擦肩而过
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.87,0:22:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相遇尔后离别
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.99,0:22:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此对我而言
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.23,0:22:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那所有一切都是最珍贵的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.18,0:24:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又和妖怪有关
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.12,0:24:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文化祭绝对是兔女郎咖啡店
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.81,0:24:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兔女郎不行的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.21,0:24:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.43,0:24:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祭典可是相当令人期待的哟
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.46,0:24:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我也相当期待
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.66,0:24:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在猫咪咖啡店好好疼爱我吧
