[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.04,0:03:09.05,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}夏目        被擒
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.05,0:24:16.02,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\pos(188,296)}东方之森
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.82,0:01:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下周周六？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.38,0:01:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  刚好那时候能看到最美最壮观的流星雨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.38,0:01:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流星雨吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.19,0:01:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还得练习一下如何许愿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.92,0:01:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,许愿？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.19,0:01:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流星雨不就是流星吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.46,0:01:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在消失前许三次愿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.90,0:01:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能找到另一半
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.58,0:01:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是服了你了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.07,0:02:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就开始担心结婚了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.81,0:02:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  人多才开心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.44,0:02:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再约一些人来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.07,0:02:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如田沼…还有多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.28,0:02:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.18,0:02:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.60,0:02:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  燃起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.41,0:02:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燃起来干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.19,0:02:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  西村
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.70,0:02:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在不久前我还只是独自一人看星星
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.50,0:02:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么再见
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.15,0:02:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿时起就经常看到些奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.38,0:02:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人似乎看不到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.90,0:02:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些可能就是所谓的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.16,0:02:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.29,0:02:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您是夏目大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.47,0:02:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.77,0:02:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  请无论如何帮帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.89,0:02:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友的脚被石头夹住  动弹不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.23,0:02:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.32,0:02:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.20,0:02:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不快点的话  它的脚就…脚就…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.14,0:03:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不像以前那么讨厌看到它们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.07,0:03:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但一如既往地  每天会有很多麻烦事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.49,0:03:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差一点点  还差一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.27,0:03:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万分感谢  然后…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.14,0:03:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.50,0:03:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到夏目大人的话…该是拥有友人帐的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.38,0:03:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请…请把名字还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.48,0:03:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这样啊  明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.71,0:03:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护吾之人  显其名
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.37,0:04:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢  夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.07,0:04:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.86,0:04:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.10,0:04:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.27,0:04:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来似乎是真正的友人帐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.37,0:04:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是拥有友人帐的夏目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.61,0:04:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.43,0:04:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是传说中的夏目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.39,0:04:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很弱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.33,0:04:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是很好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.68,0:04:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧收拾掉他
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.94,0:04:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  小鬼  快点交出友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.20,0:04:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.31,0:04:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.49,0:04:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.64,0:04:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.98,0:04:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来接你放学  却又给我惹麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.98,0:04:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要总是什么事都参一脚啊  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.30,0:04:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  得救了啊  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.15,0:04:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.40,0:04:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得的微醉的气氛都被破坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.47,0:05:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要大白天开始就摄入酒精啊  保镖
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.19,0:05:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  那些家伙是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.67,0:05:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盯上了友人帐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.51,0:05:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是  但是居然那样一大群一起来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.25,0:05:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓友人帐  是祖母夏目玲子的遗物
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.85,0:05:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将打败了的妖怪收为佣人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.39,0:05:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迫使那些妖怪留下其名最终集成一册
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.14,0:05:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据使用方法  可以操纵众多妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.15,0:05:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.79,0:05:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.39,0:05:34.05,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面很冷吧  快进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.20,0:05:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想拿回名字的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.35,0:05:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想得到力量的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.61,0:05:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各种妖怪为了友人帐而来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.01,0:05:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过从今天出现的那些家伙那里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.23,0:05:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感受到了和以往妖怪不同的阴暗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.56,0:05:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令人讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.35,0:05:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来那些家伙是用小妖怪做诱饵
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.16,0:05:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引你过去的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.47,0:06:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想尽可能将名字都还给妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.71,0:06:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此  我不能把它交给奇怪的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.84,0:06:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西村说夏目君也会去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.68,0:06:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流星雨什么的  仔细想想  还真没有好好看过呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.42,0:06:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是  第一次  所以好期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.59,0:06:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  也许我去不了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.45,0:06:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时西村他们可以拜托给你们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.35,0:06:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是妖怪的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.17,0:06:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点在意的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.21,0:06:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  下节课要换教室哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.25,0:06:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.39,0:06:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.06,0:06:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说他稍微可以依赖我们了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.70,0:06:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.34,0:06:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他总是那么见外啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.31,0:06:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问过他一次
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.42,0:07:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不跟别人说自己看得到妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.12,0:07:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤原先生他们应该会听他说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.55,0:07:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真直接啊  然后  为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.48,0:07:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说不希望失去他们的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.02,0:07:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑容？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.80,0:07:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初我也是不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.40,0:07:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我曾经梦到夏目被妖怪吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.78,0:07:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.38,0:07:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.35,0:07:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说夏目迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.76,0:07:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就会惊出一身冷汗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.46,0:07:31.69,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西村  你太兴奋了！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.62,0:07:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想着该不会就像梦里一样  被妖怪吃了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.89,0:07:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  毫不知情的西村他们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.90,0:07:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却能笑着等待夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.11,0:07:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想着  肯定是睡过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.56,0:07:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是跟他们说了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.12,0:07:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每当弄脏衣服时
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.69,0:07:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子阿姨他们肯定会以为出大事了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.50,0:07:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法一直微笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.07,0:07:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目不喜欢这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.04,0:07:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那肯定是他最害怕的事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.32,0:08:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.44,0:08:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  吃点鲷鱼烧再回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.78,0:08:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊  肚子也很饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.32,0:08:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.78,0:08:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.36,0:08:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.36,0:08:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.27,0:08:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  西村  我先回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.18,0:08:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然跑到这里来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.68,0:08:41.27,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.60,0:08:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.91,0:08:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 等等  夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.88,0:08:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.91,0:08:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是在这众目睽睽的地方逗留的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.96,0:09:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猿面军团？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.74,0:09:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎不是这一带的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.12,0:09:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是为夺友人帐慕名而来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.07,0:09:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说  友人帐之名开始在妖怪圈里盛传了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.59,0:09:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个感觉  那些家伙看上去还有点能耐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.34,0:09:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么线索吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.81,0:09:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说起来  听说东部的山里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.09,0:09:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个森林好像住着这样一群妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.92,0:09:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,森林？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.60,0:09:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是说  人同妖的界线很模糊的境地
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.11,0:09:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我想起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.38,0:09:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.62,0:09:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好不要接近那里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.02,0:09:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃？ 为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.35,0:09:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有不祥的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.06,0:09:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不祥的东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.92,0:10:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这里是？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.41,0:10:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们的森林
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.22,0:10:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类一旦闯入  就没那么容易出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.94,0:10:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想吃苦头的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.88,0:10:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就快点将友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.68,0:10:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们打算拿友人帐来做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.61,0:10:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那本册子能让很多妖怪听从命令吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.62,0:10:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区一人类居然想操控妖怪  真是不知天高地厚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.12,0:10:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的首领正需要有那种力量的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.41,0:10:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须献给我们的首领
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.74,0:10:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.58,0:10:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.79,0:10:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我既不打算操纵它们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.95,0:10:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不打算交给企图操纵它们的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.41,0:10:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有骨气  小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.87,0:10:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好觉悟了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.17,0:10:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.98,0:10:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.03,0:11:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么来着  这个感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.52,0:11:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉不妙…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.48,0:11:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安静
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.93,0:11:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.37,0:11:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.69,0:11:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在意三筱的话  就跑来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.67,0:11:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你居然被带到这里来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.33,0:11:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.95,0:11:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不清楚  到处都有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.27,0:11:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定是陷阱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.03,0:11:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了不让我逃走吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.05,0:11:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不对
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.91,0:11:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是他们干的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.54,0:11:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.04,0:11:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  先离开这个森林吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.44,0:11:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真狡猾  藏起来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.79,0:11:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实这附近有人类的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.06,0:11:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.35,0:12:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.03,0:12:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙…那家伙来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.33,0:12:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.97,0:12:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.69,0:12:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个好像能派上点用场
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.77,0:12:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.43,0:12:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人是的场先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.75,0:12:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.99,0:12:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个除妖师吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.39,0:12:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当家  怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.82,0:13:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到一只了  但不知是否能派上用场
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.17,0:13:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是流言传入妖怪们耳中
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.65,0:13:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这附近都少见他们的踪影了…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.41,0:13:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘  那边的草丛里…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.31,0:13:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.60,0:13:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.76,0:13:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的错觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.02,0:13:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除妖师  的场一族的当家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.74,0:13:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是对妖怪还是对人类都毫不手软
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.58,0:13:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想见到那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.93,0:13:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.31,0:13:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是…陷阱吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.88,0:13:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.93,0:13:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是似乎是的场设下的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.24,0:13:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.30,0:13:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定对人类也起反应
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.50,0:13:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要往哪里走
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.10,0:13:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是变回原来妖怪的样子  一跃就能逃出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.71,0:13:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是会被那家伙发现的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.16,0:13:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来只好先去哪避避风了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.15,0:13:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来三筱的话是应验了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.60,0:14:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这附近…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.30,0:14:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.93,0:14:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  在哪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.57,0:14:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事…在这深山老林中
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.62,0:14:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人住吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.75,0:14:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场…这里是的场的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.24,0:14:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场的式卫
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.65,0:14:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会有这么多…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.19,0:15:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里到底是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.53,0:15:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出口在哪边
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.44,0:15:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之得先找回装着友人帐的书包
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.63,0:15:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.24,0:15:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那似乎是个少年
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.85,0:15:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说是在这间家宅前抓到的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.42,0:15:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到竟能如此轻易地接近这里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.82,0:15:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.43,0:15:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场  还未察觉到抓到的人是我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.52,0:15:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经扣押于西边牢房中了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.02,0:15:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的随身物品放置于雾之间了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.75,0:15:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来楼梯下有什么在呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.78,0:16:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是何人  请出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.45,0:16:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.04,0:16:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  在这边
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.02,0:16:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么有人类的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.33,0:17:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.93,0:17:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  有个像猫咪老师一样的东西被扔进垃圾桶里了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.48,0:17:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过只是装作招财猫的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.71,0:17:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小妖怪竟敢把本大爷扔进了垃圾桶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.52,0:17:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这岂是笑话  笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.59,0:17:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  竟会被那种小妖怪抓住还扣留了友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.30,0:17:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是丢死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.30,0:17:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.78,0:17:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过的场他若真如你所述的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.30,0:17:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说明友人帐的存在尚未暴露
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.91,0:17:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然如果看到了就应当对之关注不已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.69,0:17:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是的场同许多妖怪有过照面
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.24,0:17:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.41,0:17:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.13,0:17:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若让的场那样的家伙得知友人帐的存在后会成怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.64,0:18:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪们多少也是能预料到的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.22,0:18:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不会轻易就泄露出去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.98,0:18:06.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.13,0:18:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呆子  只要你拿着友人帐就是不断地招惹麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.77,0:18:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧做个了断  转让给我就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.91,0:18:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让我玩出趣味来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.35,0:18:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  有啥好笑的  呆子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.63,0:18:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来挺热闹的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.78,0:18:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有少年潜入宅子里来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.03,0:18:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就有劳七濑你去逮住他了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.74,0:18:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.08,0:18:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说今天也要去找这座森林的主人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.74,0:18:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是比那还有趣的事情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.10,0:18:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那所说的少年…难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.94,0:18:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是命运吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.99,0:18:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别院？ 这里吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.15,0:18:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  根据三筱所述
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.88,0:18:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在东边的森林中有的场家的别院
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.81,0:19:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说曾经以这为据点猎捕妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.92,0:19:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是这些装饰或是这庭院氛围绝对没错
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.17,0:19:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除妖师一职逐渐荒废  最近似乎不太盛行了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.29,0:19:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那当家的看来是相当有势力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.79,0:19:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎捕…妖怪？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.62,0:19:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区一人类居然想操控妖怪  真是不知天高地厚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.24,0:19:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须献给我们的首领
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.46,0:19:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说那些妖怪是为了保护森林
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.22,0:19:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底该往哪走
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.38,0:19:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶  猫咪老师您不知道的来着？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.79,0:19:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呆子  不是你说友人帐在雾之间么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.23,0:19:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是听说在那  又不知道雾之间在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.45,0:19:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么?!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.79,0:19:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说你什么都不知道就到处乱跑么  呆子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.07,0:19:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是老师您先跑起来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.65,0:20:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.15,0:20:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个壶好像在哪…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.50,0:20:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放我出去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.88,0:20:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壶在说话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.84,0:20:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.63,0:20:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目那小子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.57,0:20:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是被的场的式卫所抓住的…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.32,0:20:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就老实放弃友人帐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.70,0:20:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里没有  走人  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.60,0:20:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是这么说  该往哪走呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.40,0:20:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要人带路么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.79,0:20:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾潜入过这家宅
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.34,0:20:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷路了的话  我能够帮上忙哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.20,0:20:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.11,0:20:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就试试看你是否在说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.03,0:20:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾之间在哪你说说看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.26,0:20:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾之间？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.56,0:20:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那令人毛骨悚然的的场当家的房间么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.42,0:20:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.56,0:20:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不过既然我告诉你们了相应地你们把我也带过去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.71,0:20:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么  小东西还敢跟我谈交易
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.99,0:20:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这小猪般的家伙嚷嚷什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.16,0:21:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是小猪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.31,0:21:02.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这小东西  臭壶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.66,0:21:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住…住手  死猪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.19,0:21:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了  壶猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.83,0:21:08.88,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是猪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.25,0:21:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  老师  别闹了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.33,0:21:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是碰到设有圈套的房间就麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.13,0:21:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就躲在这里好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.34,0:21:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师您也多加小心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.27,0:21:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢你了  能告诉我房间的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.77,0:21:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要道谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.08,0:21:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.80,0:21:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个就…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.08,0:21:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.25,0:21:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若不是这般样子的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.58,0:21:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类什么的早就…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.12,0:21:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是  明明只是人类竟敢剥夺妖怪的名字来控制它们
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.08,0:21:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是想要控制它们
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.00,0:21:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦  交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.99,0:21:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么想要友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.33,0:21:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用来做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.64,0:21:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给首领的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.09,0:21:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定能够替我们将森林恢复原貌
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.90,0:21:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.51,0:22:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐可不是那般有魔力的道具
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.11,0:22:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我能理解你想要恢复森林…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.45,0:22:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  肯定行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.05,0:22:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首领能将那些家伙赶出去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.09,0:22:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后让森林重返原貌
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.62,0:22:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.89,0:22:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若那样使用友人帐的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.04,0:22:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所说的首领也会变成像的场那样的人一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.00,0:22:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是久违了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.08,0:22:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.18,0:24:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  现在是和的场捉迷藏的时候吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.24,0:24:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  得赶紧夺回来
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.18,0:24:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想要得到力量强大的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.46,0:24:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能让的场知道友人帐的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.42,0:24:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有力量强大的人类也一样
