[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,1
Style: OP_jp,方正楷体_GBK,33,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,45,1
Style: OP_ch,方正楷体_GBK,36,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,5,1
Style: ED_jp,方正楷体_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,45,1
Style: ED_ch,方正楷体_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,5,1
Style: bt,方正楷体_GBK,55,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H32A8D0C8,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,33,&H00E8EEF4,&HF0000000,&H1E23384E,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text



Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.40,0:01:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.13,0:01:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.00,0:02:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.51,0:02:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在干嘛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.91,0:02:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来买烙菜盘 塔子婶婶的 滋叔叔的 还有我的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.94,0:02:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你把我的份也一起算进去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.28,0:02:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再去给我弄个盘子 快起来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.21,0:02:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快起来去找 夏目!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.98,0:02:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事? 刚才好像有股异样的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.60,0:02:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从这幅画里传出来的么?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.78,0:03:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢这画吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.96,0:03:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.88,0:03:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳蚤市场快结束了都还没卖掉 喜欢的话就给你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.10,0:03:15.15,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱树林中的他
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.94,0:03:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,净是些树枝 要把这么无聊的画挂起来?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.35,0:03:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会么 我倒是觉得很漂亮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.63,0:03:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 随你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.51,0:03:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 说的也是啊 如果有点花什么的就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.30,0:03:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.71,0:04:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从什么地方吹进来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.32,0:04:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可思议的是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.06,0:04:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊? 又来啦!?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.04,0:04:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在第二天的早晨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.34,0:04:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 今天也是这样啊!?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.01,0:04:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有第三天的早晨枕边总散落着花瓣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.16,0:04:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是你喝醉后从什么地方摘来的吧 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.85,0:04:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么啊你 我对花才没兴趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.43,0:04:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呸 呸呸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.41,0:04:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从把这画挂起来的那天开始的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.82,0:04:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这是妖怪搞的鬼的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.17,0:04:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就必须尽早解决才行了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.96,0:05:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你啊 我就是想要这个大小的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.51,0:05:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要杜绝所有降临在这个家里的灾祸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.37,0:05:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵 喵喵
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.17,0:05:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要随便进来啊 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.07,0:05:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么拿着网啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.83,0:05:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定是小精灵搞的鬼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.96,0:05:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我逮住你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.50,0:05:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么不符合科学的东西是不会有的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.18,0:05:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒是真敢这么说啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.91,0:05:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啊 说啊 还亏是你说的了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.49,0:05:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啊 真亏你说得出来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.36,0:06:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然敢闯进我的地盘 真是个让人不爽的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.78,0:06:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你... 这些花到底是?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.67,0:06:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花是献给「那个人」的 跟你无关
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.40,0:06:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这小偷
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.37,0:06:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小偷? 我偷了你什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.96,0:06:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚣张的家伙 我要吃了你 看招
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.99,0:06:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住...住手 先生!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.01,0:06:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会 为啥啊 难得我想做个尽职的保镖...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.12,0:06:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「那个人」是指谁? 这里只有我跟先生两个人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.17,0:06:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呀  不是好好的在这儿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.40,0:06:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.62,0:07:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要大呼小叫的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.66,0:07:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八坂大人会被你吓到的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.41,0:07:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是...是哦 而且家里人也会...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.17,0:07:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八坂大人?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.30,0:07:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 他住在这幅画里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.94,0:07:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它还给我 这是我的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.93,0:07:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不小心把它弄丢了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.78,0:07:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就被人类捡走 贩卖
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.05,0:07:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终流落到这种寒酸的地方来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.25,0:07:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒酸地儿...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.87,0:07:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒酸地儿...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.21,0:07:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么从墙壁上取不下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.90,0:07:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 怎么回事? 取不下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.75,0:07:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 难道用钉子钉住了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.09,0:07:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有呢 倒是你没有动什么奇怪的手脚吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.29,0:07:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.27,0:08:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法 到取下来为止 我会一直来这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.73,0:08:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫巳弥 我明天会再来的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.00,0:08:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.09,0:08:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂...喂!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.20,0:08:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要把这么可怕的东西扔在这里啊 喂!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.00,0:08:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是 理所当然似的...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.15,0:08:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.75,0:08:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二天巳弥又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.77,0:08:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把手伸出来 小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.43,0:08:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是照顾八坂先生的谢礼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.69,0:08:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很感谢你啊 但也不要放在房间里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.61,0:08:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很漂亮吧 八坂大人原本也是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.15,0:08:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他非常喜欢看花和蝴蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.51,0:08:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经...是人?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.08,0:09:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是很久以前的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.92,0:09:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在樱树的树枝上赏着樱花
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.08,0:09:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盛开的樱花让我的心情格外愉悦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.98,0:09:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一时疏忽 就这么躲在樱树枝间跟他聊了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.16,0:09:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这么美丽的樱花为伴 还觉得书本比较重要吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.85,0:09:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起樱花看书会更有趣吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.30,0:09:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,书也好 樱花也好 我都很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.87,0:09:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有跟你交谈似乎也很有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.04,0:09:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他叫八坂 身体很弱但因是名门之后
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.14,0:09:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以几乎没有属于他自己的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.08,0:10:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没有察觉我是妖怪 自在地跟我交谈着
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.48,0:10:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.73,0:10:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很怕他知道我是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.87,0:10:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以在没有樱花 无法藏身的季节里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.25,0:10:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会离开那片林子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.56,0:10:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们成了只有在樱花的季节才互相谈心的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.65,0:10:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳弥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.16,0:10:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有一天我获得了自由 我要随性地到处游历
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.31,0:10:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在不同的地方欣赏风光一定很棒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.37,0:10:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳弥 不知道为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.30,0:10:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有好多好多话想跟你说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.03,0:10:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道度过了几个这样的春天
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.53,0:10:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然有一年 他不再出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.44,0:10:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等啊 等啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.28,0:10:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等了一个春天 又一个春天
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.04,0:11:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开始寻找他
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.96,0:11:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不知道去哪里找只好到处乱转
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.66,0:11:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后终于
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.66,0:11:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我找到了这幅画
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.62,0:11:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打听后 才得知是一个很有名的妖怪画家画的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.99,0:11:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他一定是厌倦了人世 才躲进画里去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.58,0:11:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我收下了这幅画
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.73,0:11:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了安慰他 带着这幅画开始到处旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.11,0:11:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想着 等到有一天他的心灵得到慰籍之后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.74,0:11:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会从画里出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.48,0:11:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话就可以再一次跟他畅谈了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.36,0:11:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实这幅画很像是那个有名的妖怪画家画的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.93,0:12:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这只是幅普通的画
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.48,0:12:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,画着冬天的树排下站着一个叫八坂的男人而已
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.57,0:12:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么等 那个男人也不可能出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.17,0:12:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使这样 巳弥还是每天拿着花前来拜访
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.53,0:12:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.90,0:12:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.29,0:12:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.14,0:12:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咳得很奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.51,0:12:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知怎么就是停不下来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.54,0:12:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵~
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.73,0:12:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵~
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.91,0:12:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 不要破坏绿化哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.33,0:12:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳弥一定是像这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.70,0:12:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若无其事地一边追寻着这样美丽的景色
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.50,0:12:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边旅行着的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.39,0:12:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带着一幅普通的画 独自一人地...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.40,0:13:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜见 拜见
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.41,0:13:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙是春地藏
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.18,0:13:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟着春天出现为了修行而占卜吉凶的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.70,0:13:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的身边有不祥的阴影
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.53,0:13:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到您的尸体上有一棵树在生长
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.88,0:13:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 尸体是怎么...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.74,0:13:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.68,0:13:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 塔子婶婶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.27,0:13:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 好像你一个人在大声喊话?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.89,0:13:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.48,0:13:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.49,0:13:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.80,0:13:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.18,0:14:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.05,0:14:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.77,0:14:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一起回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.01,0:14:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.70,0:14:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我开始害怕被他发觉我是妖怪」...吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.04,0:14:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是一样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.88,0:14:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 那个春地藏的话 是什么意思呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.97,0:14:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.84,0:14:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.86,0:14:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 这是!?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.70,0:14:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.90,0:14:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 我知道咳嗽的原因了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.00,0:14:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这幅画正在吸取你的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.47,0:14:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它伸展着树枝是想吸收更多的能量
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.20,0:14:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.03,0:14:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区一幅画 竟敢碰我的猎物 不可原谅!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.41,0:14:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就吃掉你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.02,0:14:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以 先生!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.32,0:15:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这幅画是巳弥的...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.73,0:15:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白痴夏目 你干什么呢 振作点!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.90,0:15:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白痴夏目!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.83,0:15:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳弥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.81,0:15:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有一天我获得了自由 我要随性地到处游历
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.21,0:15:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 一个人的话一定很没意思
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.39,0:15:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时候 你会和我一起去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.93,0:15:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊 巳弥 今年你也来见我了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.39,0:15:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天说点什么好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.39,0:15:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.39,0:16:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我一直带在身边 让这幅画有了妖力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.25,0:16:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生根在了墙上 已经拿不下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.61,0:16:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去你的生命也会有危险
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.79,0:16:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想用妖力把这幅画烧掉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.42,0:16:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以 巳弥
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.09,0:16:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是你重要的画啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.43,0:16:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.04,0:16:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.78,0:16:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.35,0:16:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八坂大人 其实也许已经不在了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.58,0:16:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 带着这幅画去旅行的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.10,0:16:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像和那个人在一起一样很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.57,0:16:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下雨也好 刮风也好 感觉我并不是一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.18,0:16:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 已经没关系了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.60,0:17:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕只要一次也好 我只是想可以不在意自己是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.52,0:17:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想那样面对面说说话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.03,0:17:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳弥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.23,0:17:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没事 再找一下拿下来的办法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.11,0:17:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.05,0:17:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也喜欢这幅画
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.75,0:17:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.36,0:17:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和巳弥是一样的啊 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.78,0:17:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕对重要的人说真话而悲伤着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.07,0:17:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 抱歉 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.38,0:17:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想把这幅画留给巳弥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.22,0:17:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这幅画上画的正是八坂大人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.29,0:17:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是明明知道巳弥不会来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.79,0:17:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却仍在冬天的树林中
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.34,0:17:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找着她  想要见她的八坂大人的身影
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.48,0:17:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 结果还是没有什么办法 几天过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.60,0:18:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸好塔子婶婶看不见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.61,0:18:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白痴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.45,0:18:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.18,0:18:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要烧了这幅画
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.06,0:18:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳弥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.38,0:18:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在此之前 我想让这幅画开满樱花
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.21,0:18:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像和那个人相遇时的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.57,0:18:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会帮我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.15,0:19:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.85,0:19:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.58,0:19:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮啊 巳弥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.91,0:19:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳弥 八坂大人他...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.86,0:19:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.79,0:19:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.70,0:19:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.67,0:20:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 这里是那幅画的...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.98,0:20:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我醒来的时候 画中伸展出的树枝和画满的樱花
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.89,0:20:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都消失得干干净净了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.57,0:20:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看画的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.53,0:20:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「那个人」 八坂大人的身影也已经不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.22,0:20:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伸手 很容易就拿了下来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.58,0:21:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天以后 巳弥再也没有来过
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.81,0:21:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳弥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.07,0:21:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许不知何时那个人的心已经寄居在画里了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.65,0:21:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这幅画会伸展出树枝吸取我的能量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.58,0:21:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是为了能再和你相见 为了让树开花吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.74,0:21:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个人是否还在盛开的樱花林中呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.44,0:21:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是已经从画中解脱 已经开始两个人的旅行了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.00,0:21:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.98,0:21:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巳弥她 已经说出真相了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.21,0:21:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 你有说什么吗 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.57,0:21:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.86,0:21:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别了 巳弥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.60,0:22:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在花的季节中相遇的友人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.85,0:23:50.94,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,554)}{\fs52}临时的家
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.58,0:23:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从看到了奇怪的脚印之后
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.50,0:23:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里就开始出现了一些奇怪的现象
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.91,0:23:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我小时候也遇到过这种情况呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.17,0:23:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滋叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.08,0:23:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那个人来了之后就完全没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.79,0:23:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她虽然有点奇怪 却是个很漂亮的女生呢

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 少しだけ大人の色に染まる指先
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 指尖稍露成年的沧桑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 照れくさそうに そっと隠して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 你就害羞得将它悄悄收起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 頬杖ついた君 見つめてる視線の先に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 手托下巴的你将视线投向
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 小さな蕾が ゆらゆら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 那随风轻曳的小小花蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} ねぇ 僕なんて いまも迷いばかりで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 喂 现在的我仍迷茫依旧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} あの日贈った言葉 今さら思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 这才回想起 那日你的临别赠言
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「君色に未来染めて...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「将我的未来染成你的颜色...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ 聞いていてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 听我倾诉好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ わがままいいですか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 让我任性好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手に入れた途端に消えてしまいそう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}拥有的瞬间仿佛就会消散
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}言葉をくれませんか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不说点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あなたがいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}因为有你在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}それだけで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう世界が変わってしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我的世界就会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}モノトーンの景色が ほら 鮮やかに映る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}映入眼眸的单调景色也会光鲜亮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}いつのまにか 離れていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不知何时却已离开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手を繋いで歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}牵着手 向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}上手く愛せているかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}能够好好去爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あの空に聞いてみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}天空也许会回答
