[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,1
Style: OP_jp,方正楷体_GBK,33,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,45,1
Style: OP_ch,方正楷体_GBK,36,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,5,1
Style: ED_jp,方正楷体_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,45,1
Style: ED_ch,方正楷体_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,5,1
Style: bt,方正楷体_GBK,55,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text



Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.19,0:01:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师 老师
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.85,0:01:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目他又说谎了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.57,0:01:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窗户上有个女人一直在偷窥 怎么可能嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.11,0:01:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这里可是三楼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.92,0:01:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会说那种话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.33,0:02:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 梦到以前了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.33,0:02:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.66,0:02:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.31,0:02:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真少见呐 雪堆得这么高
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.08,0:02:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡眠不足吗 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.00,0:02:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道晚上干了什么了么 这个色家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.42,0:02:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么烦心事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.21,0:02:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 每一天我都从心底里感到幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.97,0:02:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太夸张了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.13,0:02:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.35,0:02:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.58,0:02:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么呢 猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.81,0:03:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看着不就明白了 调戏小狗呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.11,0:03:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愉快愉快愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.14,0:03:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 你这样子小心滑下来...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.54,0:03:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.35,0:03:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏你还是只猫呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.03,0:03:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白痴 笑什么 都说我不是猫了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.46,0:03:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 我的腰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.16,0:03:23.18,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪化之后是春天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.46,0:03:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个是可以治腰痛的草药啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.56,0:03:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都不知道吗 都怪你都怪你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.30,0:03:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 痛痛痛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.04,0:03:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.76,0:03:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 这附近我还没来过呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.00,0:03:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里叫柴原
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.00,0:03:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来有两尊雕像守护着森林之神
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.18,0:03:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在只剩下一尊了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.88,0:03:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真漂亮啊 一个脚印都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.92,0:04:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啪呼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.43,0:04:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 你这只臭...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.15,0:04:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又...扭到腰了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.07,0:04:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光顾着跟笨蛋玩 太阳都快落山了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.11,0:04:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,草药 草药 啊 又扭到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.14,0:04:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久没玩雪了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.20,0:04:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.17,0:05:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦? 你看得见我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.60,0:05:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 我正需要个身体来附身
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.15,0:05:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.24,0:05:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.66,0:05:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.92,0:05:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 进入这里了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.29,0:05:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 反正有实体能动了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.00,0:05:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这...这样就可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.62,0:05:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然能用雪做出让我寄宿的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.94,0:05:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是了不起的人类啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.64,0:05:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫玄 是寄宿在那个石像里的神明
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.33,0:05:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请帮帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.72,0:05:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.55,0:05:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个身体融化之前
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.16,0:05:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能帮我实现愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.21,0:05:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就诅咒你家三代!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.05,0:05:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好恶劣的性格
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.75,0:06:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 我可以吃掉这刨冰吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.90,0:06:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我错了 请一定要帮帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.67,0:06:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 先说说是怎么回事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.30,0:06:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶灵退治?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.55,0:06:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 听说从这里一直向西有棵封魔之树
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.37,0:06:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但封印已经被打破 恶灵被释放了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.56,0:06:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是散发着黑气 使草木枯萎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.24,0:06:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扰乱人类心灵的邪恶之灵
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.42,0:06:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能放任不管
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.19,0:06:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要...一定要用这双手将其封印
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.71,0:06:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉是什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.54,0:06:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是玄不是还有同伴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.27,0:06:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前还有另一尊石像吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.56,0:06:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候真的很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.05,0:06:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是两个人一起守护着森林
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.54,0:07:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一同凝望风霜雨露 日月星华
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.38,0:07:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她...翠被打碎成粉末
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.57,0:07:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴原现在只剩下我一个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.44,0:07:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独自一人...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.05,0:07:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄大人 这里很无趣吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.28,0:07:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点都不觉得这里无聊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.35,0:07:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为能一直在一起...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.62,0:07:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是玄的梦 涌进了我的心里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.03,0:07:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一定是翠 被恶灵打碎的翠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.86,0:07:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄 再哭就要融化了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.30,0:07:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶灵的话我也不会放着不管
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.58,0:08:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄 这里也有很多我想要守护的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.50,0:08:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志 吃饭啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.74,0:08:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.29,0:08:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封魔之树?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.00,0:08:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是森林公园那吧? 好像是有一棵
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.63,0:08:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那棵树的话 最近因为扩建道路被砍掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.13,0:08:26.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.81,0:08:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.09,0:08:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太可怕了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.58,0:08:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有谣言说那边的植物开始枯萎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.84,0:08:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是恶灵作祟呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.17,0:08:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得呢 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.75,0:08:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃? 啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.87,0:08:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是酸雨的关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.92,0:08:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎您回来 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.34,0:08:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问你是哪位
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.27,0:08:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.49,0:08:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为慢慢适应了雪兔的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.68,0:08:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多少可以变回原来的样子了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.08,0:09:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以算是训练 也当是回礼 就想着扫扫院子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.46,0:09:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.62,0:09:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扫真是令人高兴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.77,0:09:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不小心一点的话 会融化掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.65,0:09:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管他 他化掉之后你也就解放了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.03,0:09:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我剥下这橘子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.32,0:09:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经答应了要帮他的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.69,0:09:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你尽说些天真的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.09,0:09:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好甜 好甜 这个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.68,0:09:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩感情真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.76,0:09:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从哪里看出来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.75,0:09:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个橘子啦 还有打雪仗啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.59,0:09:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生~~
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.90,0:09:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目~~
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.54,0:09:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.56,0:09:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都因为你 连我都做出那么丢人的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.23,0:09:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高贵的我竟然会打什么雪仗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.27,0:09:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哪里高贵了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.57,0:09:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 你不是腰疼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.57,0:09:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 你们俩感情真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.72,0:09:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我想起翠的事情了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.14,0:09:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄 封魔之树虽然已经被砍掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.14,0:09:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道树的所在地
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.00,0:09:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.16,0:09:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.49,0:10:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌总是恣意许些任性愿望的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.91,0:10:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翠虽然也同意我的看法...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.10,0:10:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前人们都传说要是看到三色彩虹的话 愿望就可以实现
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.62,0:10:24.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翠笑着说他们可真傻呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.93,0:10:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但从那之后 她每次看到彩虹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.19,0:10:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会遗憾地说 不是三色的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.69,0:10:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不知那些人的愿望实现了没有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.57,0:10:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使那样 翠却...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.09,0:10:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄 那个把翠打碎的人是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.70,0:10:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.71,0:10:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.06,0:10:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.96,0:10:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边 追过去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.75,0:11:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个破屋里 好像有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.52,0:11:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.46,0:11:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空气好混浊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.48,0:11:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要深吸气 不然会失去意识的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.60,0:11:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.88,0:11:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.11,0:11:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.55,0:11:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄 危险 快放开
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.44,0:11:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人 这是翠
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.80,0:11:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翠变成恶灵了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.09,0:11:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要用这双手..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.64,0:11:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翠 回去吧 我们一起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.78,0:11:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.37,0:12:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那竟然是翠...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.94,0:12:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么回事 玄
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.47,0:12:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和翠原本是二尊成对的神明
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.54,0:12:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寄宿在柴原的石像里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.96,0:12:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,净化森林 祛除邪气
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.42,0:12:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一次 农作物收成不好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.68,0:12:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村民们都跑来哭诉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.24,0:12:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈求能让土地富饶起来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.52,0:12:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我们是驱邪守护神
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.82,0:12:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法润泽田地
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.14,0:12:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有询问过路过的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.69,0:12:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但依旧束手无策
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.44,0:12:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后 我和翠开始消耗自己的生命之光来照耀村子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.10,0:12:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可即使如此 也无法使田地富饶起来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.78,0:13:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于 人们...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.53,0:13:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将干旱欠收的原因归罪于我们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.31,0:13:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.51,0:13:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.42,0:13:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.41,0:13:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.89,0:13:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翠哭喊着让人们住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.10,0:13:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喊着她曾是多么地爱怜他们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.91,0:13:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么地希望他们幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.24,0:13:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 他们还是没能听到我们的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.68,0:13:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.67,0:13:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.34,0:13:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我宁可削减自己的生命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.49,0:13:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来祈求你们的幸福 一直守护着你们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.81,0:13:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的人类啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.66,0:13:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨你们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.31,0:13:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨你们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.56,0:14:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨你们!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.48,0:14:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是翠化成恶灵袭击了村民
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.60,0:14:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就被人类封印至今
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.05,0:14:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没能守护好她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.75,0:14:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能从人类的手中守护好她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.74,0:14:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能从憎恶中守护好她的心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.06,0:14:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 至少
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.69,0:14:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要用这双手将化为恶灵的翠...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.19,0:14:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲手...亲手...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.67,0:14:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.73,0:14:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.83,0:14:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.95,0:14:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找那只雪兔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.85,0:14:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为实在太可爱了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.37,0:15:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住就把它放进冰箱里了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.15,0:15:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.54,0:15:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为今天有点暖和
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.25,0:15:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵 只有一只的话总觉得有些可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.31,0:15:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就另外再做了一只
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.19,0:15:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 不行呢 做得好难看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.33,0:15:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.28,0:15:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天晚上 玄靠着小小的雪兔睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.16,0:15:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那小小的雪兔到早上时已融化消失殆尽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.04,0:16:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罕见地连续下了几天的雨
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.19,0:16:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉翠就隐藏在那朦胧的雨的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.09,0:16:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是翠吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.08,0:16:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄!?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.17,0:16:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住...住...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.31,0:16:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.50,0:16:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.15,0:16:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跑去哪里了 先生 玄他...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.51,0:16:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要靠近他 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.12,0:16:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他正在变成恶灵
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.47,0:16:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伴随着寂寞 憎恶与恨意也在他体内逐渐滋生膨胀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.87,0:16:51.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然他也在努力地压制着
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.70,0:16:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.48,0:16:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.41,0:16:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我纸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.08,0:17:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有听过友人帐的传闻
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.04,0:17:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人 请把我的名字也...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.35,0:17:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底明不明白 玄
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.91,0:17:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦写上你的名字 那张纸就等同你的生命
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.41,0:17:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.90,0:17:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请烧掉那张纸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.95,0:17:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我变成了恶灵 那时就...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.83,0:17:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.24,0:17:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.02,0:17:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要独自一人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.34,0:17:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄 振作点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.05,0:17:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是孤身一人 有翠在
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.56,0:17:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有我们也在
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.05,0:17:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说过会帮你 会努力想办法了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.84,0:17:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么也做不了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.05,0:17:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只能保护森林
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.03,0:17:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 现在连这也做不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.24,0:17:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个无法守护任何人的没用家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.03,0:17:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才不是没用的人!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.63,0:17:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄...玄你帮我们打扫了院子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.35,0:17:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从翠手里保护了我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.63,0:17:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄可能讨厌人类
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.38,0:17:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是喜欢玄的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.43,0:17:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我也一定喜欢着向彩虹许愿的翠
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.74,0:18:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.79,0:18:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目老大
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.73,0:18:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在北边的森林里看到了可疑的影子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.18,0:18:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来通知一声
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.45,0:18:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以啊 给我们曲奇吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.13,0:18:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他比之前轻了好多
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.14,0:18:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果就这样融化了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.19,0:18:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄就会一直孤独一人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.44,0:18:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.93,0:18:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翠
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.58,0:18:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.50,0:18:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.38,0:19:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放手 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.65,0:19:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙的邪念化为了高热
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.89,0:19:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 如果在这里放走了她 又会...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.57,0:19:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.09,0:19:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.59,0:19:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这感觉 这是 翠的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.84,0:19:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄大人 三色的彩虹还没出来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.05,0:19:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快再下些雨吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.39,0:19:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊 翠 下雨会很冷的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.08,0:19:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.63,0:19:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.26,0:19:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不冷
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.26,0:19:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.73,0:19:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有你在我身边
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.88,0:19:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.85,0:19:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.73,0:19:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快放手 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.15,0:19:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的身体也会受不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.47,0:19:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.92,0:19:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄已经没多少妖力了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.09,0:19:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算让他们在一起 玄也可能就此消失的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.56,0:19:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放手 你的小命也会没了的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.06,0:20:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果怎么都不放手的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.78,0:20:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 住手!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.72,0:20:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.61,0:20:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也好冷啊 翠 好冷啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.61,0:20:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我们回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.22,0:20:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.58,0:20:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到你心灵的创伤愈合后
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.17,0:20:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再两个人一起等待彩虹吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.28,0:20:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是那么幸福啊 翠
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.23,0:20:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有你陪在我的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.82,0:20:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玄...大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.10,0:20:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.00,0:20:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.69,0:21:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们有好好回去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.27,0:21:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.77,0:21:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪可不像软弱的你那么弱小
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.09,0:21:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.39,0:21:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 我也不是先生想像的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.40,0:21:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,习惯于应对别离
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.46,0:21:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我还是会好好地珍惜重要的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.14,0:21:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 你说的话总是这么晦涩难懂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.62,0:21:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来我们现在是要去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.02,0:21:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去柴原啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.54,0:21:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想去埋下一些花的种子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.31,0:21:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然无法让彩虹出现
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.37,0:21:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就种下一些鲜花吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.55,0:21:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类 是喜欢花草的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.42,0:21:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪一定也是如此吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.11,0:22:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为花会诉说春天的来临
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.95,0:23:50.98,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(350,550)}{\4c&HD8F1E9&}妖怪退治 温泉旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.85,0:23:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要跟名取先生一起去温泉旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.62,0:23:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抽奖抽中了温泉双人游呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.72,0:23:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要和我一起呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.83,0:23:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为能看到同样风景的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.66,0:23:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只有你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.73,0:23:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我也要去 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.25,0:23:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸡蛋 鸡蛋 温泉鸡蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.42,0:23:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当当

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 少しだけ大人の色に染まる指先
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 指尖稍露成年的沧桑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 照れくさそうに そっと隠して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 你就害羞得将它悄悄收起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 頬杖ついた君 見つめてる視線の先に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 手托下巴的你将视线投向
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 小さな蕾が ゆらゆら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 那随风轻曳的小小花蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} ねぇ 僕なんて いまも迷いばかりで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 喂 现在的我仍迷茫依旧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} あの日贈った言葉 今さら思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 这才回想起 那日你的临别赠言
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「君色に未来染めて...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「将我的未来染成你的颜色...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ 聞いていてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 听我倾诉好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ わがままいいですか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 让我任性好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手に入れた途端に消えてしまいそう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}拥有的瞬间仿佛就会消散
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}言葉をくれませんか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不说点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あなたがいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}因为有你在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}それだけで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう世界が変わってしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我的世界就会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}モノトーンの景色が ほら 鮮やかに映る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}映入眼眸的单调景色也会光鲜亮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}いつのまにか 離れていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不知何时却已离开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手を繋いで歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}牵着手 向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}上手く愛せているかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}能够好好去爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あの空に聞いてみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}天空也许会回答
