[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.30,0:01:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从小开始 就常常...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.42,0:01:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会看见奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.24,0:01:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,河童?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.19,0:01:58.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水...水...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.21,0:02:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.80,0:02:41.80,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时雨与少女
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.45,0:02:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君 别忘了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.82,0:02:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.58,0:02:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶什么啊 今晚的试胆大会啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.92,0:02:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非去不可吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.09,0:02:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对这个没什么兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.37,0:02:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人数不够才拜托你的 稍微奉陪下总行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.72,0:03:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是你有什么其他重要的事?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.64,0:03:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒不是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.34,0:03:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旧校舍下周就要拆除了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.70,0:03:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年的试胆大会就是最后一次了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.32,0:03:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要来 我等着你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.71,0:03:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夜是妖怪们出没频繁的时段
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.79,0:03:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,办什么试胆大会 真的没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.57,0:03:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 来了啊 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.67,0:03:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 那是你家的猫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.76,0:03:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你会跟来啊?!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.91,0:03:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系 貌似很有趣的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.49,0:03:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是这种时候才需要保镖 不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.05,0:03:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是这么说啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.90,0:03:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚有没有听到那只猫发出了什么怪声
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.60,0:03:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不 是你的错觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.25,0:03:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.23,0:03:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝～对～!不要在大家面前说话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.55,0:03:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是爱瞎操心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.44,0:03:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么?!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.65,0:04:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好 知道啦 知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.42,0:04:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规则是 两人一组
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.71,0:04:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在二楼尽头的墙上写上名字再回来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.59,0:04:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次没有安排吓人的角色 所以大家放心地去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.33,0:04:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来用抽签 按1号到20号的顺序来决定组合
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.22,0:04:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 大家都来抽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.95,0:04:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这间校舍曾经流传过这么一个传说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.07,0:04:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从前有个很喜欢人类的年轻招福神明
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.32,0:04:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他假扮成小孩子到村子里来玩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.91,0:04:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.95,0:04:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个贪婪的商人为了扩张生意
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.95,0:04:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将那个神明监禁在地牢里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.96,0:05:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那天起 商人凭借福神的力量发起大财
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.61,0:05:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.40,0:05:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年轻神明在幽暗的地底悲伤不已 悲伤不已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.74,0:05:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他开始变得憎恨人类 最终变成了恶神
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.04,0:05:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商人最后家道中落
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.76,0:05:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来在那片变成不祥之地的土地上 建成了这间校舍
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.84,0:05:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年轻神明悲叹自己变成不祥的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.49,0:05:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说至今仍在这片土地上徘徊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.85,0:05:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要告诉我这个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.46,0:05:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.70,0:05:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 大家都抽完了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.23,0:05:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么一起把抽到的签亮出来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.66,0:05:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.37,0:05:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 少了一张
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.36,0:05:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 但数字是编到20号啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.54,0:05:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是说多了一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.90,0:05:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～?!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.85,0:06:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大...大家镇定 只是有人没报名就来了而已吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.52,0:06:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是执行委员你故意安排的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.20,0:06:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.88,0:06:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会是有人伸了两只手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.71,0:06:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么 在这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.77,0:06:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.72,0:06:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是刚刚笹田说的那家伙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.25,0:06:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不知道呢 若是的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.17,0:06:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可就是个令我察觉不到气息的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.21,0:06:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼哼 变得越来越有趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.13,0:06:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.79,0:06:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.80,0:06:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.91,0:06:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机会难得 还真希望能和女生一组啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.40,0:06:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.93,0:06:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然已经破烂不堪 但一想到要被拆除还是有点寂寞呐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.02,0:06:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.26,0:06:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像完全没有遇到其他人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.62,0:07:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 的确呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.59,0:07:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.15,0:07:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去哪里来着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.87,0:07:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.11,0:07:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一...一个人在干吗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.49,0:07:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...那什么 暗号是什么来着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.28,0:07:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.48,0:07:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒过来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.09,0:08:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 这张脸似乎在哪儿...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.53,0:08:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 也无关紧要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.19,0:08:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我弄成不洁之人 竟然还要剥夺我的住处
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.62,0:08:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.99,0:08:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样 人类都是些任意妄为的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.28,0:08:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君 怎么了 没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.37,0:08:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.84,0:08:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.51,0:08:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 这里一个人也没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.75,0:08:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 西村同学人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.93,0:08:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 有看到和我一组的北本同学吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.53,0:08:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微一没留神就走散了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.13,0:08:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.99,0:08:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先发的几组也都没回来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.73,0:08:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.61,0:08:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.15,0:09:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都被那家伙带走了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.45,0:09:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你在和谁说话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.22,0:09:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.45,0:09:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君 你看得见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.73,0:09:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候会做些奇怪的行为对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.37,0:09:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在空无一人的地方被吓一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.86,0:09:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明没人 却像对着什么说话似的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.20,0:09:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能看见什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.06,0:09:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难不成 是不属于这个世上的东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.97,0:09:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.73,0:09:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会帮你保密的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.37,0:09:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿不愿意帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.29,0:09:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.94,0:09:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确实看得见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.42,0:09:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.99,0:09:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.23,0:09:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...这家伙原来不是妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.06,0:09:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.23,0:10:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.43,0:10:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校舍四周都布了结界 出不去了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.14,0:10:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 有其他出口吗 帮忙找找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.32,0:10:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么! 真会差遣人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.55,0:10:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这...这副样子是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.30,0:10:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样比较方便吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.13,0:10:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像...有个像躲避球样的东西飞了过来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.73,0:10:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.03,0:10:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.76,0:11:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人似乎是躲避球部的人 来拿飞进来的球
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.36,0:11:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 原来我们学校有躲避球部啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.39,0:11:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我去看看情况
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.02,0:11:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃脱之前我会照顾你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.57,0:11:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.84,0:11:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉有点傲慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.16,0:11:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因...因为她是主将吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.81,0:11:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是人类 人类
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.96,0:11:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类 是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.25,0:11:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来还有剩下的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.85,0:11:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得快点报告时雨大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.00,0:11:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂!低级球怪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.87,0:11:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 被看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.39,0:11:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快...快逃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.84,0:11:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边 这边
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.60,0:11:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初中的时候 因为地方上的活动
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.46,0:11:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我参加过这里的试胆大会
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.76,0:11:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是哭着跑完了整个校舍
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.04,0:11:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家后才发现把重要的东西给丢了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.92,0:11:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慌慌忙忙地一个人回到校舍里寻找
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.29,0:12:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时非常害怕 又沮丧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.86,0:12:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是却完全找不到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.11,0:12:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.73,0:12:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从刚才起就在干些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.88,0:12:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的护身符...掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.47,0:12:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我非常重要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.07,0:12:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点找 然后赶快回去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.96,0:12:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 那...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.36,0:12:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后我依然没放弃寻找 但还是没找到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.79,0:12:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就在不知所措的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.09,0:12:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.41,0:12:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.87,0:12:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.30,0:13:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 都快放弃了的说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.56,0:13:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是我母亲的遗物来着
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.93,0:13:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但 那个树枝是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.69,0:13:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这样的不洁之人是不能触及洁净之物的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.54,0:13:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了吧 你快点回去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.11,0:13:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不洁? 那是在说什...么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.37,0:13:24.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种说话方式 还有那种氛围
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.93,0:13:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想那难道就是妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.09,0:13:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而后就调查了很多 知道了那个年轻神明的传说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.73,0:13:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也知道了「不洁」就是指被玷污了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.90,0:13:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后我每天都会来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.76,0:13:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我想好好谢谢你 出来吧」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.40,0:13:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「你不是不洁之人」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.50,0:13:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都想这么对他说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.19,0:13:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他始终没有现身
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.88,0:14:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 如果夏目君你能看见的话 想请你帮个忙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.46,0:14:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就快要被拆毁了 觉得这或许是最后的机会了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.00,0:14:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 刚刚那样跟你说话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.61,0:14:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别介意
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.39,0:14:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君 你真的看不见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.50,0:14:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.39,0:14:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.33,0:14:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都没有回来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.07,0:14:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.80,0:14:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?夏目君?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.47,0:14:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.32,0:14:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.10,0:14:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然手下都是下等妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.05,0:14:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但老大却意外的是个大人物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.14,0:15:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且似乎友人帐上有他的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.43,0:15:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那妖怪的名字是「时雨」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.09,0:15:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时雨?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.00,0:15:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太麻烦了 还是快点回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.59,0:15:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是强力结界 但是我的话还是能打破的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.28,0:15:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.69,0:15:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家呢 他们怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.43,0:15:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管不着了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.17,0:15:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不怎么喜欢人类吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.81,0:15:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常做到的小时候的梦不是很痛苦么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.72,0:15:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...可能确实是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.93,0:15:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我也不能放着他们不管
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.07,0:15:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能做到的事 我还是想去做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.34,0:15:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君 你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.98,0:15:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君 没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.30,0:15:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.79,0:15:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手下们开始集合了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.65,0:16:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙在屋顶 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.83,0:16:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屋顶? 那家伙?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.65,0:16:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 是那个人么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.38,0:16:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪 笹田
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.66,0:16:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去见那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.28,0:16:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在吧 在这屋顶上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.18,0:16:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.22,0:16:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想告诉他
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.27,0:16:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个护身符对我来说有多么重要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.32,0:16:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他帮我找到 我有多么高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.04,0:16:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.93,0:16:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 把笹田带到安全的地方 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.66,0:16:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想干什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.66,0:16:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他住手 把名字还给他并说服他
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.62,0:16:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏...夏目君!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.31,0:17:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 还想着去哪里了 没想到你自己来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.31,0:17:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.97,0:17:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.21,0:17:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌人类
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.01,0:17:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我变成这样卑贱的妖怪 像嘲弄般地随意踏入这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.87,0:17:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至还想夺走我的住处
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.75,0:17:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不会把他们还回去的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.51,0:17:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要看着你们的父母悲痛欲绝的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.42,0:17:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个女孩子想见你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.70,0:17:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留在校舍里的另一个女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.49,0:17:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你不愿见她
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.45,0:18:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不会明白的 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.01,0:18:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.78,0:18:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是铃子的血亲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.37,0:18:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要使用友人帐让我服从不就行了么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.91,0:18:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是善良呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.69,0:18:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就简单了 我把名字归还于你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.66,0:18:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.53,0:18:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要解放
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.44,0:18:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个早就被玷污的名字任你处置就好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.42,0:18:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「时雨大人 归还汝名」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.97,0:19:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一个支撑了少女心灵的善良之人的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.83,0:19:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你出来吧 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.49,0:19:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 又来了 烦人的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.12,0:19:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想给你道谢 无论怎样都想
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.43,0:19:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一次想早些赶她走而帮忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.65,0:19:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一天每一天不厌其烦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.87,0:19:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么古怪的生物
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.94,0:19:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦触碰到不洁的我 果然还是会被玷污的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.77,0:19:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 只要一次就好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.35,0:19:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.72,0:19:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要见过一次的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.84,0:19:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.91,0:20:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也就不会再来了...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.62,0:20:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 夏目 我要走了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.73,0:20:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经厌倦了诅咒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.09,0:20:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时雨大人 笹田她说过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.10,0:20:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时雨大人您根本不是不净之人 是您拯救了她
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.32,0:20:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不相信人类的话也没关系 不过请您
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.05,0:20:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少对笹田所说的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.30,0:20:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君 你没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.49,0:20:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起了呢 人类的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.50,0:20:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不畏惧不洁的我的人 就只有你和铃子了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.52,0:20:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.99,0:21:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.27,0:21:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.08,0:21:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君 昨天晚上我...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.04,0:21:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 到底怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.93,0:21:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家竟然都在屋顶上睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.55,0:21:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.87,0:21:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.67,0:21:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田 其实那一瞬间我看到了轻抚你的时雨大人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.09,0:21:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了他那颗想要交流的心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.00,0:21:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定也感觉到什么了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.65,0:23:50.17,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,540)}心色的车票
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.48,0:23:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子外婆留下的一张车票
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.99,0:23:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,循着车票探寻到的古旧车站
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.21,0:23:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里的是一只妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.29,0:23:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很迟钝的家伙啊 别管他不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.55,0:23:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫三斗 拜托了 我想见三棱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.90,0:22:12.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.90,0:22:12.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.94,0:22:19.90,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.94,0:22:19.90,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.90,0:22:26.37,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.90,0:22:26.37,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.37,0:22:33.30,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.37,0:22:33.30,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.06,0:22:44.35,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.06,0:22:44.35,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.35,0:22:48.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.35,0:22:48.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.74,0:22:58.20,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.74,0:22:58.20,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.20,0:23:05.84,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.20,0:23:05.84,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.84,0:23:12.90,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.84,0:23:12.90,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.90,0:23:20.26,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.90,0:23:20.26,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.26,0:23:26.98,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.26,0:23:26.98,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
