[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.13,0:02:56.13,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1}浮春之乡
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.92,0:24:15.96,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1\pos(220,296)}虚伪的友人
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}なくした温もりを一つ一つ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色取り取りの君のカケラは　笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出の作り方も　まるでうまくならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れに　タダ身を任せて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこに行けばいい　この闇の先でまだ
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな　君のカケラ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}なくした温もりを一つ一つ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色取り取りの君のカケラは　笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出の作り方も　まるでうまくならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れに　タダ身を任せて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこに行けばいい　この闇の先でまだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな　君のカケラ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.96,0:01:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看啊老师
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.65,0:01:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八原那里好像光的海洋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.69,0:01:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管那些了  还是赶紧回家给我吃那团子吧  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.76,0:01:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师真是贪吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.21,0:01:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.02,0:02:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.38,0:02:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,味道真香  我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.37,0:02:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白色肥猪来袭了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.90,0:02:18.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们说什么！  吃掉你们啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.04,0:02:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手吧老师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.49,0:02:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是夏目大人和肥猫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.04,0:02:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肥猫…肥猫…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.06,0:02:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是斑大人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.84,0:02:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  这是给我们带来的礼物对吧  谢谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.78,0:02:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个再这样闹的话可是又要被那个和尚驱除了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.95,0:02:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为最近几天听不见寺庙那里的念经声了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.84,0:02:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个和尚死了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.97,0:02:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了死了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.95,0:02:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼的父亲怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.40,0:03:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼知道我能看见妖怪  是我重要的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.85,0:03:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  西村  下节课是体育课吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.50,0:03:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  要跑马拉松呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.95,0:03:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.26,0:03:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.23,0:03:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么  回头见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.61,0:03:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  回头见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.23,0:03:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他自己也能感受到妖怪的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.50,0:03:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也能模糊的看到一些妖怪的影子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.01,0:03:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样什么都没有问就回来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.35,0:03:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时不知道该怎么去问他
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.47,0:03:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  那家伙不是知道你能看得见妖怪的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.99,0:03:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他的父亲生病或有何不测的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.06,0:03:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得在别人面前也不太好问这些
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.10,0:03:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.59,0:03:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…有关朋友的家人的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.81,0:03:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以涉足到什么地步…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.05,0:03:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事我才不知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.59,0:03:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也对呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.93,0:04:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候  我没有能闲聊家常的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.59,0:04:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  至今还不知这时应当如何把握分寸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.00,0:04:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.74,0:04:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁也不在呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.81,0:04:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把名字…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.46,0:04:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的持有者夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.24,0:04:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要我归还你的名字吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.69,0:04:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  现在我要去上学  下次再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.38,0:05:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.76,0:05:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  我老爸的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.82,0:05:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说最近都没有听到念经声了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.75,0:05:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为去总寺院进行仪式
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.79,0:05:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以一个月都不在家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.47,0:05:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像出差一样  偶尔也会有这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.63,0:05:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.94,0:05:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在担心我吗  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.06,0:05:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.80,0:05:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你现在是一个人生活吗  会很辛苦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.12,0:05:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不尽如此  安静一点也好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.63,0:05:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.07,0:05:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.44,0:05:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就到这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.08,0:05:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.87,0:05:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.29,0:05:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.92,0:06:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把名字…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.36,0:06:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里就没问题了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.11,0:06:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护吾之人  显其名
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.54,0:06:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.91,0:06:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种地方呆站着干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.19,0:06:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.15,0:06:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有她的名字…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.49,0:06:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.13,0:06:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又擅自打算将名字还给他们了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.29,0:06:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.12,0:06:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混小子  这么随便地把名字还给他们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.40,0:06:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在到我手上之前
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.93,0:06:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐上的名字都要被你送完了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.49,0:06:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0020,0000,,蓝调的牛肉盖饭
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.15,0:07:00.37,small,NTP,0020,0000,0000,,为什么会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.37,0:07:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  那和尚好不容易不在了却又来了一个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.77,0:07:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要到何时才能在八原享受和平生活
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.01,0:07:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.00,0:07:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白肥猪又袭来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.68,0:07:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是斑大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.60,0:07:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这群杂鱼在吵嚷什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.74,0:07:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为那家伙复苏了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.00,0:07:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.27,0:07:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有只不知是何时流落到这附近
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.02,0:07:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四处散发瘴气的妖怪对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.59,0:07:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有过有过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.75,0:07:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有过一只那样的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.23,0:07:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱小的妖怪只要碰到那瘴气就会患病倒下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.63,0:07:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给大家造成很大的困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.22,0:07:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,困扰困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.95,0:07:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说他输给了夏目玲子名字也被夺走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.74,0:07:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后应该一直在深山中沉睡才对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.91,0:07:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子吗  依旧那么过分呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.52,0:07:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙的瘴气又飘过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.07,0:07:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实…那家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.67,0:08:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天真是失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.07,0:08:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的持有者夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.78,0:08:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你的名字没有写在友人帐上面吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.00,0:08:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  想要归还的并不是我的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.66,0:08:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是我哥哥的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.19,0:08:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.23,0:08:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的哥哥曾是是浮春之乡的居民
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.69,0:08:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浮春之乡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.86,0:08:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起浮春之乡  不是现世无法看到的梦幻之乡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.42,0:08:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的居民为什么会来这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.95,0:08:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个就…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.16,0:08:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是听说多年来一直在寻找回去的方法而到处旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.51,0:08:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浮春之乡是一个全年都百花齐放
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.80,0:08:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸟鸣声从未断绝的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.38,0:08:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般是与这个世界没有任何交集的彼岸之乡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.21,0:08:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但会因节日庆典什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.88,0:08:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔有机会与这个世界相连接
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.59,0:09:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被某处传来的神乐所吸引的我和哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.01,0:09:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一不留神来到了现世
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.42,0:09:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥和我为了寻找浮春之乡的入口而开始旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.36,0:09:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年复一年…日复一日…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.30,0:09:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那途中哥哥患上了疾病  开始散发出瘴气
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.81,0:09:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也因那瘴气的影响而变得衰弱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.68,0:09:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到这些的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.44,0:09:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我沉睡于某座山上的神木洞里之后
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.00,0:09:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随后便一个人不知道去了哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.03,0:09:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后时日流逝
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.30,0:09:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借由神木的灵力而恢复起来的我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.32,0:09:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,循着传闻追寻哥哥来到了这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.16,0:09:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  听这一带的妖怪说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.06,0:09:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥被夏目大人夺取了名字
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.77,0:09:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自那之后就消声匿迹了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.84,0:10:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会来找我这友人帐的拥有者吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.30,0:10:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但夺取了你哥哥的名字的不是我而是我祖母
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.49,0:10:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道他长相的我并不能召出他
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.38,0:10:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.88,0:10:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道他长相的我便可以召出他对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.25,0:10:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.34,0:10:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  把友人帐给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.00,0:10:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.03,0:10:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.72,0:10:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三篠
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.97,0:10:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚在这里闻到了妖怪的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.74,0:10:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.85,0:10:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是碰巧路过而已
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.74,0:10:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这河岸附近有好几只低级的妖怪被吃掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.65,0:10:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正寻找着那犯人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.76,0:10:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  那不是三篠吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.74,0:10:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑  难不成是你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.67,0:10:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的地盘吃了低级的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.53,0:11:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  突然这么说我  不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.66,0:11:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说了作为美食家的我怎么会吃那种东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.71,0:11:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那难不成是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.05,0:11:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  隐居在那座山里的家伙就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.69,0:11:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你遇到的妖怪的哥哥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.54,0:11:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙出现的地方是田沼家对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.13,0:11:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为和尚不在  所以才会在院内徘徊的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.94,0:11:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.29,0:11:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里？你在哪里？我会带你去的  夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.61,0:11:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.99,0:11:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你在找什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.81,0:11:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对夏目做什么的话我可不会饶过你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.12,0:12:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铁锈？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.32,0:12:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是过去寺院的图纸吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.61,0:12:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼他早退了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.34,0:12:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上确实是来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.05,0:12:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是头很痛就回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.43,0:12:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头痛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.30,0:12:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.42,0:12:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是因为那个妖怪的瘴气引起的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.45,0:13:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是个弱不经风的家伙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.36,0:13:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很担心他
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.78,0:13:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.25,0:13:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.43,0:13:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.71,0:13:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道去医院了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.62,0:13:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  能嗅到妖怪的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.65,0:13:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.69,0:13:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…这所寺院？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.15,0:13:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然如今虽只有这般大小
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.53,0:13:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但曾经可是有着大伽蓝的大寺院呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.53,0:13:34.09,Banner,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}伽蓝：修行僧人在雨季等时期的休息处
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.39,0:13:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在寺院领地内的神社每年都会供奉神乐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.01,0:13:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神乐？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.01,0:13:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经由神乐之舞
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.56,0:13:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常少有的会打开通往彼岸世界的大门
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.63,0:13:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.56,0:13:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神乐堂…是在这
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.29,0:13:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边是八原的边角了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.48,0:13:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.89,0:13:55.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.03,0:13:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…稍微…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.49,0:14:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爹现在不在家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.16,0:14:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生病的时候一个人也很辛苦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.90,0:14:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.33,0:14:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不太想待在家里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.45,0:14:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么客气
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.97,0:14:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说田沼病倒了  夏目可是非常担心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.33,0:14:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这边吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.54,0:14:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.11,0:14:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.47,0:14:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是中瘴气了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.98,0:14:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就放它在一边睡着好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.07,0:14:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师没有事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.98,0:14:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别拿我和那些低级妖怪来比较
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.32,0:14:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们抓紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.70,0:14:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有种不详的预感
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.91,0:14:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接近了  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.94,0:14:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.27,0:14:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.89,0:14:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.80,0:15:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.92,0:15:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.98,0:15:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  玲子已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.17,0:15:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我的血让周围的妖怪们紧张不已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.80,0:15:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了很对不起各位的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.80,0:15:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是浮春之乡的入口只对其住民起反应
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.12,0:15:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才伤害自己的身体吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.25,0:15:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但看来那已没有什么必要了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.44,0:15:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.41,0:15:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说你这是要放弃了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.82,0:15:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有只自称是你妹妹的妖怪在四处找寻你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.87,0:15:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会  那不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.42,0:15:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妹妹很早以前就过世了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.65,0:15:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.78,0:15:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受到神乐的吸引不知不觉地带着妹妹出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.98,0:15:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果水土不服  让幼妹客死异乡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.62,0:15:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后便一直独自一人彷徨于世
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.18,0:16:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在要放弃回村子去的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.96,0:16:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇见了玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.49,0:16:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候被修理的很惨吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.75,0:16:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是什么紧要的比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.84,0:16:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我输了就将名字交给了她
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.30,0:16:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但玲子她终究没有召唤过我就去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.60,0:16:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后我在山中找了个洞穴开始沉睡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.42,0:16:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉时光荏苒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.96,0:16:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我苏醒过来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.29,0:16:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现那旧寺庙已经修葺一新
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.89,0:16:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼和他的爸爸搬过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.63,0:16:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有段时间曾无法接近
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.50,0:16:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这些天来未能感觉到住持的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.79,0:16:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就决定去看看了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.69,0:16:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就找到这幅旧地图了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.62,0:16:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会来到这片大地
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.27,0:16:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是听说过去寺院领地内曾开启过入口
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.38,0:16:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕那就是神乐堂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.06,0:17:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这应该是火灾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.84,0:17:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若能留下些建筑的话还好办…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.21,0:17:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今这种样子…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.42,0:17:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这样一来那个女妖怪是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.40,0:17:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那恐怕是被浮春之乡所通缉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.07,0:17:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫做茶虞女的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.27,0:17:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许认为只要能找到我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.98,0:17:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天就能回到村子里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.61,0:17:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.74,0:17:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会想要友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.82,0:17:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算利用你来打开进入村子的大门
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.33,0:17:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是三筱所说的吃掉小妖怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.06,0:17:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是那个茶虞女吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.90,0:17:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就赶在她找过来之前
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.51,0:17:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,替玲子把名字还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.20,0:17:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护吾之人  显其名
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.47,0:17:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还汝之名  铁轮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.07,0:18:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请收下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.29,0:18:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是伐倒几株花木就被通缉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.75,0:18:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怨
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.58,0:18:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罪人之血无法打开门
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.70,0:18:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.84,0:18:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐已经没用了  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.62,0:18:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我已经得到这家伙的血了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.65,0:18:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神乐堂烧毁后养育起来的树木起反应了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.31,0:18:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大门就要开启了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.18,0:18:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就能回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.18,0:19:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要给让她看一看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.14,0:19:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让玲子一览这风景
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.99,0:19:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙全身生锈了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.20,0:19:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是惹人厌
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.47,0:19:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不跟先来的人打声招呼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.23,0:19:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能看见我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.00,0:19:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他妖怪间的话题人物就是你了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.20,0:19:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怕我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.69,0:19:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是很厉害的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.61,0:20:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的故乡是那么好的地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.08,0:20:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  那可是相当漂亮的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.77,0:20:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你还要放弃返回家乡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.07,0:20:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的身躯即便是回去了也维持不长久
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.97,0:20:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在只不过是彷徨着寻找自己的葬身之处
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.26,0:20:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你要不要和我比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.05,0:20:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头剪刀布
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.96,0:20:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.14,0:20:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头剪刀布
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.66,0:20:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.90,0:20:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头剪刀布
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.79,0:20:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.90,0:20:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  这样一来就是我赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.82,0:20:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是我的仆人了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.09,0:20:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么把你的名字写下来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.73,0:20:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  找到了的话  也要通知我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.65,0:20:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通往你故乡的入口
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.80,0:21:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让我也想要看看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.21,0:21:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真有那么美丽的地方的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.84,0:21:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么愿意跟我结伴同行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.56,0:21:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然那么厌恶人类的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.53,0:21:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我一起去浮春之乡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.17,0:21:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要跟我一起去吗  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.19,0:21:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子的孙子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.28,0:21:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  对我而言这边才是最重要的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.20,0:21:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铁轮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.21,0:21:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.35,0:21:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你有关系很好的人类朋友嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.37,0:21:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.76,0:21:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  你去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.63,0:21:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你倒下了  就很担心…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.08,0:21:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.04,0:21:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实是家里有奇怪的妖怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.30,0:21:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙已经离开了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.02,0:21:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是胖太帮忙退治了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.32,0:22:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  是回到他的故乡了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.17,0:22:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是危险的家伙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.68,0:22:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是坏妖怪哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.99,0:22:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.98,0:22:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正犹豫该不该去找夏目商量
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.34,0:22:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怕会把你也卷进来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.41,0:22:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但若是能早点告诉你就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.70,0:22:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.63,0:24:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人总有不想被他人知道的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.73,0:24:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是夏目吧  骗人说能看到妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.32,0:24:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会知道那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.58,0:24:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这自以为是的混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.38,0:24:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让我吃掉你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.13,0:24:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟那孩子相遇  让我想起了你
