[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.04,0:01:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会看见那种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.78,0:01:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我很奇怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.08,0:01:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.57,0:01:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体不舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.69,0:01:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 你是住在这附近的孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.87,0:02:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常看到你总是一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.92,0:02:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.02,0:02:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你也能看见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.16,0:02:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.39,0:02:18.44,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八原的怪人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.50,0:02:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 请问夏目是在这个班吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.08,0:02:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.20,0:02:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哪一个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.08,0:02:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道在不在啊 那家伙的存在感很薄弱的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.85,0:02:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 在的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.22,0:02:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 就是靠窗的那个
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.19,0:02:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.77,0:02:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏～目～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.44,0:02:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.40,0:02:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.32,0:02:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有客人～哦!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.31,0:02:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.19,0:02:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不见了 刚刚还在问你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.24,0:02:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.20,0:03:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...没怎么见过的脸孔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.91,0:03:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思啊 把你叫醒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.80,0:03:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.14,0:03:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你还真能睡啊 晚上睡不安稳吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.57,0:03:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.23,0:03:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有烦恼的话可以和我们说哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.59,0:03:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.39,0:03:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你们几个 上课铃响过了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.92,0:03:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好凶哦!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.71,0:03:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从继承了外婆的友人帐后
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.52,0:03:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为拿回名字的妖怪们就开始纷纷找上我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.42,0:03:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与外婆相反
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.76,0:03:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一天天归还它们视如生命般重要的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.60,0:03:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,累死人了...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.96,0:04:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.81,0:04:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我～回～来～了～ 哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.29,0:04:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生 你去哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.09,0:04:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就稍微出去了下...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.48,0:04:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生你一身酒气
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.12,0:04:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别靠近我 呆一边去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.59,0:04:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要这么冷漠嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.27,0:04:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有给你带礼物哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.94,0:04:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼物?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.75,0:04:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.22,0:04:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家去吧 下次别再被那只傻猫抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.19,0:04:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会遭报应的！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.41,0:04:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志 我出去买东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.41,0:04:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.68,0:04:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路上小心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.94,0:04:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是休息天
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.23,0:04:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志你也不要老呆在家里 出去玩玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.92,0:04:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里交到新朋友了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.95,0:04:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 大家都待我很好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.42,0:04:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 那我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.71,0:05:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 是虫...子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.10,0:05:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无视无视
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.33,0:05:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初次见面 您是夏目大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.12,0:05:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰您了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.46,0:05:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要随便...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.52,0:05:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰您了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.36,0:05:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要随便进来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.48,0:05:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是来要回名字的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.30,0:05:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 这样友人帐变得越来越薄了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.87,0:05:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏我还一直期待能来个厉害角色把这傲慢小鬼一口吞掉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.26,0:05:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 蠢猫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.68,0:05:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么来的尽是些小喽罗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.01,0:05:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是搞喽罗军团吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.27,0:05:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子你个笨蛋 你个...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.43,0:05:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 我们是来拜托持有强大妖力的夏目大人的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.62,0:05:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还请帮帮我们吧 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.45,0:05:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想请夏目大人帮我们驱除一个人类
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.23,0:05:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱除人类?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.09,0:06:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近在我们住的八原来了个自以为是的驱妖师
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.21,0:06:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是驱妖 那人类似乎只对尝试自己的妖力乐在其中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.37,0:06:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明明只是好玩有趣地生活着而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.29,0:06:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 真的有能够驱除妖怪的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.08,0:06:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有啊 低头
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.23,0:06:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.17,0:06:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也许不知道 要驱除人类的话会产生很多问题
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.80,0:06:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,办不到呢 抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.07,0:06:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.43,0:06:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不帮忙呢 不是很好玩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.49,0:06:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教训人类可是我的专长哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.27,0:06:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会惹麻烦的 先生你就别管了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.97,0:06:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱妖人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.90,0:06:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就表示那个人相信有妖怪的存在吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.15,0:06:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定 也能看到的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.08,0:06:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也看得见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.79,0:06:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我...一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.92,0:06:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿咻嘿咻
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.03,0:07:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.74,0:07:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.19,0:07:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还在啊 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.85,0:07:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在呢 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.55,0:07:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.07,0:07:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退下退下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.05,0:07:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退下退下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.81,0:07:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人要过去了 过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.07,0:07:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退下 退下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.93,0:07:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你们...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.62,0:07:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开 让开
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.32,0:07:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 听我说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.26,0:07:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 为了表示我们的诚意
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.45,0:07:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们接送您上下学吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.89,0:07:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不要! 麻烦!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.76,0:07:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 这就是学校吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.51,0:07:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校学校
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.67,0:07:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.17,0:07:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏～目～ 啊锵锵锵
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.57,0:07:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏～目～ 啊锵锵锵
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.30,0:07:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.15,0:07:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,字写的不错 你会念么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.79,0:07:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「祝」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.75,0:07:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,26)}{\fs23}译注:实际是诅咒的「呪」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.91,0:07:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个家伙在干些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.37,0:08:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.20,0:08:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.59,0:08:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.22,0:08:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们等您很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.28,0:08:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 快回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.04,0:08:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.40,0:08:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先听听你们要拜托的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.13,0:08:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 实在太感谢您啦 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.76,0:08:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.59,0:08:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么对方是什么样的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.63,0:08:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是突然释放出强大的灵波
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.21,0:08:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为无法靠近 所以不清楚他的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.92,0:08:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过确实是人类的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.04,0:08:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.27,0:08:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是跟妖怪们有仇吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.47,0:08:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因被妖怪们打扰而无法融入社会...之类的?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.73,0:08:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是不能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.81,0:08:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒不如说 与其和这些妖怪 我更想和那个人谈一谈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.62,0:09:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 又来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.54,0:09:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 你有说「你也能看见吗?」 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.29,0:09:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐也能看见吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.89,0:09:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很奇怪吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.65,0:09:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.10,0:09:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.20,0:09:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是人类 有人类啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.17,0:09:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.85,0:09:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是来赶我们走吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.04,0:09:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.19,0:09:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.16,0:09:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你们搞错了 这位大人是...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.46,0:09:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是小喽罗 差不多自己也能驱除了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.02,0:09:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种程度的家伙 甩开就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.25,0:09:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不快点的话 脑浆可要从鼻孔和耳朵里被吸走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.95,0:09:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 NO
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.56,0:09:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 你们这群性骚扰妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.79,0:09:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性骚扰?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.14,0:10:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.29,0:10:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是性感的花样美男啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.29,0:10:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,26)}{\fs23}译注:猫先生的冷笑话 原指sexual harassment(性骚扰)
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.80,0:10:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快让他们住手 你这只假猫！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.13,0:10:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个...是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.79,0:10:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 好像有声音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.07,0:10:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么东西过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.24,0:10:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了 是那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.06,0:10:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.89,0:10:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 抓紧了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.94,0:10:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底发生什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.37,0:10:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵力强大的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.24,0:10:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能发出净化妖怪的灵波
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.38,0:10:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 有人不知从何处向我们释放了灵波
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.12,0:10:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.59,0:10:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,净化的灵波
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.50,0:10:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 都被消灭了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.65,0:10:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是被吓跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.85,0:10:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.28,0:11:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这里也被净化了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.09,0:11:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,低级的家伙们暂时没办法回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.39,0:11:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被赶出栖身之地了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.50,0:11:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无预兆的攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.90,0:11:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真够独断专行的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.31,0:11:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么样的人...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.99,0:11:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 有干劲了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.02,0:11:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大胆去做吧 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.61,0:11:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.63,0:11:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不是暂时回不来了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.27,0:11:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万岁 万岁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.93,0:11:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俩是中级妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.64,0:11:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你们不会自己想想办法吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.04,0:11:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.67,0:11:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.14,0:11:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉和妖怪越扯越深了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.70,0:11:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太接近它们的话 又要...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.61,0:11:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.08,0:11:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脸色不好哦 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.62,0:11:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.75,0:12:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的视线
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.03,0:12:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 你们认不认识刚刚经过的那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.42,0:12:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是一班的田沼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.80,0:12:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.08,0:12:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那家伙 上次来打听你的那个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.70,0:12:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像最近才搬到八原的古庙里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.39,0:12:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八原?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.18,0:12:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.09,0:12:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道...是那个田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.76,0:12:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到的东西可能并不存在
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.93,0:12:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独自一人走在这不安定的世界中的那份恐惧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.68,0:12:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人能够理解
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.78,0:12:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和说好的不一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.41,0:12:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下个月该轮到你们照顾他了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.10,0:12:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家也只是勉强糊口而已
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.76,0:12:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他还总说些让人毛骨悚然的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.03,0:12:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么看到奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.88,0:13:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.67,0:13:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说我不是家人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.38,0:13:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然的确是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.13,0:13:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很寂寞吗 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.75,0:13:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.38,0:13:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为夏目会来 所以我不寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.19,0:13:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我不是一个人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.74,0:13:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐也看得见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.03,0:13:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.01,0:13:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是一个人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.72,0:13:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 这不是隔壁的贵志吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.55,0:13:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 一个人在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.68,0:13:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.24,0:13:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到的东西也许并不存在
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.32,0:13:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种...不安定的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.52,0:14:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 你怎么了 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.28,0:14:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.25,0:14:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走开!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.69,0:14:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.98,0:14:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.11,0:14:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走开!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.88,0:14:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是住在八原附近 知道地址吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.62,0:14:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.52,0:14:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到夏目你会对某个人感兴趣 真是少见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.41,0:14:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.33,0:14:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.28,0:14:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的确和田沼在某方面有些相像
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.07,0:14:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢一个人独处 会突然慌张不安
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.86,0:14:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像看到了可怕的东西一样 突然铁青着脸低下头去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.53,0:14:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个驱妖人 恐怕是田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.85,0:14:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼大概能看见
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.36,0:14:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 对我来说 他是我第一个同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.34,0:14:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.32,0:14:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.22,0:14:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 中级的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.50,0:14:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们中招了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.92,0:14:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不偏不倚地...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.37,0:14:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱妖人又来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.71,0:14:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 大概还在森林里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.71,0:15:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.45,0:15:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 只要像这样 吸收土地的能量休息一下的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.02,0:15:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.31,0:15:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能看到的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.30,0:15:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会做出这么过分的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.81,0:15:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然它们也不全都是好人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.01,0:15:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.40,0:15:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.92,0:15:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 有什么东西过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.46,0:15:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.83,0:15:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.25,0:15:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参见夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.69,0:15:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.55,0:15:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傲慢的样子和铃子一模一样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.68,0:15:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您带着友人帐吧 请把名字还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.67,0:15:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉 能不能稍后再说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.16,0:15:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在有点忙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.04,0:15:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点忙?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.60,0:15:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要去驱除人类
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.75,0:15:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.95,0:15:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 那让我三篠来帮忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.99,0:15:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然被夺走了名字
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.06,0:16:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果一次都没服侍过主人 那也太无趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.04,0:16:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.23,0:16:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前的....
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.53,0:16:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前几日我的家臣好像是承蒙您的搭救呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.70,0:16:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人的确要做好事呢 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.85,0:16:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生你就闭嘴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.76,0:16:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 居然能使唤三篠这样的人物
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.39,0:16:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.14,0:16:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强大无敌的友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.07,0:16:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用不着你们一一附和
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.38,0:16:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三篠大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.44,0:16:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人的敌人就潜伏在这森林里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.97,0:16:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请您惩治
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.35,0:16:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.83,0:16:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等...等等
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.90,0:16:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.77,0:16:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 糟了 糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.56,0:16:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对如此强力的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.24,0:16:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱妖人...田沼他也许会被杀死
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.03,0:16:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得抢先找到他才行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.37,0:16:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.41,0:17:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下 停下 停下 停下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.46,0:17:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我停下!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.73,0:17:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 快命令它 叫它名字
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.56,0:17:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 三篠!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.93,0:17:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.40,0:17:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这朽木不可雕的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.15,0:17:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是笨死了!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.91,0:17:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要名字还在友人帐上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.04,0:17:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你下命令就能阻止的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.55,0:17:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说...说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.05,0:17:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.66,0:17:47.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.49,0:17:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是驱妖人的真面目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.88,0:17:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在 夏目大人 快给他最后一击
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.78,0:17:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一击 最后一击
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.39,0:17:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 确定是这个人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.43,0:18:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个味道 没有错
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.99,0:18:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.93,0:18:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.81,0:18:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人在自言自语些什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.70,0:18:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶!?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.23,0:18:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看...看不见...妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.65,0:18:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是最近才搬到这八原的寺庙里的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.58,0:18:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我的儿子是个稍微有点敏感的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.75,0:18:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因时常受到影响而搞坏了身体
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.21,0:18:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以在听说这一带因妖怪出没而闻名后
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.77,0:18:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了能让他静养 算是在到处净灵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.15,0:18:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是图个安心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.90,0:18:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,图...图个安心...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.77,0:18:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明拥有那样的力量 可是却看不见我们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.51,0:18:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与其说是灵力妖力 倒不如说那是法力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.67,0:18:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是与生俱来 而是在修行中不知不觉间积累的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.34,0:18:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以现在还看不见妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.88,0:18:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 这里的妖怪都不会做什么坏事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.47,0:18:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还请您手下留情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.46,0:19:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你能看见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.05,0:19:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 不用回答也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.23,0:19:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有想说的话 欢迎随时过来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.52,0:19:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不好你能和我的儿子谈得来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.80,0:19:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿子?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.50,0:19:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主持 您贵姓
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.53,0:19:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我姓田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.94,0:19:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.66,0:19:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说你还是很偏爱妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.77,0:19:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不能说是偏爱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.28,0:19:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是交谈过后渐渐了解了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.28,0:19:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候 有个变成人形来和我说话的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.32,0:19:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时还是小孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.72,0:20:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种好意的行为却让我非常受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.08,0:20:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过现在回想来...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.10,0:20:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.81,0:20:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是无论如何都想和你说说话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.83,0:20:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使如此
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.45,0:20:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能遇见她 真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.08,0:20:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.94,0:20:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能看见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.51,0:20:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看得见吗 操场上那些奇怪的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.19,0:20:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.54,0:20:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一瞬间感觉似乎看到了两个奇怪的影子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.20,0:20:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是一直以来的错觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.70,0:20:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常会看到些影子 察觉到些气息
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.28,0:20:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起跟你说了奇怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.14,0:20:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我听说一个叫夏目的家伙似乎偶尔也会看到些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.79,0:20:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以想和你认识一下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.89,0:20:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 大概 是我的错觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.58,0:20:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看得见
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.36,0:20:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些非常奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.73,0:21:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 要替我保密哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.55,0:21:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 搞不好是我们两个都很奇怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.55,0:21:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.93,0:21:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.02,0:21:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知如何表达 但最近似乎开始明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.87,0:21:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是人类还是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.05,0:21:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要付出真心去对待 就毫无分别
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.86,0:21:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人会觉得寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.18,0:21:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为害怕踏出最初的一步
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.29,0:21:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人 请归还我的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.14,0:21:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 今天我很困 下次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.01,0:21:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是老样子 每天都有诸多麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.02,0:21:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管还是不善于应付妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.46,0:21:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.55,0:21:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷偷摸摸 偷偷摸摸
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.34,0:22:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过偶尔的话 或许陪它们聊聊也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.99,0:23:50.15,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,540)}时雨与少女
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.92,0:23:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字是?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.08,0:23:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫「时雨」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.47,0:23:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 原本是神明吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.32,0:23:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个想见你的人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.30,0:23:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如今 我已不想再和人类扯上关系
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.34,0:23:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在只是个不洁的妖怪罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.10,0:22:12.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.10,0:22:12.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.14,0:22:20.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.14,0:22:20.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:26.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:26.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.57,0:22:33.50,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.57,0:22:33.50,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:44.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:44.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.55,0:22:48.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.55,0:22:48.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:58.40,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:58.40,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:06.04,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:06.04,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:13.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:13.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.10,0:23:20.46,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.10,0:23:20.46,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.46,0:23:27.18,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.46,0:23:27.18,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
