[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,1
Style: OP_jp,方正楷体_GBK,33,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,45,1
Style: OP_ch,方正楷体_GBK,36,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,5,1
Style: ED_jp,方正楷体_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,45,1
Style: ED_ch,方正楷体_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,5,1
Style: bt,方正楷体_GBK,55,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,33,&H00E8EEF4,&HF0000000,&H1E23384E,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text



Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.21,0:01:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸟巢?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.78,0:01:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.81,0:01:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它在孵五颗蛋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.99,0:01:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前四只已经孵化了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.11,0:01:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还留下一颗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.51,0:01:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非你想吃掉那颗蛋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.61,0:01:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在看护那蛋啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.10,0:01:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生你尽想着吃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.26,0:01:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.20,0:01:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.78,0:01:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 一个人也没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.40,0:01:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.90,0:02:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚确实在这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.54,0:02:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.39,0:02:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妖怪写的东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.54,0:02:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 这不是实际写在上面的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.71,0:02:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这是只有我们才能看到的文字
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.88,0:02:30.87,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雏鸟 孵化
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.17,0:02:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母鸟没回来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.85,0:02:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志 怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.24,0:02:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 没什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.07,0:02:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.51,0:02:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可别做那么危险的事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.95,0:02:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.67,0:03:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还很温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.85,0:03:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 这是啥啊!?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.41,0:03:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.56,0:03:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你很闲嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.19,0:03:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能麻烦你来孵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.82,0:03:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.75,0:03:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这笨蛋真是笨到家了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.38,0:03:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋这种东西从被丢弃的那刻起就已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.93,0:03:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雏鸟孵化出来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.29,0:03:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能会很美味哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.90,0:03:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.93,0:03:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.90,0:04:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.33,0:04:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涂鸦的文字变了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.82,0:04:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样 因为一时兴起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.59,0:04:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便让先生来孵那颗蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.54,0:04:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.77,0:04:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去喝酒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.73,0:04:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.26,0:04:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.34,0:04:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不开裂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.36,0:04:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 快出来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.70,0:04:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 快住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.01,0:04:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.86,0:04:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉稍微大了一点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.21,0:04:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么的蛋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.88,0:05:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果孵化出小鸟的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.65,0:05:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该给它取什么名字呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.12,0:05:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.81,0:05:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造访
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.81,0:05:41.52,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,译注:日语中「参」有来到、登门造访的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.09,0:05:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造访
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.00,0:05:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.04,0:05:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.57,0:06:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是大写数字啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.31,0:06:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陆是六
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.70,0:06:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伍是五
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.90,0:06:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天那个是四
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.43,0:06:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是三
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.16,0:06:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在倒数
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.18,0:06:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟是为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.40,0:06:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.09,0:06:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然看得见这文字 你是何人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.92,0:06:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你写的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.87,0:06:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.22,0:06:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是这家里的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.42,0:06:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.01,0:06:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你知道那边鸟巢里的蛋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.73,0:06:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾家主人想要那只雏鸟
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.85,0:06:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「想要」是指?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.57,0:06:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.45,0:06:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是要拿来吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.18,0:06:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说那雏鸟的肉具有无可比拟的美味
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.18,0:06:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,榨出的血液更有不老不死的功效
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.40,0:06:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于在这里找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.20,0:06:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在计算它孵化的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.46,0:06:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在我发现蛋已经不在原来的地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.05,0:07:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非是身为卑下人类的你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.72,0:07:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想从中强行抢夺吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.28,0:07:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.56,0:07:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的话 可以相信吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.82,0:07:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.75,0:07:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子 别起什么坏心眼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.21,0:07:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 外面有个奇怪的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.58,0:07:41.58,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(不行 忍到极限了 我去喝一杯)
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.90,0:07:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个没丁点毅力的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.05,0:07:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果给他的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.40,0:07:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚出生就要被吃掉了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.45,0:08:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这颗蛋还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.31,0:08:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是想要活下去的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.96,0:08:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想活得更久一点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.96,0:08:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我～回来～啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.33,0:08:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炸虾盖浇饭...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.47,0:08:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.51,0:09:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那今天就到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.98,0:09:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起立
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.46,0:09:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行礼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.45,0:09:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.46,0:09:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙最近怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.65,0:09:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 蛋快要...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.69,0:09:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 雏鸟 美味的雏鸟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.50,0:10:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 热水热水
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.74,0:10:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛巾毛巾 记得还有毛巾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.10,0:10:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙 应该是妖怪辰未的雏鸟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.19,0:10:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰未?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.38,0:10:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是种近鸟似龙的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.46,0:10:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们自己不会养育孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.73,0:10:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以数量很少
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.89,0:10:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说雏鸟会变成孵化时最初看到的生物的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.35,0:10:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后养育到一定程度后
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.98,0:10:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会变回本来的样子 离巢独立
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.12,0:10:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 那最先看到先生的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.71,0:11:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真幸运呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.65,0:11:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那是什么意思!?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.05,0:11:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.16,0:11:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.25,0:11:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说喂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.40,0:11:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.75,0:11:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 这样就差不多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.65,0:11:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然无视我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.04,0:11:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要多久才能长大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.25,0:11:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.54,0:11:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然听说辰未生长得很快
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.71,0:11:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但详细我也不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.24,0:11:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它吃什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.90,0:11:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给它喝牛奶没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.82,0:11:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定 是吃人肉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.27,0:11:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 喂 小心吃坏肚子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.70,0:11:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个不知感恩的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.29,0:11:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个火柴棒样的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.62,0:11:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是养育的父母啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.17,0:11:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火柴棒是什么意思 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.95,0:11:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火柴棒就是火柴棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.82,0:11:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住口 你这只肥猫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.35,0:11:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒是自己照镜子看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.72,0:11:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是火柴棒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.42,0:11:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我太轻率了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.38,0:11:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然一时兴起就捡回了一条生命
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.91,0:12:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人不可能理解龙的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.03,0:12:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙也不可能明白人的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.52,0:12:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明明早该知道这个的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.45,0:12:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.75,0:12:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.91,0:12:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个烤板是收到的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.69,0:12:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就稍微努力了下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.40,0:12:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以再吃一个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.52,0:12:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.59,0:12:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是失败作啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.01,0:12:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的非常好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.92,0:12:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.42,0:12:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是被先生吃掉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.86,0:12:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 原来在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.72,0:13:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我跟过来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.73,0:13:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.58,0:13:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是巢吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.14,0:13:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰未是不会自己养育幼子的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.18,0:13:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以雏鸟会变化成最初见到的生物的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.93,0:13:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是想得到最初看到的人的怜爱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.09,0:13:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.45,0:13:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你辛辛苦苦做的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.63,0:13:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却没有办法一起进去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.73,0:13:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几天后 我做了一个梦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.88,0:13:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是进到这个巢里的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.41,0:13:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷偷跑进的这个巢里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.74,0:14:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有着什么重要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.79,0:14:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是长大了不少呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.26,0:14:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然心智尚幼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.57,0:14:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但终究是龙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.77,0:14:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一起的时间已经不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.35,0:14:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.12,0:14:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长大后就会独自飞走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.71,0:14:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也该给她取名字了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.41,0:14:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字的话我早就取好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.81,0:14:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是从蛋里出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.32,0:14:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就叫「小玉」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.70,0:14:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是很喜欢吧 那个名字
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.37,0:14:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小不点 我饶不了你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.22,0:14:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉一点一点地
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.71,0:14:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点一点地在成长
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.41,0:15:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.23,0:15:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.60,0:15:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始渐渐变得衰弱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.39,0:15:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了啊 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.88,0:15:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西都没吃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.89,0:15:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去换牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.23,0:15:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜哇 老鼠
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.96,0:15:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.04,0:15:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是磯月的鼠
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.38,0:15:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子 我应该警告过你别起什么坏心眼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.74,0:15:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰未的雏鸟我来带走了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.31,0:15:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 是下贱的妖兽吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.45,0:15:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然跑到我的地盘 还真是胆大包天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.33,0:16:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老鼠就由我用逗猫棒锻炼出来的右勾拳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.04,0:16:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.91,0:16:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然这么无礼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.10,0:16:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么奇怪的生物
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.30,0:16:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是猪吗 还是狸猫
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.87,0:16:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 我一定要吃了你 老鼠小子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.37,0:16:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住 小子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.14,0:16:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤脑筋了 该逃去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.93,0:16:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是 到底为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.13,0:16:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得如此消瘦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.92,0:16:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不吃饭了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.47,0:16:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你是不想长大吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.68,0:17:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怕长大之后要离开这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.05,0:17:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.17,0:17:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是想在我身边再多待一阵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.68,0:17:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到你了 小子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.96,0:17:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我不会把她交给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.24,0:17:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不交出来的话就用抢的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.06,0:17:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗 小子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.90,0:17:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无力的人类啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.37,0:17:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正对于弱小的人类来说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.47,0:17:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰未也只会招来灾害
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.86,0:17:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 快交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.14,0:17:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是一只妖怪的生命
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.50,0:17:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说应该也无关痛痒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.32,0:17:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小...小玉 不要闹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.41,0:18:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.40,0:18:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使长大了也不必离开
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.76,0:18:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以继续待在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.30,0:18:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好地吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.39,0:18:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算总有一天 离别的时刻来临
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.68,0:18:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那也不一定意味着永别
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.60,0:18:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.39,0:18:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那时为止
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.70,0:18:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以一直待在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.16,0:18:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.64,0:18:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.79,0:18:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.66,0:18:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 小玉 这样他会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.11,0:18:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.22,0:18:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.43,0:18:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在突然成长的冲击下 它已经失去自我了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.20,0:19:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家吧 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.27,0:19:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.97,0:19:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒啊 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.40,0:19:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像鸟一样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.39,0:20:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听我说 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.77,0:20:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道亲生父母的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.14,0:20:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是独自一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.70,0:20:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这说起来或许会有点奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.67,0:20:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我完全不觉得孤单
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.65,0:20:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可却是非常地悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.24,0:20:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 我来到了这个小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.74,0:20:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与许多人相遇之后
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.84,0:20:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悲伤已被渐渐地冲淡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.33,0:20:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你也能这样觉得就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.30,0:21:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解孤独的滋味
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.83,0:21:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要被人爱怜的你的悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.97,0:21:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕只有一点 我是否
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.52,0:21:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮你抹去了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.11,0:21:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后我偷偷看了下小玉留下的巢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.86,0:21:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.33,0:21:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.38,0:21:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面果然空空如也
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.94,0:21:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想我知道 留在里面的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.95,0:23:51.01,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,550)}{\4c&HDDF9F2&}约定之树
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.65,0:23:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么名字
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.11,0:23:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫雾叶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.35,0:23:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...我的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.82,0:23:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我会归还给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.50,0:23:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.25,0:23:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐上没你的名字嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.85,0:23:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字是在其他地方的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.10,0:23:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 那去看看吧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 少しだけ大人の色に染まる指先
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 指尖稍露成年的沧桑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 照れくさそうに そっと隠して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 你就害羞得将它悄悄收起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 頬杖ついた君 見つめてる視線の先に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 手托下巴的你将视线投向
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 小さな蕾が ゆらゆら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 那随风轻曳的小小花蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} ねぇ 僕なんて いまも迷いばかりで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 喂 现在的我仍迷茫依旧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} あの日贈った言葉 今さら思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 这才回想起 那日你的临别赠言
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「君色に未来染めて...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「将我的未来染成你的颜色...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ 聞いていてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 听我倾诉好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ わがままいいですか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 让我任性好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手に入れた途端に消えてしまいそう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}拥有的瞬间仿佛就会消散
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}言葉をくれませんか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不说点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あなたがいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}因为有你在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}それだけで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう世界が変わってしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我的世界就会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}モノトーンの景色が ほら 鮮やかに映る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}映入眼眸的单调景色也会光鲜亮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}いつのまにか 離れていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不知何时却已离开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手を繋いで歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}牵着手 向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}上手く愛せているかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}能够好好去爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あの空に聞いてみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}天空也许会回答
