[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.19,0:03:27.19,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}代答
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.97,0:24:16.02,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\pos(228,296)}给过去的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.56,0:01:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.48,0:01:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能否替我开门呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.30,0:01:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.80,0:01:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.50,0:01:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  把钥匙给弄丢了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.01,0:01:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买完东西回来得真早呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.07,0:02:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有上锁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人在
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.71,0:02:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了  估计刚刚是妖怪想要进来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.47,0:02:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.90,0:02:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是来索要友人帐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.49,0:02:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.20,0:02:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.65,0:02:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是夏目贵志吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.61,0:02:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐放在哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.44,0:02:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚是你假装了塔子阿姨的声音吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.15,0:02:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.29,0:02:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若不交出来  我就压折了你这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.86,0:02:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.82,0:02:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  不能给你友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.28,0:02:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.04,0:02:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.94,0:02:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都说很痛了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.28,0:02:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  替我打开这瓶果酱
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.29,0:02:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.53,0:02:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这老朽的家伙是什么来历呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.13,0:03:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  喂  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.42,0:03:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  输给这黄毛小子真是太耻辱了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.55,0:03:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是若使硬的不奏效的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.10,0:03:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想着或许会变这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.27,0:03:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就准备好见面礼来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.50,0:03:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.38,0:03:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说不可能给你友人帐的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.48,0:03:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就算是借给我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.09,0:03:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没戏
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.85,0:03:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到借  你到底是打算用来做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.39,0:03:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您该知道名为借纸的妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.73,0:03:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽未曾见过
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.50,0:03:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但听说它的名字有上友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.40,0:03:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要召唤出它来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.44,0:03:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,召唤出素未谋面的家伙来  是做何打算
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.91,0:04:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.32,0:04:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纸？ 已经相当破旧了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.56,0:04:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都干瘪瘪的了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.93,0:04:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此  感觉轻碰就会碎掉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.50,0:04:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那然后呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.00,0:04:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不明白吗  真迟钝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.37,0:04:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没辙  就告诉你了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.04,0:04:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来话长  做好觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.53,0:04:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  是美酒
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.89,0:04:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我善于模拟声音
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.53,0:04:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还拥有能让人类听到的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.61,0:04:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鄙人名为呼子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.25,0:04:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,元居住于狩山山道上的古木中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.78,0:04:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知何时起有位人类女子开始从那面前经过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.02,0:04:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就每日不曾间断
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.26,0:04:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽对人类没有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.15,0:04:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  不过是一时兴起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.87,0:05:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心人类步入这深山中或遭遇危险
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.01,0:05:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就跟着那位女子了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.95,0:05:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着在前面有座小的庙堂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.10,0:05:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有位耀眼而又清爽的男子在那等着
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.83,0:05:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女子看起来非常开心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.11,0:05:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常幸福地笑着同他聊着
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.51,0:05:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来他们是在那里幽会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.11,0:05:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是幽会但也只是见面聊些无关紧要的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.59,0:05:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是每一天  每一天…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.22,0:05:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你在偷窥咯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.11,0:05:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  是担心他们对庙堂不敬而在监视着
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.57,0:05:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.15,0:05:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思   请继续吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.02,0:05:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来是十分亲密的恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.57,0:05:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只可惜男子他琐事繁忙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.12,0:05:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微闲聊后就回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.89,0:06:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女子则总是远望着男子回家的那个方向
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.56,0:06:14.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待到日落才依依不舍的沿着山道返回
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.35,0:06:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心野兽或蛇突袭就危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.20,0:06:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是替她事先开路
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.51,0:06:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要笑  那可是每天都在做
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.61,0:06:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  尽给我增加不必要的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.33,0:06:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  只是觉得您真善良
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.83,0:06:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  才没有那么善良
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.54,0:06:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.59,0:06:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之赶紧替我召唤出借纸来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.96,0:06:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额  不好意思  我召唤不出来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.67,0:06:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.06,0:06:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是听说记载在友人帐上的妖怪们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.37,0:06:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要被赋予命令就无法反抗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.64,0:06:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是知道外表和姓名的情况下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.41,0:07:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收集姓名的是祖母
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.48,0:07:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽是些我从未谋面的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.12,0:07:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.01,0:07:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到竟然会帮不上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.38,0:07:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还白喝了我的酒…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.05,0:07:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没有喝哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.82,0:07:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚就让我在这休憩一宿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.41,0:07:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得重新想想该怎么办才好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.22,0:07:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  已经睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.64,0:07:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里睡下…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.85,0:07:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些妖怪待在人类的圈子里会消耗特别多的精力
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.76,0:07:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真够为难的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.59,0:07:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与这种随性而为
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.22,0:07:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却背负着某种思念的妖怪接触的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.01,0:07:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个夜晚  不出我所料又做梦了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.55,0:07:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隆彦  隆彦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.22,0:07:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知是谁在断肠地呼唤着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.68,0:08:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到这声音的妖怪也肯定…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.00,0:08:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君  来吃早饭咯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.95,0:08:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  吃咯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.75,0:08:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么打算怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.89,0:08:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有办法  自己去找借纸
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.55,0:08:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有听你说哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.11,0:08:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何要去找借纸
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.02,0:08:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是夏目啊  看起来好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.81,0:08:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.80,0:09:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小角色  还真敢乱来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.18,0:09:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢了  呼子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.17,0:09:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.79,0:09:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.10,0:09:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.56,0:09:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算做什么  要去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.62,0:09:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道借纸的长相
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.07,0:09:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但知道他有可能出没的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.17,0:09:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若持有友人帐的夏目出现的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.31,0:09:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许他就会赶来要求归还名字
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.31,0:09:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要拿我做诱饵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.90,0:09:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说借纸是很随和的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.77,0:09:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我答应一定会保护好你护送你家
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.62,0:09:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以现在请暂时助我一臂之力  夏目殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.64,0:09:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…就告诉我其中缘由
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.48,0:10:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借纸是能修复旧纸的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.45,0:10:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这张暴晒雨林后打不开了的纸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.32,0:10:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许能将它给修复返原
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.36,0:10:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天又说过他俩的幽会
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.90,0:10:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有一天起男子却不再出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.16,0:10:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此女子仍旧来到庙堂等候男子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.15,0:10:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我见如此就前往男子家中一探究竟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.94,0:10:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从以往的谈话中了解到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.38,0:10:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男子出身村里名门是长子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.33,0:10:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是了不起的新郎和新娘呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.12,0:10:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  而且还是出身相当富裕的千金
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.49,0:10:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此一来 这个日渐衰落的家族
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.56,0:10:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于能稳定下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.20,0:10:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是本家  必须要振兴起来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.92,0:11:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知人不能同妖怪结连理
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.83,0:11:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来无论人与人是如何的情投意合
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.34,0:11:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也会有无法结合的时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.68,0:11:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隆彦  隆彦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.40,0:11:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过女子却不知真相
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.94,0:11:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仍旧守候在那
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.09,0:11:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隆彦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.82,0:11:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日日夜夜呼唤着男子的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.57,0:11:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隆彦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.85,0:11:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.82,0:11:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隆彦  你在里面吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.86,0:11:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  千万不可开门  阳子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.95,0:11:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…我感染上疾病
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.50,0:11:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不能同你接触
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.35,0:11:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疾病？ 严重吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.10,0:11:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怎样的疾病？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.16,0:11:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经治疗得差不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.26,0:11:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.31,0:12:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  只不过以防万一就暂时同你保持距离…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.98,0:12:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗…是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.30,0:12:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.25,0:12:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.43,0:12:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那时其实应当是替他向她告别来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.70,0:12:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而她的笑声却是那般幸福…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.96,0:12:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了  隆彦你能来看我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.55,0:12:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  既然不便接触到你的话就先回去休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.33,0:12:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我还好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.25,0:12:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.11,0:12:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就约好明天再来这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.06,0:12:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天再会  就这么日复一日
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.70,0:12:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无数次再去同她相会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.96,0:12:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隆彦你已经累了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.53,0:12:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 一点都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.63,0:13:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过看起来就要下雨了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.92,0:13:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请先回去好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.23,0:13:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了  阳子你先回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.75,0:13:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  隆彦你先请
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.90,0:13:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  阳子先
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.19,0:13:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是倔强
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.02,0:13:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  明明是阳子你顽固
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.51,0:13:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天天气真好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.07,0:13:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  真的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.42,0:13:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,树木们都换上新色了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.35,0:13:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.73,0:13:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷不冷啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.65,0:13:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不冷  没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.02,0:13:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚做了一个梦  是个美梦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.67,0:13:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过一扇小小的窗户看到一片大海
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.36,0:14:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海上风平浪静波光闪闪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.49,0:14:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.02,0:14:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而我明明没有印象去过那里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.25,0:14:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却不知为何心中感到似曾相识
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.73,0:14:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉像是回到了那儿一样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.77,0:14:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平静得让人舒心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.24,0:14:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.09,0:14:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这说的可是我的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.62,0:14:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦也好无论是哪…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.65,0:14:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真像是童言无忌
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.25,0:14:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉不像是隆彦你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.11,0:14:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…才…才没有那么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.44,0:14:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还这么当真  真是愈发可疑了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.99,0:14:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很奇怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.28,0:14:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  相当的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.84,0:14:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越是相会  她笑得越多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.41,0:14:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就越让我感受到罪孽深重
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.61,0:15:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不可思议
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.84,0:15:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至从无法见面只能听到你的声音以来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.94,0:15:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉比以前更加亲近了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.55,0:15:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是哪怕只是一下下也好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.49,0:15:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要看看你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.61,0:15:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想见到你!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.02,0:15:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  阳子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.05,0:15:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男子因为家事已经不能再来这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.29,0:15:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是假扮他的冒牌货
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.14,0:15:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.00,0:15:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.69,0:15:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这永远都得不到宽恕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.68,0:16:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不敢直视她受伤后的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.72,0:16:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那以后再也不曾…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.81,0:16:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己的罪恶感和害怕同她相见
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.61,0:16:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那起就未曾回到古树和庙堂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.60,0:16:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始外出流浪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.77,0:16:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再经过相对人世间相当漫长的时间之后
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.46,0:16:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再一次返回了那座庙堂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.17,0:16:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.90,0:16:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现怕被风吹走而压在石头下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.69,0:16:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是书信一样的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.52,0:16:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是毫不相干的人的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.61,0:16:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但或许也有可能是阳子她留下的信
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.08,0:16:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是那样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.60,0:16:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是留给隆彦君的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.60,0:16:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又或许是给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.61,0:16:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.95,0:16:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是愤怒和怨恨的字语的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.70,0:16:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就必须得由我来承担
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.17,0:16:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都在逃避
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.23,0:17:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是无法忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.43,0:17:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有可能的话  就想读读这封信
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.07,0:17:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.59,0:17:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到这里  我也对里面的内容在意起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.27,0:17:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  那个元眉毛的妖怪跑去哪里了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.76,0:17:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.53,0:17:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  借纸  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.94,0:17:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借纸在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.88,0:17:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来把名字还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.69,0:17:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个白痴又做些傻事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.65,0:17:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  借纸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.88,0:17:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来还你重要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.57,0:17:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你出来一下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.94,0:17:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.86,0:17:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.04,0:18:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.55,0:18:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 擅自到处乱嚷嚷
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.35,0:18:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就那么想成为妖怪的食物吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.18,0:18:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要还给我名字是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.89,0:18:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和玲子的味道有点不一样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.47,0:18:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目玲子是我的祖母
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.33,0:18:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她把友人帐托付给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.11,0:18:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,束缚了你那么久很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.13,0:18:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.48,0:18:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外我还有一个请求
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.18,0:18:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请求？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.88,0:18:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有友人帐的话  你命令我就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.15,0:18:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实这是我的请求
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.55,0:18:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你能帮忙把这封信恢复原样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.52,0:18:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何  请帮帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.83,0:18:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  你和玲子奇怪的地方大不相同啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.61,0:18:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚好  你把名字还给我  就当回礼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.49,0:19:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护吾之人  显其名
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.47,0:19:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借纸  还汝之名  请接受
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.07,0:19:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  没想到居然会败给一个人类
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.66,0:19:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时都可以召唤我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.37,0:19:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是那张纸变的破旧不堪了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.71,0:19:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就由我来修复吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.86,0:19:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.00,0:19:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经收回我的名字了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.34,0:19:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  接下来该我了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.13,0:19:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信纸还原  信纸还原
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.77,0:20:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请好好保管
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.73,0:20:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  借纸大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.91,0:20:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.88,0:20:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  眉毛妖怪  要用酒做谢礼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.00,0:20:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  帮了大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.73,0:20:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是女子的信啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.53,0:20:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这个气味
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.46,0:20:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写信之人已经不在世上了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.74,0:20:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.39,0:20:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  从那张纸的颜色看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.79,0:20:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在妖怪心中即使今日依旧鲜活的那个声音  那个笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.58,0:20:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都是很久很久以前的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.04,0:20:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让人在不经意间  突然就离去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.86,0:21:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子也  已经不在这个世上了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.22,0:21:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.91,0:21:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  那个时候我不就变老婆婆了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.94,0:21:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.77,0:21:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.58,0:21:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又在发呆
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.40,0:21:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那么大意  若又要被妖怪吃掉的话  我可不管哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.30,0:21:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你接下来要继续旅行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.02,0:21:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我想回到原来的古树那里  古庙也在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.26,0:21:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想继续守护那个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.94,0:21:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.98,0:21:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信  是写给你的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.76,0:21:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写了什么  我可以听一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.09,0:21:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  说来惭愧  我看不懂人类的字
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.20,0:21:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以念给我听吗  夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.37,0:22:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写了什么  夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.48,0:22:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悲伤吗  不可饶恕吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.15,0:22:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.07,0:22:20.53,Banner,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你告诉我真相
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.30,0:24:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在看着什么东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.17,0:24:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你粘上了奇怪的东西哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.93,0:24:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个妖怪  我以前见过
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.59,0:24:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有能问出口就分别了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.65,0:24:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小镇上有些奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.18,0:24:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在过得是否开心呢
