[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,1
Style: OP_jp,方正楷体_GBK,33,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,45,1
Style: OP_ch,方正楷体_GBK,36,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,5,1
Style: ED_jp,方正楷体_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,45,1
Style: ED_ch,方正楷体_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,5,1
Style: bt,方正楷体_GBK,55,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text



Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.83,0:01:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.11,0:01:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好小
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.95,0:01:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 这样子过不去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.67,0:01:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了 这样子无法继续前进了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.10,0:01:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绕过去不就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.42,0:02:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀呀 有路了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.26,0:02:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下可好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.74,0:02:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前进 前进
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.80,0:02:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前进 前进
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.75,0:02:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好小啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.26,0:02:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个神轿只有小包裹那么大
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.62,0:02:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 赶快把大人抬到他身体那儿去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.11,0:02:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抬啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.20,0:02:27.29,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪退治 温泉旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.30,0:02:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.75,0:02:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.81,0:02:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门缝里夹着纸条?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.85,0:02:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纸人偶？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.54,0:02:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 回来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.07,0:02:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生 你去哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.42,0:02:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巡逻啊 巡逻
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.93,0:02:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看有没有会诱骗你然后一口把你吃掉的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.45,0:02:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那是啥?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.47,0:02:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不清楚 夹在门里的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.19,0:03:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.00,0:03:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎...怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.37,0:03:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体被很大的力量牵引着
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.62,0:03:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼...疼疼疼疼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.18,0:03:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.14,0:03:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.15,0:03:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.78,0:03:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了能在你回来的时候通知我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.98,0:03:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才把施了术的纸人偶夹在门缝里的 不过...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.66,0:03:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是迟钝呐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.53,0:03:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被它缠住了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.02,0:03:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西 是你搞的鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.71,0:03:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生 私底下从事着驱妖的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.86,0:03:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 这儿也不适合闲谈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.11,0:03:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但表面上其实是...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.75,0:03:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.67,0:03:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.26,0:03:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取周一
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.02,0:04:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要一起喝杯茶呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.51,0:04:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时下当红明星 名取周一
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.01,0:04:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话 他稍微有点烦人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.97,0:04:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次的连休 有空吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.30,0:04:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没空
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.61,0:04:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢泡温泉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.20,0:04:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.93,0:04:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一起去吗 温泉旅馆
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.06,0:04:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.54,0:04:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在买香水附赠的抽奖活动中抽到的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.09,0:04:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温泉旅馆双人住宿券
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.21,0:04:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,香水? 抽奖?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.70,0:04:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 为什么找我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.24,0:04:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邀请女孩子去不更好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.55,0:04:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们事务所里那是被禁止的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.65,0:04:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个形迹可疑的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.19,0:04:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 要不要我把这小子油炸下吃掉?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.72,0:04:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就没有其他男性朋友了么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.82,0:04:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 能看到同样风景的朋友就只有你一个
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.54,0:04:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没去过什么旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.86,0:05:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了对了 那家旅馆还允许带宠物哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.03,0:05:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什~么~! 去吧夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.83,0:05:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸡蛋 鸡蛋 温泉鸡蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.45,0:05:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 鸡蛋 温泉鸡蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.90,0:05:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就由我来和你家里人说一声吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.62,0:05:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 旅行 太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.07,0:05:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会负责的 请把夏目君交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.46,0:05:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 好漂亮的花啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.35,0:05:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和这么可靠的朋友一起旅游的话 我也就放心了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.69,0:05:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.16,0:05:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天我来接他
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.62,0:05:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志他总是太过客气拘束
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.69,0:05:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能这样也让我开心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.95,0:05:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好好地去玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.70,0:05:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我会带土特产回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.85,0:05:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样 两个人和一只猫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.94,0:05:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两天一夜的温泉旅行开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.44,0:05:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里还真重峦叠嶂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.36,0:05:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要掩人耳目刚刚好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.40,0:05:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随心所欲地坐公车和电车 不算是掩人耳目吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.61,0:06:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿啦 走快点 臭小子们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.35,0:06:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,累了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.40,0:06:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 不过晴天真好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.21,0:06:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.08,0:06:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远道而来 欢迎欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.91,0:06:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去打个电话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.92,0:06:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘记跟经纪人说出来旅游的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.10,0:06:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带您去房间
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.66,0:06:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.67,0:06:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很累 不过真是舒畅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.24,0:06:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔能这样也不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.46,0:07:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壁橱里是什么声音?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.54,0:07:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.25,0:07:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在好像没什么人 一起去泡温泉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.22,0:07:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.46,0:07:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.88,0:07:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.20,0:07:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}包场温泉浴
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.40,0:07:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愉快 愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.83,0:07:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 作为一只猫第一个进来泡是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.25,0:07:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了我不是猫了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.76,0:07:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你说是什么 肥猫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.13,0:07:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然说什么肥猫 肥猫是什么意思!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.95,0:07:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把如此高贵的我当成什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.92,0:07:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一 只 猫
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.50,0:07:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啥!?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.23,0:07:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 吵架可不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.37,0:07:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可别把温泉水弄脏了 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.79,0:07:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来就是陶器 怎么会弄脏呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.08,0:07:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.02,0:07:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.08,0:07:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.50,0:08:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎别人都看不到名取先生那壁虎状的痣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.66,0:08:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道眼睛该往哪里看才好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.81,0:08:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我不擅长跟妖怪打交道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.20,0:08:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但名取先生大概对妖怪心怀憎恨吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.15,0:08:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了夏目 泡晕了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.83,0:08:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是女生 你紧张什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.52,0:08:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类总是有容易敏感的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.04,0:08:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不都是因为你突然出现 才被吓到了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.01,0:08:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊 不是说了不能吓唬夏目的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.64,0:08:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我忘记他是个软弱的家伙了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.28,0:08:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊 是名取先生持有的式神之一
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.03,0:09:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉啊 不赶快擦干的话会感冒的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.73,0:09:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用管她 没关系的 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.42,0:09:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪是不会感冒的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.76,0:09:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.26,0:09:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不喝牛奶 是因为要喝啤酒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.04,0:09:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啤酒很好喝哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.49,0:09:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是夏目你也是成年人的话 还想跟你喝一杯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.47,0:09:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.36,0:09:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.05,0:09:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里的天花板上吊着个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.74,0:09:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.58,0:09:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到什么东西了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.04,0:09:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有... 是错觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.04,0:09:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去旅馆里兜一圈看看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.22,0:09:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚洗完澡会受凉的 夏目你就在房间里待着好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.27,0:09:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.97,0:09:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 我很快就回来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.48,0:09:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 柊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.11,0:09:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.36,0:09:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我没说出来就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.52,0:10:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是为了休养才邀请我一起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.19,0:10:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 总之要当心友人帐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.75,0:10:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好好在这儿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.57,0:10:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 我还没跟名取先生说过友人帐的事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.09,0:10:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说 会被抢走的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.65,0:10:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然他不是太可靠 但也不会做出这种事情的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.74,0:10:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要诚实说出来是你的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.24,0:10:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正到时去烦恼他会不会也是冲着友人帐来的肯定也是你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.04,0:10:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实 那样就麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.73,0:10:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个消极的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.58,0:10:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个壁橱
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.79,0:10:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道里面有老鼠吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.38,0:10:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.64,0:10:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个陶壶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.81,0:10:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陶壶?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.91,0:10:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在壁橱里?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.55,0:10:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.32,0:10:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个有盖子的陶壶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.76,0:10:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 盖子上有张裂开的封条
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.68,0:11:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有种不好的预感
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.42,0:11:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说起来 是在这附近吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.92,0:11:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.52,0:11:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到天花板上吊着人影的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.86,0:11:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个陶壶的大小 正好可以装下一个人的脑袋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.23,0:11:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就当作没看到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.21,0:11:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊? 不打开看看吗 真无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.96,0:11:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定里面放着美味的腌辣韭菜哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.87,0:11:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会上当的 即便是如此有趣的诱惑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.83,0:11:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么辣韭菜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.36,0:11:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.14,0:11:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.39,0:11:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.25,0:11:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.23,0:11:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 那么 去吃东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.61,0:11:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给猫咪多点些生鱼片吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.07,0:11:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.94,0:11:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实有件事情令我有点在意
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.91,0:11:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但目前为止也只是捕风捉影 并无大碍
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.46,0:12:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得出来旅行 不该说这些破坏气氛的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.97,0:12:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 今天就不要管妖怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.19,0:12:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.62,0:12:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 去吃东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.89,0:12:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.14,0:12:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好累 困死了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.04,0:12:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和现在的监护人相处得愉快吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.71,0:12:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.94,0:12:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们待我非常好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.84,0:12:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.25,0:12:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.24,0:12:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 要是对谎言感到厌倦了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.94,0:12:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就来我这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.48,0:12:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谎言?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.60,0:12:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 因为你和我之间
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.61,0:12:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许不需要用谎言来编织生活
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.97,0:12:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谎言
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.94,0:13:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗子 骗子 骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.02,0:13:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候因为能看到妖怪的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.17,0:13:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常被大家说成骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.60,0:13:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近时常会做到那时候的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.08,0:13:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明明没有说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.10,0:13:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明明...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.15,0:13:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.94,0:13:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧夏目 你怎么流泪了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.02,0:13:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 真的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.91,0:13:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.28,0:13:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.47,0:13:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好丢脸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.15,0:13:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然会因为梦境而流泪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.04,0:13:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.56,0:14:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壶的盖子开了?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.34,0:14:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.30,0:14:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.16,0:14:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陶壶的盖子开了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.78,0:14:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陶壶?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.71,0:14:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是之前说到的辣韭菜壶吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.83,0:14:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许不是辣韭菜壶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.94,0:14:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那陶壶时不时会发出声响
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.60,0:14:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似刚才它的盖子自动打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.80,0:14:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.83,0:14:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壁橱里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.99,0:14:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连看都没看就知道盖子打开了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.53,0:14:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有种不妙的气息散发了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.85,0:14:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.37,0:14:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来在这种地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.36,0:14:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.16,0:14:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空空如也么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.78,0:14:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说里面的东西逃走了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.53,0:14:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去下面看看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.87,0:14:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.93,0:14:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.71,0:14:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个陶壶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.90,0:14:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为贴着强大的封印
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.54,0:14:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以本来还觉得不必太在意的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.78,0:14:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.57,0:14:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然能自行打破封印
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.12,0:14:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是个很强的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.69,0:14:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.56,0:15:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那道封印是最近才布下的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.17,0:15:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近的?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.99,0:15:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.58,0:15:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.86,0:15:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在流血
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.01,0:15:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是个大家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.74,0:15:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能吃掉她吗 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.75,0:15:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.67,0:15:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个持有友人帐的夏目大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.29,0:15:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求您 求求您把我的名字还给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.95,0:15:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫澄江
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.66,0:15:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直居住在此
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.52,0:15:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但人类来了之后说我碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.46,0:15:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把我封印在这个陶壶里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.51,0:15:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌人类
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.64,0:15:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把我的名字还给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.98,0:15:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 我对这里也不会再心存留恋了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.99,0:16:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦取回名字 我就离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.81,0:16:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隐匿到深山中去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.98,0:16:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求您
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.18,0:16:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你并不想给这家旅馆添麻烦的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.65,0:16:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你有这种想法的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.06,0:16:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以用友人帐的力量 命令你离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.32,0:16:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.08,0:16:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用您下命令 我也会离开这座房子的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.81,0:16:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.45,0:16:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,束缚你的名字那么久 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.52,0:16:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.01,0:16:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来 就没什么可畏惧的了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.95,0:16:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和铃子不同 真是善良呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.06,0:16:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.91,0:16:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少就让你毫无痛苦的...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.21,0:16:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一口吞掉你吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.45,0:16:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.29,0:17:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.41,0:17:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 逃走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.57,0:17:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 难得如此美味的佳肴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.77,0:17:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不会让你逃出这间房子的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.84,0:17:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走这边
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.82,0:17:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到走廊尽头的房间去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.00,0:17:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕 我太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.35,0:17:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自诩为对妖怪十分了解
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.16,0:17:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我还会这样...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.05,0:17:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫名取的小子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.62,0:17:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该告诉我们了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.18,0:17:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底有什么企图
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.07,0:17:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太小看我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.20,0:17:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,企图?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.18,0:17:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.62,0:17:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这房间到底是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.33,0:17:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗完澡就已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.54,0:17:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这旅馆的后山上有个危害人类的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.37,0:17:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然其他的驱妖人已加以封印 可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.81,0:18:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他的驱妖人?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.67,0:18:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那妖怪似乎在被完全封印之前
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.29,0:18:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃进了这间旅馆
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.31,0:18:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才会来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.14,0:18:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么说的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.90,0:18:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才哄骗讨厌驱妖的夏目来这里的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.07,0:18:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了得到他的帮忙来驱妖封魔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.72,0:18:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错呢 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.99,0:18:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经习惯对人说谎了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.75,0:18:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早知道你如此乐意的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.62,0:18:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就应该先跟你说清楚的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.04,0:18:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.25,0:18:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我也有隐瞒名取先生的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.11,0:18:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看样子是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.06,0:18:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉间 我们都已习惯生活在谎言中了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.26,0:18:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是 名取先生也是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.78,0:18:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会帮忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.95,0:18:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次的事是我太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.07,0:18:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.41,0:18:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会用整个房间作为结界来封印妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.19,0:18:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊你就出去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.13,0:18:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生你也出去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.40,0:18:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 真无聊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.52,0:19:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了你 吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.60,0:19:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个房间里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.43,0:19:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.32,0:19:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类啊 我要吃光你们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.37,0:19:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不能动了...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.19,0:19:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.23,0:19:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钻出来了!?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.90,0:19:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.24,0:19:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不容许你加害夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.04,0:19:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 这妖怪是?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.21,0:19:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找您好久了 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.51,0:19:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘记了吗 您曾帮我架过桥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.42,0:20:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三只眼...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.19,0:20:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是那时的妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.59,0:20:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙就由我带走净化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.53,0:20:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么时候认识了这么大的妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.02,0:20:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是顺手帮了下忙而已
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.54,0:20:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来也有知恩图报的妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.27,0:20:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又随便和人家扯上关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.45,0:20:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.17,0:20:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为... 我都看在眼里了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.70,0:20:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪会哭 会困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.79,0:20:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且会背叛 会报恩
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.02,0:20:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人他...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.29,0:20:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人他只是来确认被封印妖怪的情况的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.08,0:20:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也因为机会难得
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.78,0:21:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以想和你多聊一聊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.38,0:21:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我也有很多话想说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.88,0:21:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明有很多的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.48,0:21:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对名取先生 面对藤原夫妇
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.32,0:21:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想说的话却无法很好地表达
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.88,0:21:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 我害怕让他们知道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.36,0:21:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明已经习惯被人所害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.36,0:21:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.30,0:21:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天 一定会
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.49,0:21:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会毫无保留地向那些想真心相待的人们倾诉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.17,0:21:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.60,0:21:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 又把你卷进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.87,0:21:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会 真的很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.71,0:21:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次有机会再一起出来玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.17,0:21:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 当然可以
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.74,0:21:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我们回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.48,0:21:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.71,0:21:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样 第一次的温泉之旅结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.94,0:21:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带着些许兴奋 我们踏上了归途
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.62,0:21:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愉快的旅行回忆 想要倾诉的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.22,0:21:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此之多
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.82,0:22:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该从何说起呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.65,0:23:50.75,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(295,550)}{\4c&HD8F1E9&}雏鸟 孵化
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.55,0:23:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庭院里的鸟巢里 只有一颗蛋被留了下来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.33,0:23:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 拜托你了 反正你很闲嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.07,0:23:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 要让我来孵这个蛋?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.89,0:23:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO 变大了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.16,0:23:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要破了 好像快要孵出来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.99,0:23:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子 那只辰未的雏鸟我要了

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 少しだけ大人の色に染まる指先
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 指尖稍露成年的沧桑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 照れくさそうに そっと隠して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 你就害羞得将它悄悄收起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 頬杖ついた君 見つめてる視線の先に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 手托下巴的你将视线投向
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 小さな蕾が ゆらゆら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 那随风轻曳的小小花蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} ねぇ 僕なんて いまも迷いばかりで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 喂 现在的我仍迷茫依旧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} あの日贈った言葉 今さら思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 这才回想起 那日你的临别赠言
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「君色に未来染めて...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「将我的未来染成你的颜色...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ 聞いていてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 听我倾诉好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ わがままいいですか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 让我任性好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手に入れた途端に消えてしまいそう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}拥有的瞬间仿佛就会消散
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}言葉をくれませんか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不说点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あなたがいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}因为有你在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}それだけで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう世界が変わってしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我的世界就会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}モノトーンの景色が ほら 鮮やかに映る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}映入眼眸的单调景色也会光鲜亮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}いつのまにか 離れていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不知何时却已离开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手を繋いで歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}牵着手 向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}上手く愛せているかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}能够好好去爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あの空に聞いてみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}天空也许会回答
