Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Banner3,方正兰亭黑_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,80,80,0,0,1,1,0.8,8,0,0,10,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text000,0000,,{\be1\blur2\shad2\bord1}破碎的镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.01,0:24:16.02,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1\pos(177,296)}现影之物
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.60,0:09:36.60,Banner3,NTP,0000,0000,0265,,{\bord1\shad0\b1\fs40\3c&H111111&\fsp8}第二天
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.61,0:09:42.65,Banner3,NTP,0000,0000,0265,,{\bord1\shad0\b1\fs40\3c&H111111&\fsp8}第三天
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.15,0:09:48.11,Banner3,NTP,0000,0000,0265,,{\bord1\shad0\b1\fs40\3c&H111111&\fsp8}第四天
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.10,0:01:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  快看快看  打雷闪电咯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.89,0:01:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真吵啊  我现在在做作业
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.91,0:01:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  你害怕吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.43,0:01:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会分散我注意力的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.46,0:01:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把窗帘拉…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.48,0:01:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是落到森林里了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.69,0:02:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和平时散步的路线不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.99,0:02:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是在学校附近呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.01,0:02:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底想去哪呢  猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.30,0:02:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去找被闪电劈中的树
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.26,0:02:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪电？ 是指昨晚的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.37,0:02:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇心真大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.97,0:02:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无知的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.09,0:02:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很多被闪电所劈中的古树上
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.13,0:02:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会泉涌出绝非现世之物的美酒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.93,0:02:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是流传于妖怪之间的传说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.17,0:02:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还是免费喝酒的好机会呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.24,0:02:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边  快跑  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.85,0:02:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.62,0:02:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  老师  你在哪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.82,0:02:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.20,0:02:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.22,0:03:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.46,0:03:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有声音  说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.58,0:03:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在树上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.99,0:03:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪着光呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.26,0:03:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在闪光呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.33,0:03:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.76,0:03:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.82,0:03:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.95,0:03:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传说中的…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.69,0:03:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢  有什么东西在发光
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.65,0:03:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.82,0:03:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕  有什么东西掉到眼睛里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.80,0:03:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.70,0:03:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这种地方做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.90,0:03:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼吗  你在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.76,0:03:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,横穿这个森林是为了抄近路啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.78,0:03:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.02,0:03:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  昨晚起在这附近…能听到些声音
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.38,0:03:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.10,0:03:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚是有小妖怪们在闹腾着
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.26,0:03:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目真是厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.67,0:03:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我听到的不是那种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.69,0:04:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些匆忙慌张  像是在找什么东西的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.35,0:04:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.34,0:04:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么东西要过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.19,0:04:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.49,0:04:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.82,0:04:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.32,0:04:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.60,0:04:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.68,0:04:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  刚刚那是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.73,0:04:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道只是阵疾风而已吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.29,0:04:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了  田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.70,0:04:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过别再替我挡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.58,0:04:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若有个万一就太危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.59,0:04:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不过夏目你要是有个三长两短也不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.64,0:04:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.28,0:05:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咳…总觉得有些小害羞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.89,0:05:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对不用隐藏自己的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.12,0:05:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互相都是第一次如此亲密
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.00,0:05:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而很难将两人之间的距离拿捏妥当
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.09,0:05:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美酒啊  真是美酒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.92,0:05:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狸猫妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.06,0:05:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是狸猫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.67,0:05:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是夏目家的胖…猫太老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.76,0:05:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记不住我的话  就叫我老师好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.44,0:05:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  跑哪去了  猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.34,0:05:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是去喝酒了呗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.54,0:05:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这醉汉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.68,0:05:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝醉酒了的是怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.61,0:05:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪少在那说怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.71,0:05:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪和怪物不同
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.90,0:05:41.78,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪老师喝太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.78,0:05:44.69,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒本来就是为了喝醉而准备的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.64,0:05:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我走这边回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.26,0:05:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  再见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.10,0:05:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.83,0:05:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是一如既往地被妖怪缠身的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.90,0:05:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因为有能理解我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.17,0:05:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才让我觉得有些快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.19,0:06:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果田沼也是这样认为的话就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.53,0:06:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头疼…这是怎么了  有不妙的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.27,0:06:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  早上好  看起来很困呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.50,0:06:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨  早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.94,0:06:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好  收到文化祭的相片了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.23,0:06:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想着要给你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.70,0:06:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？ 文化祭?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.63,0:06:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.61,0:06:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  弄错了  这是被迫照下来的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.73,0:06:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.82,0:06:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目的装扮很可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.00,0:06:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这照片上的我看起来相当地疲惫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.83,0:06:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这张照片不错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.16,0:06:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.51,0:06:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有田沼的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.46,0:06:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,张着嘴巴在睡觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.54,0:07:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是在后台小睡的时候被偷拍的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.76,0:07:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个能替我交给他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.63,0:07:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.25,0:07:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.81,0:07:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.81,0:07:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北本
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.47,0:07:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.79,0:07:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他今天缺席
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.84,0:07:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说是感冒了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.28,0:07:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.05,0:07:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  要还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.22,0:07:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来探病的吗  谢谢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.87,0:07:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高烧是退下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.94,0:07:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是传染给你就不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.80,0:07:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天应该能去学校
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.78,0:07:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼他很容易受妖怪影响啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.81,0:07:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会是因为昨天过于接近妖怪了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.61,0:07:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是那么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.20,0:07:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是因为那家伙太孱弱了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.41,0:07:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.07,0:07:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那也是为了保护我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.80,0:08:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在我的保镖饮酒作乐的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.32,0:08:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.28,0:08:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能怪你和我走散了  笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.59,0:08:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么  你这大肥猫
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.41,0:08:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那般孱弱的家伙随他去好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.89,0:08:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准说孱弱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.34,0:08:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孱弱  孱弱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.40,0:08:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.55,0:08:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.81,0:08:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是感冒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.95,0:08:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  不过还没有痊愈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.55,0:08:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂时和我保持点距离比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.13,0:08:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.82,0:08:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  出什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.19,0:08:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  镜子突然间就碎了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.53,0:08:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为很旧了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.41,0:08:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是粉碎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.37,0:08:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿扫帚…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.41,0:09:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚一瞬间感觉到有人影
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.13,0:09:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是错觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.17,0:09:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.51,0:09:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.39,0:09:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行  最近总觉得是妖怪在作祟
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.89,0:09:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼的感冒能快点痊愈就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.74,0:09:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒怎样了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.03,0:09:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  还没好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.62,0:09:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.75,0:09:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我要先去下教职员办公室
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.12,0:09:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.90,0:09:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.02,0:09:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  明明之前都还在的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.75,0:10:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.22,0:10:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.87,0:10:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挖这洞…到底是想做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.85,0:10:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了…右眼突然…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.67,0:10:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.70,0:11:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是哪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.59,0:11:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是后庭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.03,0:11:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么…两手都是泥巴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.53,0:11:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.41,0:11:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.09,0:11:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.47,0:11:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…眼睛疼得不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.19,0:11:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.16,0:11:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来你到底在隐瞒些什么  田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.39,0:11:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有烦恼的话  就说给我听啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.01,0:11:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.26,0:12:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  并非有意要躲着你的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.25,0:12:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那时起身体就沉重无比
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.39,0:12:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有证据说明我被附身
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.88,0:12:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更没有必要让夏目你担心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.49,0:12:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许真的只是个感冒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.07,0:12:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是直到刚刚我才注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.55,0:12:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身在后庭满手泥巴的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.95,0:12:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样可是第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.92,0:12:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.49,0:12:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  夏目你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.14,0:12:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.59,0:12:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实跟你说了之后舒服多了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.35,0:12:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独自一人伤神可不会开心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.82,0:12:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.68,0:12:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我也从那天开始…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.33,0:12:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来份鱿鱼烧怎样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.73,0:12:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鱿鱼烧  我要你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.73,0:12:57.56,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(407,356)}I want you
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.18,0:13:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.18,0:13:00.52,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(352,356)}I want you
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.92,0:13:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.50,0:13:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好幸福啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.10,0:13:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼吸困难  这小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.45,0:13:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快被勒死了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.87,0:13:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且刚刚突然剧痛无比
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.49,0:13:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在疼痛消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.31,0:13:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后校园内还有个手拿铁锤的妖怪到处游荡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.89,0:13:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道这些是否有联系
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.65,0:13:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.30,0:13:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.44,0:13:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  听到了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.92,0:13:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是拿着铁锤的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.18,0:13:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可别又说什么「你先回去」的话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.60,0:13:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我不会说的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.23,0:13:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这间教室吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.82,0:13:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后些
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.23,0:14:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦  不是都说了要你退后些了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.94,0:14:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我退后了啊  只是我比较高而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.51,0:14:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚的那个看到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.32,0:14:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩  虽然模模糊糊的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.22,0:14:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又把镜子打碎了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.23,0:14:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙到底是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.29,0:14:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.66,0:14:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  有什么东西在发光
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.01,0:14:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼痛消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.09,0:15:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铜镜的碎片吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.71,0:15:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.09,0:15:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我  还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.52,0:15:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那个还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.13,0:15:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了  我的镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.34,0:15:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.38,0:15:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  不对
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.40,0:15:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是附在田沼身上的妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.43,0:15:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.55,0:15:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.18,0:15:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.23,0:15:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明只是个人类
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.86,0:15:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然有如此了不起的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.53,0:15:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快从田沼身上出去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.05,0:15:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.38,0:15:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.40,0:15:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让镜子碎掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.60,0:15:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找寻朋友的途中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.58,0:15:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不料被闪电击中
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.28,0:16:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要去找寻碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.18,0:16:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但被闪电击中恢复得很慢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.55,0:16:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就借这孩子让我稍作休憩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.13,0:16:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让田沼挖坑也是为了找这镜子的碎片？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.98,0:16:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易…是我好不容易得到的镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.78,0:16:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决不能那么简单就放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.03,0:16:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碎片是会遇见闪光的东西就钻进去隐藏起来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.64,0:16:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且看来有一片是掉进你眼里藏起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.09,0:16:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要接近其他的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.84,0:16:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会产生共鸣要求拾起碎片而隐隐作痛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.57,0:16:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么把镜子还回去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.91,0:16:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把眼睛给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.68,0:17:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.48,0:17:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.59,0:17:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  不管怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.42,0:17:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就暂时让我停留在这个躯体里面了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.89,0:17:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.22,0:17:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.16,0:17:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心好了  不会更换他的意识太久
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.39,0:17:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过想让我将他平安无事的归还于你的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.06,0:17:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就来帮我吧  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.64,0:17:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要那有镜子的眼睛的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.08,0:17:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收集碎片也不会太难
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.55,0:17:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要镜子回来的话  我自会离去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.54,0:17:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少擅自作主了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.39,0:17:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.54,0:17:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎能再让你陪她去冒险
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.69,0:17:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  给我滚出去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.18,0:17:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还…还不行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.33,0:17:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在镜子碎片收集齐之前
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.34,0:18:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决不会离去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.15,0:18:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.07,0:18:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到我的驱妖之光都不离开
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.02,0:18:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何等执着的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.35,0:18:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼君
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.75,0:18:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.39,0:18:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.95,0:18:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情缘由都听到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.42,0:18:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要收集齐镜子的碎片的话就会出去的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.58,0:18:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  正是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.12,0:18:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是最安全的了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.37,0:18:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚还不是盛气凌人地嚷着说快出去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.80,0:18:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要是拿出全力来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.71,0:18:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种程度的妖怪早就拜拜了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.22,0:18:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是过于蛮干的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.52,0:18:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小子的身心可就危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.05,0:18:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样也没有关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.58,0:18:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.85,0:18:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要替我收集齐镜子的碎片就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.10,0:18:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.10,0:19:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又觉得自己的身体不听使唤了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.84,0:19:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  不好意思  能否陪我一起去收集镜子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.28,0:19:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  当然  一起去找
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.67,0:19:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.87,0:19:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也来帮忙  可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.11,0:19:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了  多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.43,0:19:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  该怎么找呢  那个镜子…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.85,0:19:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妖怪说过
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.72,0:19:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦接近其他的碎片的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.26,0:19:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会产生共鸣要求拾起碎片而隐隐作痛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.37,0:19:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想只要我的右眼作疼的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.88,0:19:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那附近应该就有吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.39,0:19:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初在后庭眼睛就开始疼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.33,0:19:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.47,0:19:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边也有碎片吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.39,0:19:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.70,0:19:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿铲子什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.57,0:19:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  有劳了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.77,0:19:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚是在这附近眼睛就开始疼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.37,0:19:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.91,0:19:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这里…这里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.16,0:19:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里吗…挖这里就好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.28,0:19:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.89,0:20:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.09,0:20:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着  夏目  现在就找
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.70,0:20:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在做什么呢  他们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.79,0:20:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道啊  是在练习话剧吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.37,0:20:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.39,0:20:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.73,0:20:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  只是玻璃碎片啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.36,0:20:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妖怪的镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.01,0:20:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般是看不到也摸不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.36,0:20:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么到底怎么样才能找到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.12,0:20:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.81,0:20:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.79,0:20:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.44,0:20:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…看不到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.29,0:20:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是在碎片的下面
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.06,0:20:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪她告诉我的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.04,0:20:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼痛也舒缓了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.79,0:20:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定没有错  就是这个了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.69,0:20:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.77,0:20:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.71,0:20:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和刚刚的那块合得起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.99,0:21:03.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合成一块了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.62,0:21:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.03,0:21:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…到底发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.63,0:21:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  夏目接下来是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.81,0:21:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这附近再找找看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.01,0:21:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个缜密的活啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.57,0:21:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是就在那附近
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.48,0:21:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛痛痛…那里…就是那里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.79,0:21:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.26,0:21:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.17,0:21:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在干啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.63,0:21:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来是的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.54,0:21:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天再接着干吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.03,0:21:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.43,0:21:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不知是因为被附身了还是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.37,0:21:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有些明白了…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.96,0:21:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.75,0:21:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.52,0:21:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是相当重要的镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.85,0:22:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎其友人重病
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.97,0:22:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个镜子拥有能够驱除那重病的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.12,0:22:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了朋友？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.35,0:22:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有给出了警告
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.48,0:22:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警告？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.53,0:22:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个镜子拥有相当强大的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.05,0:22:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有盯上那镜子碎片而去的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.94,0:22:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是要多加小心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.85,0:22:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盯上碎片而来的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.41,0:24:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目总是看着这样的世界吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.29,0:24:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快离开田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.60,0:24:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我最重要的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.86,0:24:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也曾有朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.65,0:24:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没说就离开了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.29,0:24:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙或许也有什么打算吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.97,0:24:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此我也想帮上他什么忙
