[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.72,0:01:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要有点猫的样子哦 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.54,0:01:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 为什么非得来这么远的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.88,0:01:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.58,0:01:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不是因为先生最近变胖好多
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.00,0:01:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才陪你出来散步的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.94,0:01:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 地震了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.11,0:02:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是天气变凉了 所以毛长长了而已 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.49,0:02:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是蚱蜢 蚱蜢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.58,0:02:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有蚱蜢在跳 蚱蜢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.37,0:02:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.28,0:02:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 不小心打盹睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.53,0:02:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.74,0:02:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 没事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.32,0:02:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.89,0:02:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺青?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.26,0:02:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢...谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.02,0:02:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生 休息时间结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.62,0:02:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那人不是名取周一吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.77,0:02:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取周一?那是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.05,0:02:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么呀 他是现在正走红的演员啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.26,0:02:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.69,0:02:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓了一跳 有一瞬间还以为是先生变的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.17,0:02:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先拍名取先生的远景 然后...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.34,0:02:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取...周一
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.23,0:03:04.30,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱妖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.35,0:03:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绳子?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.16,0:03:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是绑着的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.95,0:03:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妖怪吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.73,0:03:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 绷带快散掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.69,0:03:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要帮你绑好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.98,0:03:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区人类别来管我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.69,0:03:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 不要随便跟妖怪讲话啦 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.60,0:03:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.55,0:03:50.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我居然如此随便地跟妖怪讲话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.97,0:03:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗子 骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.75,0:03:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君 为什么尽说些令人恶心的谎话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.25,0:04:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也差不多该把过去的事忘记了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.42,0:04:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.65,0:04:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn迷你简隶变}{\1c&H000000&}{\bord0}{\pos(360,330)}{\b0}{\shad1}{\4c&HFFFFFF&}我去喝酒了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.22,0:04:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又去喝了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.58,0:04:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.95,0:04:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.04,0:04:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.57,0:05:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.24,0:05:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被看到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.40,0:05:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 反正对方看不见刚才那东西
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.69,0:05:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 没什么 你别介意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.98,0:05:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.71,0:05:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看到刚才那个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.75,0:05:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.03,0:05:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也能看到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.46,0:05:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「能看到」是指...看到什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.76,0:05:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛 大概是被称作妖怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.16,0:05:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事怎么会...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.43,0:05:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.13,0:05:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 没认出来吗 白天有碰到过一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.11,0:05:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫名取 名取周一
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.52,0:05:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试探了一下 你似乎不仅看得见妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.34,0:05:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且也拥有很强的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.67,0:06:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 貌似听迷糊了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.28,0:06:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 因为太高兴了有点忘乎所以
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.06,0:06:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你是同伴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.04,0:06:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同...同伴?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.61,0:06:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.50,0:06:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.62,0:06:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘了哦 便当
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.94,0:06:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.57,0:06:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 今天早上似乎一直在发呆
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.38,0:06:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.69,0:06:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.00,0:06:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「甚至最后变成了一种习惯 把无主的尸体扔到门里来了」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.69,0:06:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,45)}{\fs23}译注:出自 芥川龙之介 作品「罗生门」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.37,0:06:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你是同伴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.55,0:06:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同伴? 但他说在试探我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.95,0:06:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是在捉弄我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.19,0:06:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.13,0:06:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼? 嗯 没事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.89,0:06:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振作点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.14,0:06:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 我竟然会如此动摇
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.76,0:07:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 站在门那边的人 像不像演员名取周一
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.79,0:07:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 真的 还真有点像
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.72,0:07:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取周一啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.39,0:07:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.91,0:07:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把我当成笨蛋呀 就算是我也看电视的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.91,0:07:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过像他那种演员不是我喜欢的类型
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.40,0:07:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托走路的时候离我远一点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.63,0:07:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.97,0:07:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢太过引人注目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.70,0:07:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪我太耀眼了 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.24,0:07:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想跟你聊一聊 能稍微奉陪下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.81,0:07:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.88,0:07:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的是人类呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.12,0:07:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为气息很不可思议 还想实际上是不是妖怪来着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.88,0:07:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟要跟我说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.83,0:08:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要不要来帮我一起工作
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.48,0:08:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到工作的话...难道是指拍电视吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.10,0:08:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是私底下的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.89,0:08:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上我也在做驱妖的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.33,0:08:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱妖?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.66,0:08:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好需要个助手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.18,0:08:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说应该也是个不错的学习机会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.33,0:08:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 要不要试次看看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.96,0:08:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.71,0:08:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是任性啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.23,0:08:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是钱吗...是想要钱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.96,0:08:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.00,0:08:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开个玩笑 你还真是没有耐性啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.91,0:08:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 那个刺青原本是那种形状的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.78,0:08:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺青竟然动了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.16,0:08:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害啊 你连这个也能看到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.04,0:08:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个痣可以游走全身的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.21,0:08:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痣?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.34,0:08:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候在我的脚踝处发现了这个痣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.01,0:08:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二天还以为它消失了 结果是移动到左手去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.34,0:09:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是很恶心呢 调查过后才知道是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.57,0:09:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了知道解决的方法 下了很大功夫去学习
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.75,0:09:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是自学的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.86,0:09:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对身体有什么影响吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.10,0:09:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因为没什么特别的 反倒令人毛骨悚然
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.03,0:09:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果其实是寿命正在被吃掉的话 就伤脑筋了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.54,0:09:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人一直都是独自一人与不安对抗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.56,0:09:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不觉得好笑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.18,0:09:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.17,0:09:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这傲慢的小鬼是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.81,0:09:38.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请...请问 客人 您怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.58,0:09:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是贫血吧 抱歉 请拿杯水来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.11,0:09:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.31,0:09:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 不要乱来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.35,0:09:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我重要的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.65,0:09:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许你这么失礼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.39,0:09:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼的人是你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.45,0:09:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别随便跟我的猎物搭讪 小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.38,0:09:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.80,0:10:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.08,0:10:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...那个珍奇的动物是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.21,0:10:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人 带猫咪进店很令人困扰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.23,0:10:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.10,0:10:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论看几次都觉得十分有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.90,0:10:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.83,0:10:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...是我家的猫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.39,0:10:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.63,0:10:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 那是骗你的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.53,0:10:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生其实不是猫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.69,0:10:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.87,0:10:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 还真是个可爱的手下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.45,0:10:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是手下 是他师父 黄毛小子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.38,0:10:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 你对主人做什么 你这只肥猫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.81,0:10:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么 你这卷卷毛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.51,0:10:54.94,zhu_bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 等下 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.15,0:10:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肥猫 VS 卷卷毛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.98,0:10:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.40,0:11:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来介绍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.56,0:11:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右边的是笹后 左边是瓜姫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.18,0:11:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是在我手下做事的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.40,0:11:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次接到了某个世家的委托
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.47,0:11:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个常年封闭的仓库 据说打开就会受到诅咒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.84,0:11:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家主人因为财政上遇到了困难便找来当铺老板
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.51,0:11:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿到钥匙的当铺老板打开仓库
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.15,0:11:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和家主人一起挑了值钱的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.88,0:11:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自那之后 打开了仓库的当铺老板每晚会做噩梦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.75,0:11:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也曾差点遇到事故 总是发生些不吉利的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.45,0:11:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是妖怪搞的鬼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.05,0:11:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前去调查的这两只妖怪是这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.30,0:11:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家的祖先积存了值钱的东西 并将其封印了之后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.67,0:11:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪就定居在那间仓库里 拒绝人类的进入
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.41,0:11:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是让人伤脑筋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.57,0:11:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪们向来都是不合理又烦人的存在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.97,0:12:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗 不知道具体情况的话 什么都...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.66,0:12:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是善良啊 想替妖怪说话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.36,0:12:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种说法不要...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.69,0:12:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 名取先生有戴眼镜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.43,0:12:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是平光的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.54,0:12:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,透过玻璃或镜子看妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.18,0:12:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会比直接用肉眼看更容易看到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.97,0:12:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像手镯一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.67,0:12:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次看到你笑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.56,0:12:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来这痔也有有用的时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.87,0:12:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个善良的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.70,0:12:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,善良又普通的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.79,0:12:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.10,0:12:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么觉得好丢脸的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.52,0:12:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.87,0:12:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么明天去当铺老板的家宅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.28,0:12:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会在那里等你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.76,0:13:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没说会帮忙哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.53,0:13:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.88,0:13:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.04,0:13:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.60,0:13:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那树丛里面有什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.82,0:13:13.45,zhu_bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.85,0:13:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不快点离开的话 会把名取先生也牵连进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.23,0:13:16.51,zhu_bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.74,0:13:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我就在此...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.22,0:13:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过了吧 你用不着偷偷摸摸的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.05,0:13:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.19,0:13:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请住手 他已经受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.95,0:13:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊 他可是冲着你来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.31,0:13:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.22,0:13:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.25,0:13:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,袭击人这种事怎么可以原谅呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.25,0:13:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的「驱妖」是指做这种事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.45,0:13:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然让他们受伤 太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.02,0:13:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因妖怪而受苦的你 应该能够理解吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.89,0:14:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果是这种做法 我无法认同
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.77,0:14:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果抱着这种心软的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.82,0:14:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终受伤的还是你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.19,0:14:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使如此 我还是比较容易接受那样的结果
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.69,0:14:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.05,0:14:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.70,0:14:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇到可以看见相同事物的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.36,0:14:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但原来与那人之间相互理解是那么地困难吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.47,0:14:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明应该是跨越相同的痛苦一路走来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.30,0:14:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被他触碰的一瞬间 我可以感受到他对妖怪的憎恨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.67,0:14:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说 他因为妖怪也受了不少苦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.64,0:14:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得不到任何人的信任
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.38,0:14:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这绳子是?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.57,0:14:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不住手 小毛孩
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.66,0:14:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.72,0:15:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这绳子是谁绑的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.71,0:15:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.92,0:15:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那孩子的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.06,0:15:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.85,0:15:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.03,0:15:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在是很在意 能让我帮你绑好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.06,0:15:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要绑好了 你再无视我也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.34,0:15:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某个地方的...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.94,0:15:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.11,0:15:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从前某个地方的祈祷师帮我绑的这绳子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.23,0:15:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原本是山的守护者
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.50,0:15:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他抓到我后将我绑在了那根柱子上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.09,0:15:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且命令我保护这家宅和仓库
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.51,0:15:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你一直...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.22,0:15:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近有人打开了仓库
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.17,0:15:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不完成使命
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.15,0:15:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这绳子就会渐渐收紧 最后切断我的头
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.47,0:15:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指甲都...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.22,0:15:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前曾想过要逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.95,0:15:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但最后还是放弃了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.93,0:16:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死心之后一直一个人坐在这里发呆
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.33,0:16:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好几年
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.93,0:16:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好几年
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.30,0:16:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.00,0:16:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的假面
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.67,0:16:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的手在流血哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.32,0:16:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是人类的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.33,0:16:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你一样能够看的到我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.73,0:16:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那孩子给我绑的绷带
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.73,0:16:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也曾想过仓库被打开的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.25,0:16:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去完成使命 就那样等自己断命也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.01,0:16:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有任何留恋
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.39,0:16:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但缘分真是奇妙的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.15,0:16:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子作为驱妖人回到这小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.34,0:16:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能成为那孩子的功劳也真让人高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.32,0:16:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为异类真是麻烦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.77,0:16:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连这样一块布的谢礼都无法好好传达
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.17,0:17:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟 还想着你不会来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.40,0:17:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那些日本纸撕碎后 遮盖住这画在地上的图阵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.40,0:17:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,47)}{\fs23}译注:日本纸 和纸 与洋纸对应 \N分为手抄纸和机器抄 前者质量好 后者产量多
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.26,0:17:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生知道有关今天要驱除的妖怪的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.22,0:17:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是脖子上套着绳子 没有自由的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.00,0:17:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是应该要驱除的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.69,0:17:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然名取先生不记得了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.02,0:17:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得阻止她来这里才行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.02,0:17:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想去哪里 捣乱的话可是很让人困扰的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.89,0:17:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里老实待着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.15,0:17:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.05,0:17:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.00,0:17:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.06,0:18:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 人类
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.79,0:18:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都做不了 安分点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.96,0:18:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.52,0:18:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点出去 我没办法停住这雷电
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.22,0:18:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.50,0:18:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.02,0:18:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的假面
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.89,0:18:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的手在流血哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.33,0:18:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每当摔倒的时候 妈妈都是这样给我处理的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.14,0:19:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过妈妈已经去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.27,0:19:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的身体很虚弱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.23,0:19:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我能看到奇怪的东西而招来了不幸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.47,0:19:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔们是这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.89,0:19:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.97,0:19:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在变成那样之前有人来消灭我就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.91,0:19:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个多话的小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.97,0:19:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是小鬼 我叫周一
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.49,0:19:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人啊 人类是没有招来不幸力量的能力的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.57,0:19:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.83,0:19:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个善良的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.61,0:19:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,善良又普通的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.39,0:19:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.13,0:19:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能遇到你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.15,0:19:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然是这么地高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.66,0:19:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没发现
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.28,0:20:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是那时的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.64,0:20:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脖子上的咒缚也烧断了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.69,0:20:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本我的打算是一半一半的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.07,0:20:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是无法逃离咒缚的可怜妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.04,0:20:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就想狠下心让她逝去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.81,0:20:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果顺利的话 她可以捡回条命
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.20,0:20:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烧掉绳子或许能让她自由
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.94,0:20:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能活下来太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.42,0:20:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 夏目 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.26,0:20:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不是想以这种方式把你牵连进来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.63,0:20:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着你就想起从前的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.40,0:20:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想着自己或许能帮上什么忙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.68,0:20:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想和你说说话而已
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.88,0:20:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.54,0:20:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 像你这样乱来是不能当助手的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.68,0:20:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 那真是太遗憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.34,0:20:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.91,0:20:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是 怎么变得如此油腔滑调的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.37,0:20:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候明明很纯真的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.48,0:21:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.00,0:21:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你说我天真 我还是无法认同你的做法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.05,0:21:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样也好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.83,0:21:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用不着意见完全一致
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.22,0:21:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与别人相互理解是很困难的事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.01,0:21:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是谁都是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.68,0:21:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有困难的时候 无论何时都可以找我商量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.41,0:21:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想成为朋友的力量啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.12,0:21:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妖怪女孩 好不容易才恢复自由
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.75,0:21:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到「柊」的名字后 这次竟然成了名取先生的手下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.93,0:21:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然似乎是自己决定的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.07,0:21:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是喜欢的对象吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.31,0:21:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过那种个人的喜悦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.69,0:21:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也只有本人才能够了解
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.41,0:21:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.33,0:22:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.90,0:23:50.35,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,540)}浅葱之琴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.72,0:23:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类啊 你的身体借我用一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.98,0:23:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.80,0:23:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 这家伙是我的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.11,0:23:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候成先生的东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.45,0:23:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让浅葱再最后弹一次琴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.54,0:23:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托 已经没时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.20,0:22:12.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.20,0:22:12.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.14,0:22:20.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.14,0:22:20.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:26.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:26.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.57,0:22:33.50,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.57,0:22:33.50,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:44.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:44.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.55,0:22:48.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.55,0:22:48.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:58.40,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:58.40,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:06.04,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:06.04,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:13.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:13.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.10,0:23:20.46,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.10,0:23:20.46,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.46,0:23:27.18,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.46,0:23:27.18,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
