[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.07,0:02:10.03,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}东方森林
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.05,0:24:16.02,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\pos(208,296)}小小的妖怪
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.22,0:01:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是久违了  夏目贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.38,0:01:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场先生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.58,0:01:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然会偷溜进来  犹如猫或妖怪的样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.53,0:01:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  是你的手下妖怪强行把我拉进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.55,0:01:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  那真是失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.47,0:01:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过也好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.47,0:02:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正想找你好好聊聊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.78,0:02:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  今天没跟着你吗  那只猫
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.73,0:02:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目消失了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.51,0:02:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  抓了条不错的鮠鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.04,0:02:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想着要献给夏目老大
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.27,0:02:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既没在家也没在那叫做学校的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.40,0:02:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会是先前出现的那群东方的猴子干的好事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.80,0:02:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不太清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.66,0:02:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三筱大人说坐落在那附近驱妖人的别院之处
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.34,0:02:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又开始狩猎妖怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.14,0:02:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是为了与其相对抗而盯上了友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.10,0:02:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.57,0:02:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.47,0:02:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.79,0:02:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是东方的…有何贵干
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.40,0:02:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那叫做夏目的小子在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.78,0:02:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把同伴还给我们
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.52,0:02:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡说些什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.02,0:03:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道不是你们将夏目给拐走的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.20,0:03:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们确实将他带去东方森林了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.17,0:03:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他执意不愿交出友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.54,0:03:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  正在那时同驱妖人勾结
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.07,0:03:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夺走了我们的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.94,0:03:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才不喜欢人类之子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.51,0:03:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目在哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.38,0:03:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的同伴在哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.94,0:03:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若将他藏起来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.88,0:03:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,定当知道后果怎样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.54,0:03:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天保佑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.75,0:03:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽没啥义务要帮那些家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.47,0:03:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我看不惯你们冤枉夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.57,0:03:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我们冤枉他？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.22,0:03:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目是绝对不可能同驱妖人勾结的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.47,0:03:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不会掠夺妖怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.33,0:03:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.81,0:03:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快给我滚  我正饿着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.53,0:03:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.05,0:03:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…救了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.95,0:03:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到东方猿面军团的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.90,0:04:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得应该是由叫做六花的有名望的妖怪所率领
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.37,0:04:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会抢夺人类的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.40,0:04:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算怎么做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.92,0:04:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想听吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.10,0:04:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过夏目殿下还真易招惹麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.46,0:04:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明早点放弃友人帐就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.97,0:04:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他才不会放弃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.18,0:04:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你就抢过来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.70,0:04:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他专心生活在人类的世界中就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.44,0:04:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是真为夏目殿下着想的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.51,0:04:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目不希望变成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.59,0:04:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.67,0:04:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真搞不懂人类的心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.94,0:04:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之请先喝点茶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.65,0:04:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  没下毒
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.39,0:04:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来真是对我极其怨恨呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.11,0:05:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我冒昧  有何要事？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.14,0:05:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前不也说过了吗  对你有些兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.88,0:05:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要加入的场一族？ 夏目贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.23,0:05:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那次以来对你进行了多番调查
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.58,0:05:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双亲离世以后  辗转寄宿于亲戚家中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.40,0:05:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也曾被孤儿院收留过
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.87,0:05:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但因为有些孩子恐惧你的言行举止
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.37,0:05:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快就离开了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.74,0:05:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定吃了不少苦头啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.66,0:05:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己能看到  别人却看不到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.01,0:05:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不得不如此生活下去…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.90,0:05:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若加入我麾下的话就不用再担心那些事情了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.00,0:05:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都是知情人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.14,0:05:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惧怕你言行的人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.36,0:05:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得毛骨悚然而疏远你的人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.37,0:05:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我这里都不会有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.26,0:05:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同无法给与理解之人一起生活的痛苦也…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.55,0:05:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.83,0:06:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何故？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.90,0:06:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有过痛苦的确是事实
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.43,0:06:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是也遇见过许多内心善良的人们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.75,0:06:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比方说现在照顾着你的藤原夫妇吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.15,0:06:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是若了解了你的全部之后还能够接受你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.34,0:06:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能见到别人看不见的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.94,0:06:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们俩…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.51,0:06:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那和你没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.23,0:06:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.30,0:06:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我话还未说完
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.97,0:06:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.91,0:06:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原以为是因为你在人类的冷漠中长大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.42,0:06:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而被妖怪夺去心智同他们结伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.15,0:06:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来也并非如此
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.47,0:06:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何同妖怪做伴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.87,0:06:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会迷惑人类然后背叛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.96,0:06:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也应该有经验的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.97,0:06:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且不止经历过一两次了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.23,0:06:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实如此
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.09,0:07:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…不只有这些
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.64,0:07:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有不是那样的妖怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.15,0:07:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇见了很多…是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.99,0:07:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么不对的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.22,0:07:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是重复之前所说过的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.79,0:07:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你想说人类同妖怪是一样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.28,0:07:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.37,0:07:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.59,0:07:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  原来猫儿也在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.93,0:07:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这里了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.62,0:07:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.55,0:07:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说过少得寸进尺了  驱妖人小子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.80,0:07:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀气汹汹呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.11,0:07:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来这个能派上用场
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.13,0:07:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.66,0:07:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的书包  替我找到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.83,0:07:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走人了  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.16,0:07:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.45,0:08:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.33,0:08:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.64,0:08:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全被妖怪夺去了心智
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.76,0:08:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该清醒一下了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.38,0:08:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.47,0:08:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请让开
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.04,0:08:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那妖怪会留在你身边是因它能得到某种利益
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.60,0:08:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并非是喜欢你或是抱有任何感情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.13,0:08:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请离开那
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.15,0:08:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请让开
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.95,0:08:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我关到大牢里去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.89,0:08:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决不能让他们再前行半步
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.96,0:08:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要保护住首领
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.16,0:08:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.86,0:08:58.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.24,0:08:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散开
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.94,0:09:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在未抓捕你们的首领六花之前
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.35,0:09:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不会离开这片森林的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.55,0:09:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不会交出首领的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.34,0:09:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何？ 为何如此执着于这片森林
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.93,0:09:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何执着于首领
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.61,0:09:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们对人类做了什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.81,0:09:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理由很简单
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.94,0:09:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说这片东方森林
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.12,0:09:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在名为六花的妖怪的庇佑下享得安宁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.64,0:09:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当家对此等能力强大的妖怪有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.70,0:09:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为这个？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.84,0:10:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是和驱妖人有关联
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.60,0:10:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是什么来历
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.84,0:10:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的主人  夏目殿下在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.59,0:10:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.38,0:10:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要较量一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.29,0:10:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.20,0:10:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之感谢搭救
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.62,0:10:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若不是你们赶来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.17,0:10:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们估计就要被抓走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.41,0:10:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  叫做六花的在哪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.26,0:10:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首领藏身于安全之处
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.76,0:10:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是薄情寡义呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.11,0:10:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.17,0:10:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟敢侮辱我们首领  别想轻易得到饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.87,0:10:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来就是那样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.46,0:10:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你们前去抢夺友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.36,0:10:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己则躲在森林深处求自保
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.16,0:10:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.94,0:10:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首领才不是那种人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.98,0:11:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他正沉睡着
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.51,0:11:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉睡着？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.27,0:11:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么友人帐是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.83,0:11:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.95,0:11:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我们还是去会会六花吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.04,0:11:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿了  好无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.33,0:11:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  美酒  鱿鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.80,0:11:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快端上来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.18,0:11:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少痴人说梦了  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.06,0:11:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.04,0:11:28.01,Banner,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪退散
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.67,0:11:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场那小子  原本想要报复他来着…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.62,0:11:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明自己先趴下…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.99,0:11:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.97,0:11:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是有谁会去保护自己的保镖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.99,0:11:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保护的是友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.96,0:11:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是顺便保护老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.53,0:11:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.41,0:11:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.19,0:11:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既不打算操控妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.79,0:11:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不打算领导他们的人类之子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.09,0:11:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持有友人帐又有何意义
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.36,0:11:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然连这种小妖怪都吐槽你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.12,0:11:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我都说了  把它交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.20,0:11:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给小白猪有啥用
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.16,0:11:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我首领
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.26,0:11:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.52,0:12:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这种货色  我塞满信封扔到大海里去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.29,0:12:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像在这
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.69,0:12:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.96,0:12:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.76,0:12:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们被夺走的同伴在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.47,0:12:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  在这里  在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.90,0:12:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  那个声音  绝对没错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.42,0:12:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到竟然会关进那里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.14,0:12:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  绝对不可饶恕  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.77,0:12:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.97,0:12:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关押他的可不是我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.45,0:12:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要蒙骗我们吗  人类之子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.08,0:12:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.46,0:12:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以…那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.56,0:12:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得确认一下里面的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.83,0:12:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定友人帐就在其中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.22,0:12:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.98,0:12:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要碰那个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.93,0:12:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越说越可疑了  赶紧的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.68,0:12:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.80,0:12:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.68,0:12:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐没在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.71,0:12:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确认过了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.63,0:12:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.95,0:12:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  还是先把我放出去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.53,0:12:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看守就要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.22,0:13:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场先生的式卫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.71,0:13:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧逃走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.45,0:13:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.63,0:13:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉有些在意就过来看看了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.73,0:13:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然有吸引妖怪的力量啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.28,0:13:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有吸引啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.78,0:13:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么是谁召唤的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.24,0:13:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的猫吗  还是？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.73,0:13:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  根本就不用召唤
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.39,0:13:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是我的同伴就能轻而易举地潜入这…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.70,0:13:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天地清净  邪魅尽除…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.83,0:13:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛…好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.74,0:13:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.06,0:13:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.64,0:13:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给它些惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.02,0:13:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪竟敢擅自闯入人类的住宅
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.83,0:13:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.33,0:13:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和这个妖怪没有关系的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.25,0:13:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算是杀一儆百
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.95,0:13:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来也不像是有用的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.84,0:13:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对人类也是相当不恭敬
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.04,0:14:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请住手  拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.20,0:14:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.89,0:14:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.43,0:14:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多也该动真格地让他安静些了吧  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.86,0:14:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.04,0:14:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对这种半吊子的家伙手下留情是最麻烦的了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.34,0:14:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真敢称呼我为半吊子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.96,0:14:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好歹我还是的场一族的当家…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.33,0:14:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁吃你那套
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.71,0:14:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又让他给逃跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.35,0:14:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得救了  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.10,0:14:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是保护友人帐  顺便救你的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.23,0:14:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢了  没有告知你同伴友人帐的所在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.83,0:14:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是无法理解
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.57,0:15:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于人类来说  妖怪就如同浮云一般的存在吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.60,0:15:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护了它们  能有什么好处
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.94,0:15:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是没有办法的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.50,0:15:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体不由自主就行动起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.62,0:15:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真正珍贵的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.44,0:15:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们就要走了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.96,0:15:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在的场他们赶来之前  赶紧逃走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.84,0:15:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简单的封印  就让你同伴替你解除吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.46,0:15:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.44,0:15:36.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  或许正如你所说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.67,0:15:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是抢了友人帐回去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.33,0:15:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首领或许会是一脸悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.98,0:15:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.82,0:15:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.90,0:15:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类之子  你竟敢将我们骗入的场手中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.73,0:15:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的…我从未做过那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.07,0:15:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊  我虽在这里面但也得到他的搭救…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.40,0:15:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别被骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.98,0:16:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么为何不交出友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.61,0:16:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若想要帮助我们的话  交出来就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.15,0:16:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.15,0:16:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.81,0:16:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.67,0:16:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.98,0:16:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我适可而止
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.79,0:16:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.90,0:16:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.06,0:16:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.43,0:16:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.22,0:16:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.72,0:16:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.94,0:16:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不祥之人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.47,0:16:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不祥之人  不祥之人…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.78,0:16:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.75,0:16:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底要招来多少灾厄才满意？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.27,0:16:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失掉  给我消失掉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.27,0:16:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.52,0:16:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恨的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.34,0:16:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.89,0:16:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  我来让他消失
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.52,0:16:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是这家伙还是友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.17,0:16:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会回到该回的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.69,0:16:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说  我也是保镖
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.99,0:17:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再打他主意的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.35,0:17:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的敌人就不是除妖人  而是本大爷我了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.56,0:17:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时都放马过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.46,0:17:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.31,0:17:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三筱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.83,0:17:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首领
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.51,0:17:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首领大人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.46,0:17:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  你们在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.04,0:17:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟擅作主张
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.47,0:17:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望您能原谅他们的无礼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.59,0:17:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.86,0:17:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是统治东方这片森林名为六花的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.18,0:17:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六花因为那些除妖人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.04,0:17:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在森林里到处封印而被剥夺了力量
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.88,0:17:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在深山里被一群猿面保护着  一直在沉睡当中
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.20,0:17:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才让他们感到不安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.93,0:17:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了力量而要剥夺友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.87,0:17:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何等肤浅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.50,0:17:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  友人帐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.71,0:18:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏你们几位的到来  部分结界被解开了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.85,0:18:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才能够苏醒过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.15,0:18:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁还会去剥夺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.81,0:18:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.71,0:18:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  那群臭猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.65,0:18:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道夏目大人是我们八原妖怪的恩人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.95,0:18:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然还敢动粗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.54,0:18:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动粗  动粗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.59,0:18:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中级？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.52,0:18:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.14,0:18:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.33,0:18:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  请放心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.16,0:18:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心  放心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.90,0:18:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要干架了哦  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.85,0:18:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在喝下祈祷之水
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.82,0:18:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化身鬼神相助
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.97,0:18:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.66,0:18:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堂堂正正一决胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.13,0:18:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜负  胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.76,0:18:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  放马过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.03,0:18:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手  别再火上浇油了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.71,0:18:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放他们走真的好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.44,0:18:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使没有友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.58,0:19:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也应该借助他们的力量来恢复森林原样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.48,0:19:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们已经帮了大忙了  没发现吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.18,0:19:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.59,0:19:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的主人总是不召唤我  真是头疼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.24,0:19:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  三筱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.23,0:19:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是那样  还不如把友人帐给别人好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.21,0:19:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.93,0:19:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有代替我归还名字的人在的话也可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.05,0:19:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可是说好要交给我的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.31,0:19:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力量太悬殊了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.19,0:19:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算将我们所有的式卫召集起来  也许还是对付不了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.22,0:19:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果统治森林的是那个叫六花的妖怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够派上用场的妖怪在这片森林里或许已经没有了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.70,0:20:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要放弃森林吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.14,0:20:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.85,0:20:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  做法有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.99,0:20:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样  东方的森林被解放了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.97,0:20:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事件总算平息下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.37,0:20:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  八点集合啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.30,0:20:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别迟到了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.41,0:20:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目要多吃点肝脏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.59,0:20:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为贫血请假  肯定是缺铁  缺铁
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.21,0:20:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铁  铁
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.07,0:20:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肝脏  肝脏
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.65,0:20:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  难道说又出什么问题了？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.98,0:20:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.61,0:20:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘了说件事了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.05,0:20:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.75,0:20:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个叫学校的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.77,0:20:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你的朋友面前让你做了些奇怪的举动
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.01,0:21:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目老大  烤好了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.54,0:21:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上过去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.74,0:21:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于你  就算没有友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.82,0:21:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有妖怪肯为你奔走呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.69,0:21:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  他们是我的朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.23,0:21:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将来的某个时候应该能够将这份心情说出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.67,0:21:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.39,0:21:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要答应我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.34,0:21:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来晚的时候  一定要给家里打电话哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.55,0:21:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.46,0:21:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直说一定一定
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.45,0:21:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志已经是高中生了  晚点也没关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.25,0:21:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.80,0:21:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  拉钩
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.96,0:21:47.90,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撒谎的话  要吞千针
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.72,0:21:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心中这份喜悦让我有点焦虑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.01,0:21:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要再多穿一点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.69,0:21:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是滋以前穿过的  是不是有点大了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.68,0:22:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  很暖和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.99,0:22:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  个子很快就会长高
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.39,0:22:08.22,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明年肯定正好合身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.19,0:22:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每日的温馨让我有晕眩的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.22,0:22:09.01,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.53,0:22:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不再逃避  差不多到该认真了解的时刻了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.12,0:22:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.48,0:22:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太慢了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.67,0:22:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我决定了要好好保护友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.31,0:22:21.02,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.50,0:22:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有好好吃了肝脏没？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.17,0:22:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我决定将听到的和看到的都坦然接受地活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.32,0:24:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滨  野良  小个子
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.49,0:24:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  要养喵咪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.33,0:24:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明有了我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.97,0:24:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捡到了…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.00,0:24:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是还真是随便的名字啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.34,0:24:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师也帮忙想想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.03,0:24:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  这一只
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.18,0:24:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  刷子动了
