[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.29,0:02:21.29,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur2\shad2\bord1}夏目游戏帐
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.78,0:01:36.53,Banner,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\1a&H20&\an2}期中考试  最后一天  数学
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.14,0:01:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束了  夏目  你怎么样了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.58,0:01:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.23,0:01:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为睡眠不足  脑袋完全停止运转了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.09,0:01:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是笨蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.03,0:01:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熬夜这种临时抱佛脚的做法真是太不成熟了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.21,0:01:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熬夜是为了把名字还给妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.37,0:01:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不出口呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.76,0:02:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先不说这个  考试都已经结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.15,0:02:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起出去散散心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.89,0:02:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  什么  又要去哪里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.34,0:02:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛呀  不要凑过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.02,0:02:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么关系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.31,0:02:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想去这个美术馆
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.30,0:02:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不会去那种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.15,0:02:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.53,0:02:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不再去钓鱼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.19,0:02:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么意思  已经是秋天了要不去摘葡萄吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.79,0:02:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊   要去个能增加学习经验的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.14,0:02:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么连玩都非要去那种地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.98,0:02:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.93,0:02:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好呢  你们想去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.63,0:02:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.98,0:02:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是出游的计划吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.10,0:02:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去海边吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.56,0:02:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么冷  怎么可能去海边啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.17,0:02:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.00,0:02:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得最近田沼给人的印象有点不同了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.22,0:02:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.97,0:03:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然班级不一样  不是很了解
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.38,0:03:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得更酷了一点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.89,0:03:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不太会和其他男生闲聊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.73,0:03:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说我们一直在瞎扯闲聊吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.28,0:03:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  但是夏目例外哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.32,0:03:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙其实是同类哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.00,0:03:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.87,0:03:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  是的  田沼也是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.74,0:03:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目和田沼都是转校生   开始都很沉默
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.50,0:03:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  是的  还以为是很难接近的家伙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.32,0:03:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他们聊过之后  原来也和我们一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.26,0:03:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有两人都经常贫血晕倒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.69,0:03:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.79,0:03:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.20,0:03:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是麻烦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.19,0:03:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是去钓鱼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.18,0:03:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你自己嫌那个没趣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.59,0:03:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.59,0:03:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都已经长大了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.44,0:03:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.63,0:03:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是这样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.47,0:03:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候要去玩的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.00,0:04:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使只是附近的空地就已经玩得十分开心了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.24,0:04:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.95,0:04:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类  就该是随着年龄的增长来玩相应的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.87,0:04:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快我们就该学会成年人游戏了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.40,0:04:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成人游戏吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.42,0:04:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.49,0:04:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.87,0:04:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说小时候不管玩什么都很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.70,0:04:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有这样的烦恼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.59,0:04:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.88,0:04:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候每天都有活动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.36,0:04:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候玩了什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.33,0:04:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的话  玩过家家  打弹珠等等
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.19,0:04:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我玩过探险队游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.39,0:04:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探险队？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.64,0:04:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  带上附近的小孩到净水厂去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.42,0:04:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来被骂得很惨呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.35,0:04:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种游戏我也玩过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.62,0:04:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在总寺院里玩捉迷藏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.02,0:04:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏在作为文化财产的神殿里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.42,0:04:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被老爹发现把我狠狠地揍了一顿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.49,0:05:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捉迷藏和捉鬼游戏是少不了的游戏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.26,0:05:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踩影子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.51,0:05:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.27,0:05:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前总是玩踩影子的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.48,0:05:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被踩到影子的话  就要做鬼的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.89,0:05:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个的话我也…知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.73,0:05:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个谁都知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.57,0:05:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.86,0:05:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法加入他们  只能从远远的地方看着
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.43,0:05:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是没能决定去哪里玩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.31,0:05:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你总是反对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.34,0:05:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目想去哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.55,0:05:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.78,0:05:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说  去哪里都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.08,0:05:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能和大家一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.87,0:05:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅那样就已经很开心了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.07,0:05:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  对了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.99,0:05:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看过来  笑一个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.57,0:06:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛呀  突然…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.08,0:06:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是老师借给我用来记录文化祭活动点滴的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.17,0:06:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我顺便也拍些毕业纪念照
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.23,0:06:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕业纪念册？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.04,0:06:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得 还很早呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.44,0:06:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会啊  转眼之间的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.50,0:06:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼毕业以后  要继承寺庙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.89,0:06:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？ 现在还没有考虑过哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.89,0:06:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田应该会继续升学吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.82,0:06:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.15,0:06:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是那样  但是还没有确定要去的学校…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.02,0:06:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将来发展的方向啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.15,0:06:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了塔子阿姨和滋叔叔  要好好考虑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.56,0:06:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.67,0:06:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做的工作是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.37,0:06:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不  不可能  不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.55,0:06:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  等到充分过完高中生活以后再考虑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.98,0:06:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互相努力
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.13,0:06:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.01,0:07:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.37,0:07:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来啦  贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.55,0:07:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考试怎么样了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.95,0:07:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…啊  马马虎虎…大概…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.48,0:07:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛  辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.80,0:07:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天给你做天妇罗了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.31,0:07:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换了衣服就下来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.84,0:07:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.64,0:07:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.67,0:07:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来尝一下味道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.65,0:07:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.16,0:07:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.34,0:07:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.88,0:07:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.53,0:07:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面衣再放得薄一点就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.28,0:07:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滋  不准偷吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.50,0:07:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.00,0:07:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志就可以吃  我为什么就不能吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.09,0:07:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个可是虾啊  数量有限的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.52,0:07:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧吧  就一个而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.15,0:07:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  等会你要少吃一个
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.87,0:07:47.46,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我去换衣服了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.58,0:07:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来  夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.68,0:07:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.70,0:07:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事  都到这里来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.88,0:08:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师把你们叫来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.39,0:08:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能叫他们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.48,0:08:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有话要和你说了  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.89,0:08:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事啊  麻烦的事我就不管了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.83,0:08:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.04,0:08:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实明天是融合之月
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.93,0:08:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒也会变得很美味的夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.75,0:08:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好喝  好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.75,0:08:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,融合之月
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.12,0:08:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  而且今年的星星的走向非常不错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.44,0:08:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒会比平时香醇数倍
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.85,0:08:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们打算明天白天开始就聚在一起喝酒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.48,0:08:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝酒  喝酒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.23,0:08:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也算是缘分吧  聚集的都是夏目大人所熟悉的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.64,0:08:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就变成了在八原附近的破神社里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.87,0:08:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,举办思念夏目大人的宴会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.92,0:08:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八原  八原
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.33,0:08:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.34,0:08:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来让夏目大人分担让人无可奈何的烦恼之事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.86,0:08:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被召唤以后像狗一般忠诚的妖怪们的宴会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.43,0:09:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说  夏目组犬之会
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.35,0:09:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.72,0:09:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么名字啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.75,0:09:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以明天我们会来接你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.63,0:09:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们先来报告的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.88,0:09:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉  我不会去的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.13,0:09:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种诡异的宴会
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.78,0:09:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要这么见外嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.74,0:09:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我们不必那么客气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.93,0:09:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必  不必
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.58,0:09:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.49,0:09:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目老大  请一定要参加
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.53,0:09:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手  你们几个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.53,0:09:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志  快点下来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.69,0:09:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.69,0:09:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  今天先给我回去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.33,0:09:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.31,0:09:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师  你是我的保镖吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.31,0:09:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我想想办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.68,0:09:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是挺好的吗  去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.41,0:09:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会很开心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.22,0:09:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师只是想喝酒而已吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.88,0:09:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.55,0:10:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.90,0:10:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小猫咪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.88,0:10:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小猫咪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.77,0:10:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼  住手  住手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.02,0:10:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  快想想办法
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.09,0:10:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  好难受
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.06,0:10:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.28,0:10:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是又被诅咒了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.74,0:10:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是的  我决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.96,0:10:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想学会爷爷留下来的妖怪研究
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.45,0:10:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  我不会做出危险的事的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.46,0:10:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,画阵的时候  不会把它画完整  也会好好擦掉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.77,0:10:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有时也会像刚才那样  多复习几次
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.76,0:10:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一发生什么事  也可以帮上夏目的忙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.49,0:11:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用为我…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.26,0:11:02.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅仅是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.04,0:11:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然我还是不希望爷爷的信念就这样消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.43,0:11:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.68,0:11:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然还没有决定好将来做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.96,0:11:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我能做的事  就只有这么多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.15,0:11:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  请把我的名字还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.46,0:11:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.61,0:11:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  我陪你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.62,0:11:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨  不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.40,0:11:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点事  你先走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.09,0:11:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了  回头见
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.69,0:11:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护吾之人  显其名
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.55,0:12:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还汝之名
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.57,0:12:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.51,0:12:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是今早的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上钩了  抓住
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.10,0:12:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万岁  万岁  万岁
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.83,0:12:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.92,0:13:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.80,0:13:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…等等
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.47,0:13:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.53,0:13:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  你来得太晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.90,0:13:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.08,0:13:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太晚了  真是一如既往地悠哉着
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.75,0:13:19.20,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭候多时了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.77,0:13:21.81,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在开始要大喝咯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.74,0:13:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里这里  快来我这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.36,0:13:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  夏目老大  先敬三杯酒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.35,0:13:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我还未成年
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.57,0:13:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是老样子的固执呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.07,0:13:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痒  住手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.52,0:13:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.38,0:13:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红峰
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.46,0:13:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是久违了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.03,0:13:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说有免费酒喝就过来瞧瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.04,0:13:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你也在呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.35,0:13:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  是红峰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.00,0:13:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  斑大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.77,0:13:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次见到您怎么都是这么弱小无为般的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.99,0:13:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是目光短浅呐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.87,0:13:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这般形象还是很受欢迎的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.89,0:13:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在人类的女孩面前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.50,0:13:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.13,0:14:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是夏目老大  认识的大人物真多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.42,0:14:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.50,0:14:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀呀呀呀怎么样  呀呀呀呀怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.65,0:14:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  你也跳起来呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.53,0:14:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.42,0:14:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  人类的话一般都是玩什么来开心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.13,0:14:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想要知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.19,0:14:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩什么游戏呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.23,0:14:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会是怎样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.73,0:14:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扑克什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.10,0:14:31.19,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别突然间停下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.43,0:14:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,户外的话好像有踢罐头
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.70,0:14:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踩影子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.73,0:14:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踩影子？ 听起来很有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.72,0:14:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧  就陪不能喝酒的夏目大人玩踩影子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.86,0:14:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩吧玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.15,0:14:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  谁来玩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.01,0:14:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目老大  那是什么样的游戏呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.80,0:14:51.35,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  还要继续喝…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.97,0:14:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家知道躲猫猫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.65,0:14:55.14,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒…喝酒啦  小子  快给我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.74,0:14:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那个差不多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.82,0:14:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是影子被踩到的家伙就成为下一个鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.30,0:14:58.29,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌…喝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.70,0:15:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼？ 那个听起来很有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.95,0:15:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  鬼可以吃掉被抓住的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.42,0:15:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  完全不同
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.06,0:15:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是为了躲避被鬼踩到影子而到处逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.55,0:15:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者躲到其他影子后面以躲避鬼的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.71,0:15:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是只要跑到阴影里就行了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.37,0:15:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得那个若是超过五秒钟就算违规
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.74,0:15:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  那么最初我来当鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.57,0:15:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,范围就是这个神社境内
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.79,0:15:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.86,0:15:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概就是这样了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.10,0:15:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别过来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.64,0:15:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别来这边
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.90,0:15:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大骗子夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.27,0:15:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去一边去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.54,0:15:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走开
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.37,0:15:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来尝一口
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.78,0:15:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼 鬼 鬼…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.59,0:15:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.84,0:16:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思了  胡子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.88,0:16:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…这真是大意了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.04,0:16:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短腿生物在那边呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.87,0:16:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踩到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.27,0:16:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个轮到你是鬼咯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.33,0:16:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.55,0:16:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得很窝火
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.46,0:16:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪物之血沸腾了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.41,0:16:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  太好玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.02,0:16:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我踩…我踩…踩踩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.77,0:16:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  做好觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.79,0:16:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛  老师你已经不是鬼了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.84,0:16:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用多说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.44,0:17:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的夏目到处乱窜
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.33,0:17:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样可不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.61,0:17:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少开玩笑了  猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.43,0:17:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你是我的保镖…居然做这种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.17,0:17:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要认为我会原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.54,0:17:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑大人  动手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.60,0:17:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.85,0:17:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类都是软弱无力的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.58,0:17:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都给我闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.95,0:17:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻击影子之外的部分就是犯规  我应该说过了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.47,0:17:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是危险
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.54,0:17:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目你那不算违规吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.40,0:17:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就由最初被斑大人踩到的我来当鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.84,0:17:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三筱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.18,0:17:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久违了  夏目殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.08,0:17:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然把我们当成狗  还是那么有胆量呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.97,0:17:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是中级妖怪他们擅自…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.06,0:17:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我踩到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.14,0:18:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次就轮到三筱大人来当鬼了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.42,0:18:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是鬼？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.90,0:18:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就试试看咯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.69,0:18:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.73,0:18:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要踩逃跑的家伙们的影子就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.44,0:18:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  似乎是很有趣的游戏呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.51,0:18:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么快逃跑吧  下等的家伙们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.28,0:18:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三筱  不好意思  能不能替我们当裁判呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.68,0:18:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一…二…三
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.45,0:18:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是只要踩到影子就能随心所欲咯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.48,0:18:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有那样的规则呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.58,0:18:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  背光跑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.65,0:18:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快逃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.55,0:18:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总感觉…这个游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.31,0:18:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没个结束啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.09,0:18:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类真能想出这么恐怖的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.79,0:19:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  这该怎么样收场呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.10,0:19:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我一直只是在远处观望
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.28,0:19:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,详细的也不太清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.58,0:19:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.71,0:19:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么夏目老大也是第一次玩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.14,0:19:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算是明白孩提时大家为何会玩得那么开心了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.77,0:19:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁懂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.40,0:19:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何时起就认识了这么多的妖怪了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.91,0:19:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子她是否也稍微体会到这样的心情了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.88,0:19:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下轮鬼是斑大人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.20,0:19:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就作为最后一轮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.06,0:19:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,影子被踩到的家伙就当场失格
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.40,0:19:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全员的影子都被踩到的话就是鬼赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.02,0:19:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.19,0:19:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那鬼的运动量可不是小数目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.28,0:19:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好主意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.39,0:19:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么被踩到的家伙们就进到这圈里来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.94,0:19:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  真不想进去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.68,0:19:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  听我说话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.03,0:20:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…开始
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.68,0:20:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.28,0:20:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都给我等着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.15,0:20:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.28,0:20:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.11,0:20:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  再来一个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.00,0:20:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.09,0:20:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.42,0:20:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛  掉下来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.76,0:20:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过待在这里的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.15,0:20:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计暂时影子不会被踩到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.49,0:20:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着  老实点让我踩你影子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.39,0:20:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是那样说  有哪个傻瓜会等你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.99,0:20:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.54,0:20:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你是叫夏目吗  要不要一起玩？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.07,0:20:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不停地搬家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.47,0:20:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是有很多我刚到就立马跟我打招呼的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.29,0:20:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而也因为我尽说些莫名其妙的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.62,0:20:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被认为在说谎而被讨厌也是理所当然
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.07,0:20:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大骗子夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.69,0:20:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别来这边  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.75,0:21:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  转学生  你也来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.91,0:21:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目真好呢  到处搬家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.07,0:21:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是去了很多地方认识很多人了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.69,0:21:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.67,0:21:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.99,0:21:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天再见
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.49,0:21:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.97,0:21:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.22,0:21:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是会偷懒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.29,0:21:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快上来  你是最后一个了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.69,0:21:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要是被踩了就结束了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.11,0:21:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才一直躲藏起来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.75,0:21:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我上不去了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.63,0:21:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉我一把
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.87,0:21:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.88,0:21:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是尽添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.73,0:21:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.85,0:22:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.06,0:22:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.60,0:22:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也被踩到了阿
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.64,0:22:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然人类就是弱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.07,0:22:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.60,0:22:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家不是都被踩到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.56,0:22:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是鬼赢咯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.42,0:22:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就喝庆功酒咯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.26,0:22:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝贺啊  庆祝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.10,0:22:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,软弱无力真是不好意思了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.88,0:22:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会保护你的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.13,0:22:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被弱势的你召唤出来也是没有办法的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.53,0:22:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没办法  看上你咯  真是没辙
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.09,0:22:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.14,0:22:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.61,0:22:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来准备去田沼家
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.25,0:22:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续昨天的讨论
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.04,0:22:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.17,0:23:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在做什么呢  夏目  那边有什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.48,0:23:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.79,0:23:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.47,0:23:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再陪他们玩玩
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.76,0:23:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.60,0:23:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.37,0:23:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.94,0:23:28.53,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.25,0:23:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经非常讨厌自己可以看到妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.65,0:23:31.34,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  出发出发
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.14,0:23:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.46,0:23:33.10,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么你总是…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.86,0:23:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏于此才能让我有了这么多的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.81,0:23:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我便是如此坦诚地相信着
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.29,0:23:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的友人们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.41,0:23:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于现在的我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.26,0:23:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类也好妖怪也好都一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.39,0:23:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不可取代的宝物
