[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,1
Style: OP_jp,方正楷体_GBK,33,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,45,1
Style: OP_ch,方正楷体_GBK,36,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,5,1
Style: ED_jp,方正楷体_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,45,1
Style: ED_ch,方正楷体_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,5,1
Style: bt,方正楷体_GBK,55,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,33,&H00E8EEF4,&HF0000000,&H1E23384E,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text



Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.19,0:01:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说 听我说 5班有个超可爱的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.14,0:01:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是她稍微有点奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.75,0:01:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目 你在听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.43,0:01:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 在听呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.24,0:01:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她用清澈明亮的眼睛一直凝视着我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.53,0:01:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫什么名字
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.76,0:01:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字就不知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.45,0:01:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那女生平时都不怎么说话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.15,0:01:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.50,0:02:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要去哪里啊 夏目同学
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.45,0:02:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没要去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.47,0:02:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是5班有个很可爱的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.66,0:02:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊 快点儿 快点儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.90,0:02:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.05,0:02:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么夏目同学也要去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.07,0:02:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点儿 快点儿 休息时间要过了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.46,0:02:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.31,0:02:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在...在...啊 在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.51,0:02:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 看 就是她 就是她
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.79,0:02:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 很可爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.09,0:02:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过一副心事重重的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.05,0:02:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才是她的魅力所在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.18,0:02:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 机会来了 她要出来咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.23,0:02:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个... 我是2班的西村
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.35,0:02:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想跟你交个朋友 可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.29,0:03:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.77,0:03:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错吧  她确实是在看我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.14,0:03:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 那是你的错觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.97,0:03:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.19,0:03:20.18,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少女之阵
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.69,0:03:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.75,0:03:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来啦 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.79,0:03:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就可以吃饭了 去接它回来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.98,0:03:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.64,0:03:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是在后巷的空地附近吧 猫吉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.70,0:03:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.46,0:03:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.44,0:03:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 准备散步到什么时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.81,0:03:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你在哪儿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.01,0:03:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是夏目啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.09,0:03:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这儿呢 这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.84,0:03:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该回家了 先生 到吃晚饭的时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.00,0:04:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里等着 不会花太长时间的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.91,0:04:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿你没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.45,0:04:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是被昨天的大雨冲走了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.42,0:04:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 别提了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.91,0:04:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.65,0:04:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个奇怪的东西 是什么文字吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.66,0:04:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音 是妖怪么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.91,0:04:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在河边也见过跟这个类似的东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.69,0:04:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是什么诅咒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.53,0:04:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是赶快离开这里比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.45,0:04:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.88,0:04:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的东西是指什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.04,0:04:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊!!! 人类!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.80,0:04:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好小
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.12,0:04:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们说「赶快离开这里比较好」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.42,0:04:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在这里看到什么东西了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.51,0:04:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.72,0:04:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊~ 好可怕啊~
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.19,0:05:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,涂鸦吗 看上去像是什么阵
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.47,0:05:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.62,0:05:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是猫先生啊 不要吓我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.45,0:05:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 夏目 我抓到麻雀咯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.26,0:05:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要吃掉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.18,0:05:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 再多抓2只左右就可以用它们在空中散步啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.96,0:05:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散步~啊~~ 散步~
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.09,0:05:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该先减肥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.81,0:05:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是啥 从来没见过的阵呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.41,0:05:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 连先生都不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.77,0:05:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是想跟外星人取得联系的社团画的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.06,0:05:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔 这在我们的专长之外啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.49,0:06:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.90,0:06:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目同学
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.98,0:06:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.49,0:06:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 我刚才叫了你的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.12,0:06:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.20,0:06:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 这下麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.38,0:06:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.28,0:06:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.40,0:06:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定 一定会赢的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.06,0:06:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要赢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.18,0:06:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.93,0:06:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.31,0:06:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是她画的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.01,0:06:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「赢...」 到底是要赢什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.69,0:06:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她那认真的表情令我很在意
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.07,0:07:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大的风
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.19,0:07:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区人类竟敢盯着我看
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.63,0:07:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是狂妄 我要吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.24,0:07:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还剩360天 在那之前...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.22,0:07:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是做不到的话就算你输 然后
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.38,0:07:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.82,0:08:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么搞的 好奇怪的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.24,0:08:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道与昨天的事有关?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.61,0:08:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.48,0:08:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 什么都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.64,0:08:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才在看镜子的一瞬仿佛看到身上有字
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.77,0:08:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 怎么了呀 贵志 自我陶醉么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.22,0:08:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子婶婶 不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.41,0:08:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事 正处于这个年龄段嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.53,0:08:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.92,0:08:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 不在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.84,0:09:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.29,0:09:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜哇 妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.30,0:09:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎么进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.44,0:09:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 有个奇怪的小胡子进来咯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.12,0:09:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有好好布结界吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.04,0:09:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我这样的妖怪 那种单薄的结界根本不值一提
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.26,0:09:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目 你在吵什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.37,0:09:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇! 这个小胡子是什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.55,0:09:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱小的保镖也是多余的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.48,0:09:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我弱小!?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.95,0:09:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然是这样的大人物 到我这有何贵干
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.92,0:09:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事因人类而起 所以来拜托人类解决
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.48,0:09:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听闻如果是夏目大人的话 一定会有办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.46,0:09:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因人类而起?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.45,0:09:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上个月经过河边时
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.50,0:09:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小胡子!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.57,0:09:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我身边经过的老太太看到我竟大声尖叫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.58,0:10:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人能看到妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.18,0:10:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 只是个普通的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.86,0:10:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正想着竟会有这种怪事 不经意间往脚下一看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.61,0:10:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现自己站在一个奇怪的阵中
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.42,0:10:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阵?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.40,0:10:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个阵对妖怪来说非常不利
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.86,0:10:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姑且调查了一下 发现是个人类女孩画的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.35,0:10:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.18,0:10:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请跟我去阻止她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.21,0:10:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.00,0:10:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.30,0:10:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 快 在这边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.87,0:10:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.53,0:10:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不等等我啊 鲶鱼怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.03,0:10:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不是鲶鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.63,0:10:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲶鱼小胡子 快等下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.94,0:10:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要那样称呼我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.46,0:10:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.40,0:11:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这 就是那个女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.38,0:11:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是昨天的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.61,0:11:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身上出现的文字
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.59,0:11:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然与那个阵有某种关联吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.73,0:11:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.26,0:11:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.09,0:11:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 夏目同...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.36,0:11:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 又叫了名字
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.18,0:11:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 我有话...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.51,0:11:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.23,0:11:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.52,0:11:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.31,0:12:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.64,0:12:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可怕的怪物?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.20,0:12:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可...太可爱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.37,0:12:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么!?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.67,0:12:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暖暖滑滑的 感觉真好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.90,0:12:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要这样 先生不习惯被人夸可爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.45,0:12:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 一看到可爱的东西就控制不住
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.94,0:12:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了吗 夏目 喂 听到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.14,0:12:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么可高兴的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.69,0:12:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是5班的多轨透
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.43,0:12:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目同学 你能看见妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.82,0:12:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是听说的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.11,0:12:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听谁说的?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.59,0:12:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.89,0:12:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 你也能看见妖怪?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.29,0:12:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我看不见妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.49,0:12:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 只要是进入这个阵的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.58,0:13:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就能看见它的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.31,0:13:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是 为了能让我看见妖怪身影的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.58,0:13:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 夏目 请帮帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.65,0:13:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这是攸关性命的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.85,0:13:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.66,0:13:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与你的性命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.93,0:13:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶!?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.16,0:13:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个便签是过世的祖父留下的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.44,0:13:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这个图形很奇特 我经常模仿着在院子里画
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.44,0:13:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 有一天
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.35,0:13:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个圆圈里出现了一个小小的天狗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.11,0:13:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原本以为是幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.50,0:13:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是之后又看到了一些奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.70,0:13:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来才发觉「啊 这是妖怪啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.42,0:13:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家祖上似乎是阴阳师来着
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.81,0:14:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过世的祖父也一直很憧憬着想要看到妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.38,0:14:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴 就经常把这个阵画出来玩
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.55,0:14:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后到了去年
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.03,0:14:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到一个庞大且恐怖的妖怪走进阵里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.05,0:14:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妖怪注意到了我 并且说道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.17,0:14:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区人类竟敢盯着我看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.71,0:14:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是狂妄 我要吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.37,0:14:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就这样吃掉未免太无趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.95,0:14:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你360天的期限 如果能抓到我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.34,0:14:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你赢 我会放了你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.25,0:14:55.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但要是抓不住的话 你就输了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.54,0:14:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.62,0:15:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个梦是她的记忆吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.72,0:15:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我会顺着你的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.70,0:15:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你曾经叫过的名字中 从你最后叫到名字的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.58,0:15:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直往前回数13个 我会将这13人全部吃掉」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.01,0:15:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,13个人?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.17,0:15:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后 我都尽量不去说话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.82,0:15:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 可能在我不经意间还是叫了别人名字
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.95,0:15:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道 在同一所学校里还有这样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.61,0:15:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我一定要赢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.98,0:15:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫了你的名字很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.96,0:15:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是请帮帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.26,0:15:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被叫了名字的人都会和她一起受到诅咒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.02,0:15:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体上的那个「一」 原来是指被吃掉的顺序吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.23,0:15:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能看见这边的这家伙么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.74,0:16:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.19,0:16:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这样就能看见了么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.19,0:16:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸好大的小胡子!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.10,0:16:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.18,0:16:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说脸很大 但我也没给别人添过麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.59,0:16:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随着日期日益临近
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.99,0:16:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女孩就专注于依靠画阵来找寻吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.91,0:16:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.73,0:16:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你的大限也快到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.10,0:16:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐很快就是我的了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.53,0:16:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是我的保镖吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.75,0:16:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过养育了这么久
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.66,0:16:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要被别人吃掉了 还真可惜呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.88,0:16:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不记得你养育过我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.23,0:16:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志 吃饭咯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.37,0:16:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 吃饭啦 吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.03,0:16:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.30,0:17:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 真丰盛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.69,0:17:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为今天大减价
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.25,0:17:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滋叔叔回来得晚 我们先吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.62,0:17:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说 听我说 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.57,0:17:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天在超市的试吃柜台
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.39,0:17:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一不小心就和店里的人聊得兴起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.74,0:17:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉间就把试吃的维也纳小香肠全都吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.56,0:17:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真羞死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.35,0:17:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个叫多轨的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.50,0:17:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经忍耐着不讲话快一年了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.07,0:17:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了尽量不叫出别人的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.83,0:17:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是个喜欢说话的普通女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.42,0:17:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.03,0:17:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 这个金平真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.03,0:17:46.93,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,译注:金平牛蒡 一种日本菜肴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.93,0:17:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的么 太好了 有很多哦 多吃点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.77,0:18:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是一直无依无靠的我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.96,0:18:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也已不是能将生命随意丢弃的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.57,0:18:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要赢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.99,0:18:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么仅仅是看见 就要受到诅咒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.16,0:18:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以屈服于妖怪这种没道理的作弄
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.83,0:18:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是受到先祖的影响
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.87,0:18:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我画的阵好像可以提高妖怪的妖力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.14,0:18:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有看到妖怪资质的人就能看到阵中的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.13,0:18:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以到处去收集目击情报
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.31,0:18:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是没有头绪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.95,0:18:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过一些小妖怪告诉我说
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.03,0:18:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「夏目大人可以看见妖怪哦」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.87,0:18:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才知道我的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.02,0:18:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.65,0:18:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要猪排盖浇饭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.99,0:19:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有想试着跟你说话的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.59,0:19:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但又不知道是真是假
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.65,0:19:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我要炸虾盖浇饭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.68,0:19:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 说好要猪排的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.83,0:19:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说对吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.17,0:19:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要亲子盖浇饭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.09,0:19:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经好久没有这样跟人讲话了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.20,0:19:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.88,0:19:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都不能这样好好说话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.79,0:19:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会赢的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.90,0:19:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.37,0:19:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样 为了破除诅咒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.25,0:19:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开始和多轨搜寻妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.57,0:19:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多指教咯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.07,0:20:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.43,0:20:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以作为参考的只有额头的伤疤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.28,0:20:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天去池塘那边看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.15,0:20:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不快点的话只剩一个月了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.24,0:20:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 一定能找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.08,0:20:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那我去河滩那边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.53,0:20:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了哦 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.46,0:20:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么时候和她亲密起来的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.35,0:20:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲密?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.74,0:20:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装傻了 她是我的女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.85,0:20:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊? 你的女朋友?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.15,0:20:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 多轨的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.02,0:20:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她并不是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.19,0:20:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么? 都叫得这么亲切了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.68,0:20:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我连她的名字都还不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.37,0:20:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.69,0:20:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.91,0:21:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 好吧 反正我...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.48,0:21:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我支持你哦 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.38,0:21:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 西村
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.69,0:21:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,败给他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.89,0:21:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有~一个月~ 友人帐~就是我~的~了~
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.94,0:21:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说啊 先生你到底是不是我的保镖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.24,0:21:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有~一个月~ 友~人~帐~
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.66,0:21:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腿本来就短 还这样跑 很危险哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.43,0:21:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.04,0:21:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.67,0:21:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没用啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.97,0:21:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.02,0:21:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 跑哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.48,0:21:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.41,0:21:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.05,0:22:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.90,0:23:50.97,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,554)}{\fs52}勿唤其名
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.91,0:23:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目同学 把你卷进来真对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.38,0:23:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨 不必跟我道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.51,0:23:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也特别给你们帮个忙好了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.43,0:23:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 先生 你的后背
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.88,0:23:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 这不是我的名字嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.91,0:23:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去封印那个妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.46,0:23:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.02,0:23:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Oh No!

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 少しだけ大人の色に染まる指先
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 指尖稍露成年的沧桑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 照れくさそうに そっと隠して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 你就害羞得将它悄悄收起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 頬杖ついた君 見つめてる視線の先に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 手托下巴的你将视线投向
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 小さな蕾が ゆらゆら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 那随风轻曳的小小花蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} ねぇ 僕なんて いまも迷いばかりで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 喂 现在的我仍迷茫依旧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} あの日贈った言葉 今さら思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 这才回想起 那日你的临别赠言
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「君色に未来染めて...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「将我的未来染成你的颜色...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ 聞いていてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 听我倾诉好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ わがままいいですか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 让我任性好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手に入れた途端に消えてしまいそう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}拥有的瞬间仿佛就会消散
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}言葉をくれませんか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不说点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あなたがいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}因为有你在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}それだけで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう世界が変わってしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我的世界就会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}モノトーンの景色が ほら 鮮やかに映る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}映入眼眸的单调景色也会光鲜亮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}いつのまにか 離れていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不知何时却已离开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手を繋いで歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}牵着手 向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}上手く愛せているかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}能够好好去爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あの空に聞いてみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}天空也许会回答
