[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.31,0:01:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.05,0:01:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在上面签个名吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.65,0:01:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,签名?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.58,0:01:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要在旧校舍举办什么吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.73,0:01:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是试胆大会哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.20,0:01:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.62,0:01:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人数不够的话申请就无法通过
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.54,0:01:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮下忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.50,0:01:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有趣吧 这可是笹田的提案哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.52,0:01:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么拜托咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.63,0:02:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.10,0:02:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.63,0:02:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是觉得意外呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.33,0:02:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 我也没想到高高在上的班长同学会举办试胆大会
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.92,0:02:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.22,0:02:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那定下来了再联系你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.51,0:02:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.44,0:02:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然都看不见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.52,0:02:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不好 那再见啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.37,0:02:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂　夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.64,0:02:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙怎么了 突然慌慌张张的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.26,0:02:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.02,0:02:52.09,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露神之祠
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.98,0:03:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没追上来么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.20,0:03:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.59,0:03:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您是夏目铃子大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.50,0:03:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 铃子是我外婆
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.84,0:03:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已经去世了...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.03,0:03:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把友人帐交出来 不然就吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.21,0:03:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.98,0:03:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.59,0:03:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别捣乱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.15,0:03:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是像你这样的低等妖怪能掌握的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.32,0:03:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住口
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.13,0:03:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 友人帐已经约好等夏目死后由我来接收了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.68,0:03:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说已有预定了 你就乖乖消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.10,0:03:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该消失的...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.95,0:03:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.58,0:03:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...你是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.50,0:03:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快滚 不知好歹的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.46,0:03:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎哟哟
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.97,0:03:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.74,0:04:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道谢的话用七辻屋的馒头就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.77,0:04:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是喜欢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.20,0:04:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为友人帐而来找我的妖怪有两种
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.98,0:04:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一种是像刚才那样为了要支配被记录的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.21,0:04:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而窥伺着友人帐的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.76,0:04:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而另一种是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.25,0:04:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了 有人在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.84,0:04:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请求拿回名字的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.11,0:04:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 那家的馒头多少都能吃下呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.23,0:04:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 又归还名字了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.63,0:04:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.75,0:04:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 尽做些多余的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.03,0:04:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样友人帐不是越变越薄了么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.12,0:04:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归还名字之后就会觉得非常的疲惫
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.98,0:04:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道等我接手时还能剩几只妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.06,0:05:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干脆 把这小子吃了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.99,0:05:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了哦 阴险招财猫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.22,0:05:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.68,0:05:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多吃点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.53,0:05:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.90,0:05:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子婶婶既开朗又温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.10,0:05:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滋叔叔虽然话不多 但一直都很和蔼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.30,0:05:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 这么多就够了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.65,0:05:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不能给他们添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.60,0:05:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.23,0:05:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.25,0:05:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫猫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.63,0:05:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜哇 又任性地在制造麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.92,0:05:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不喜欢剩饭吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.28,0:05:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.78,0:05:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.42,0:05:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 真的吃了 还是个美食家呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.00,0:05:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.20,0:05:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 这是齿痕吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.36,0:05:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是相当美味呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.83,0:05:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.33,0:06:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 稍微有点呛到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.31,0:06:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸好塔子婶婶他们看不到
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.13,0:06:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人 希望您能把名字还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.18,0:06:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.08,0:06:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 仔细一看你不是露神老头儿么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.72,0:06:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 您的熟人么 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.43,0:06:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 变得这么小差点没认出来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.63,0:06:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 这声音是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.07,0:06:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 原来如此 你是斑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.84,0:06:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么变成这副可笑的样子了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.70,0:06:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再啰嗦　吃了你噢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.02,0:06:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.02,0:06:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「守护吾者 显现汝名」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.78,0:06:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这张吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.43,0:06:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 和下一张粘在一起了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.09,0:06:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢 紧紧粘在一起了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.04,0:06:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是饭粒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.75,0:06:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饭粒?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.89,0:07:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子大大咧咧的 大概边吃东西边翻阅的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.93,0:07:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.35,0:07:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.38,0:07:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要硬撕啊 皮都要被撕破了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.50,0:07:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是告诉过你了么 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.15,0:07:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把名字弄破的话 身体也会被撕裂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.65,0:07:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烧掉的话 身体也会化为灰烬
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.28,0:07:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对哦 对不起 露神
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.03,0:07:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 吓了我一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.50,0:07:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.60,0:07:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这样 你就放弃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.02,0:07:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.13,0:07:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志 可以洗澡了哟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.19,0:07:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.71,0:07:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能这样 真无情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.31,0:07:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是撕不开的话 想还你名字也还不了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.46,0:07:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想办法吧 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.44,0:07:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我的名字还给我 好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.74,0:07:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法就是没办法嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.48,0:07:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人～～～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.04,0:08:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露神就住在这前面的七森林
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.18,0:08:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说让我带着 我就带着了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.43,0:08:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这究竟是干什么用的?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.52,0:08:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防万一用 总之先收着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.82,0:08:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.93,0:08:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不 给
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.18,0:08:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你的好心 没摔坏的话就请收下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.32,0:08:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一个人的话也吃不掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.34,0:08:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 那我就收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.14,0:08:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好天气呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.86,0:08:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.67,0:08:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.24,0:08:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候 如果能应对的再机灵点的话就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.20,0:09:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真讨厌自己的笨拙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.29,0:09:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位婆婆 活不久了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.70,0:09:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻起来味道不怎么好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.82,0:09:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说这么失礼的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.20,0:09:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是...露神的祠堂?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.38,0:09:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 表情那么奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.09,0:09:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露神原来不单只是个名字 真的是位神明啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.10,0:09:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 来了吗 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.35,0:09:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙啊 昨晚做了失礼的行为 要遭报应了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.03,0:09:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该说 铃子外婆怎么没遭天谴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.62,0:09:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀　怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.47,0:09:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小子知道了你是真的神明 开始慌了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.35,0:09:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...那个 露神大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.06,0:09:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈 不是的不是的 虽然被称做神明
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.92,0:09:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我只是寄宿在这祠堂里的一只没有住处的妖怪而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.68,0:09:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从前这一带发生了一次大规模的旱灾
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.60,0:10:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村里的年轻人眼见这惨状 就向这祠堂祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.15,0:10:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果隔天碰巧下了雨
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.25,0:10:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从此之后 村里人就开始尊称这祠堂主人为「露神」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.28,0:10:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并开始奉上很多供品
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.05,0:10:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉间 我发现自己充满了力量 外形也变得越来越像样了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.48,0:10:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「像样」吗...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.95,0:10:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次遇到的时候还有「人」的大小吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.00,0:10:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在这里已经人迹罕至了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.14,0:10:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因信仰之力的减弱
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.15,0:10:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初变大的身躯也缩小成这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.68,0:10:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.06,0:10:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这个桃子给你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.22,0:10:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桃子我有哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.87,0:10:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.79,0:10:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样 是那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.07,0:10:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你遇到那个「小花」了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.75,0:10:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 原来婆婆的名字叫做「花」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.62,0:10:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是现在唯一一个还会来这儿参拜的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.71,0:10:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.59,0:10:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 一起归还么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.43,0:11:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 把粘着的那个名字也一并归还的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.91,0:11:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就用不着硬撕了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.25,0:11:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是 其中有个大问题
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.27,0:11:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不知道另一个名字的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.04,0:11:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 那个的话我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.56,0:11:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 真的吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.43,0:11:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被铃子打败后我很懊恼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.03,0:11:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说了下个被铃子夺走名字的妖怪的传闻后
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.90,0:11:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为感到幸灾乐祸 就偷偷跑去看了下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.87,0:11:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.48,0:11:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然忘了名字 不过是长这副样子的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.31,0:11:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是这家伙么?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.35,0:11:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 不愧是我 画得真好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.84,0:11:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有头发吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.91,0:11:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头发...没有的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.13,0:11:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一根也没吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.25,0:11:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一根也没吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.27,0:11:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时那家伙住在三塚山
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.61,0:11:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是影子的主人 能使用影子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.07,0:11:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么? 怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.19,0:12:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 笑什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.85,0:12:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在嘲笑我的画吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.12,0:12:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是 这两个该受天谴的家伙～～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.19,0:12:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们开始了在三塚山中寻找那个妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.54,0:12:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 花了好几天去搜寻
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.16,0:12:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终却还是没能找到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.65,0:12:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 好象很困嘛 找得很累了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.06,0:12:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.42,0:12:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 花婆婆是看不到的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.09,0:12:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明只是近在鼻息的距离
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.15,0:12:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.17,0:12:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.58,0:13:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是来参拜的吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.84,0:13:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.26,0:13:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.56,0:13:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近来的似乎就我一个了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.68,0:13:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还想露神大人是不是会觉得寂寞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.58,0:13:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您是从什么时候开始参拜的呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.32,0:13:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从小时候开始的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.03,0:13:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.17,0:13:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许笑我哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.11,0:13:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得曾有一次见到过露神大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.33,0:13:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.20,0:13:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在从女校下课回来的途中
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.69,0:13:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天也是个像今天一样的好天气
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.79,0:13:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我像往常一样在参拜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.10,0:13:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果抬头一看 在祠堂的后面看到了只脚
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.80,0:13:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有被吓到 但还是装出一副没看到的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.80,0:13:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 那个戴着老翁假面的人温和地说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.80,0:13:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,26)}{\fs23}译注:老翁假面 能乐假面的一种 用于老翁
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.80,0:13:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「今天真是好天气啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.09,0:14:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原本不由自主地就想回答「是的呢」的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.92,0:14:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但想到万一露神大人察觉到被人类发现的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.48,0:14:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定就会消失不见
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.99,0:14:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我现在一直在想
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.37,0:14:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会不加思索地说出来会更好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.41,0:14:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 露神大人不总是独自一人吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.05,0:14:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的话 会寂寞的受不了的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.39,0:14:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 即便只是一句回答...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.16,0:14:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「总是独自一人」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.00,0:14:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.05,0:14:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人的话会寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.42,0:14:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人的话会难受
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.25,0:14:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.30,0:14:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会难受
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.14,0:14:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好难受
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.63,0:14:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好重
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.21,0:14:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊 别乱来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.28,0:15:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你昨晚做噩梦了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.53,0:15:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是先生你太重了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.00,0:15:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你心灵出现空隙了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.31,0:15:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,软弱的心灵会招来妖魔
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.43,0:15:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想丢掉性命的话 无论何时都不能松懈心灵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.93,0:15:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 我倒是觉得你早点死掉的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.25,0:15:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能早点拿到友人帐 我反而觉得会比较开心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.66,0:15:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再梦游的话 就拔光你尾巴上的毛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.86,0:15:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是恶鬼么...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.46,0:15:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想被妖怪这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.75,0:15:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到他了 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.74,0:15:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.22,0:15:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙果然还在这座山里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.37,0:15:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫了他声后就逃跑了 不过应该还没跑远
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.63,0:15:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 要兵分两路吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.85,0:15:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.94,0:15:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.90,0:15:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉有什么不妙的东西过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.53,0:15:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙的?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.50,0:15:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.80,0:16:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.68,0:16:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那家伙 他自己出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.12,0:16:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和画一点也不像嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.00,0:16:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别乱说 不是一模一样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.37,0:16:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一样的只有那个字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.36,0:16:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 用镜子 反射阳光让它晕眩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.83,0:16:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.42,0:16:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.01,0:16:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.13,0:16:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了 我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.65,0:16:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来拿吃的东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.88,0:16:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.99,0:16:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.75,0:17:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 要不要和我比赛?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.23,0:17:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嬴了的话 就给你吃的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.58,0:17:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢的话 吃我也没关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.45,0:17:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是铃子 你叫什么名字?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.05,0:17:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 这家伙的名字是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.93,0:17:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.27,0:17:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.70,0:17:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「濯」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.78,0:17:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「露神」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.70,0:17:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「归还汝名」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.53,0:17:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有在听吗 露神
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.49,0:17:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有在听呢 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.46,0:18:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会一直有人来进贡的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.31,0:18:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也就只有一个桃子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.89,0:18:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.00,0:18:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类是非常势利而且无情的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.41,0:18:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁着还有力量的时候寻找新的宿地
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.57,0:18:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是为你好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.51,0:18:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.18,0:18:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 一旦被爱过
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.17,0:18:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱过 就无法忘怀了...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.04,0:18:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.79,0:18:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经可以一个人走了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.56,0:18:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个叫「濯」的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.77,0:18:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沿着影子来到村子里 向村民们讨要剩饭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.68,0:18:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为交换 会洗净那家人家里的碗盆后再回去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.62,0:18:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 你调查了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.89,0:18:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的话 就算到夜里街上也是那么明亮
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.62,0:18:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经再也见不到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.30,0:18:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山上还有他的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.09,0:19:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且与人划清界限的话 他们生活也会轻松许多吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.90,0:19:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗? 是这样的话就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.41,0:19:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露神 我带桃子来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.51,0:19:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露神?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.40,0:19:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这里 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.02,0:19:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 又变小了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.78,0:19:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.61,0:19:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在发光哦 怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.64,0:19:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 小花她去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.64,0:19:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小花长久以来都染病在身
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.30,0:19:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近好不容易才能来这里一次
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.19,0:19:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小花是最后一个信仰我的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.68,0:19:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她去世的话 我也会消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.78,0:19:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我来信仰你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.53,0:19:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不能每天来 我还是会来参拜的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.07,0:20:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 夏目大人 你是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.04,0:20:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就够了 我能和小花一起去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.05,0:20:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.11,0:20:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直...都只能看着她
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.89,0:20:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得终于...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.36,0:20:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于能够碰触到她了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.84,0:20:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她听见过的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.40,0:20:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花婆婆她有听见过你的...声音的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.80,0:20:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露神
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.86,0:20:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢您　夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.96,0:20:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是以前还是现在
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.19,0:20:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类都是可爱的生物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.38,0:21:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真是个好天气呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.60,0:21:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.29,0:21:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.72,0:21:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 怎么了 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.07,0:21:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 喂 你做什么呢 好浪费啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.64,0:21:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说会遭天谴的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.03,0:21:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里什么也没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.60,0:21:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算今天没有 可能明天就会有了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.86,0:21:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是诚心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.48,0:21:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 你在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.77,0:21:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这只蠢猫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.91,0:21:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?! 我是招财猫啊 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.18,0:21:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,26)}{\fs23}译注:日语中蠢猫与招财猫音非常相近
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.84,0:21:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.53,0:21:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么「喵」啊 把馒头还来 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.81,0:21:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.36,0:21:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住 你这馒头小偷
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.13,0:21:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的馒头
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.68,0:22:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买的人是我吧 站住
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.80,0:22:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不要 哔──
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.34,0:22:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵喵 喵～
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.02,0:22:12.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.02,0:22:12.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.96,0:22:19.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.96,0:22:19.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.92,0:22:26.39,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.92,0:22:26.39,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.39,0:22:33.32,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.39,0:22:33.32,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.08,0:22:44.37,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.08,0:22:44.37,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.37,0:22:48.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.37,0:22:48.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.76,0:22:58.22,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.76,0:22:58.22,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.22,0:23:05.86,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.22,0:23:05.86,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.86,0:23:12.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.86,0:23:12.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.92,0:23:20.28,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.92,0:23:20.28,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.28,0:23:28.00,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.28,0:23:28.00,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.77,0:23:49.58,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,540)}八原的怪人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.64,0:23:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目 八原的妖怪们哭着说被人类欺负了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.46,0:23:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是能看见妖怪的人的所为吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.00,0:23:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯! 那家伙 非常可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.78,0:23:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.00,0:23:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫田沼要
