[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.87,0:01:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪儿 到哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.14,0:01:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙 那个女人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.75,0:01:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪儿 到哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.17,0:01:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.76,0:01:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.61,0:01:55.50,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫与友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.81,0:01:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要打工的话还是要去海边吧 海之家
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.55,0:01:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 海边啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.99,0:02:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不好还会有美丽的邂逅之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.15,0:02:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有有 肯定会...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.17,0:02:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 这不是夏目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.22,0:02:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.82,0:02:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.99,0:02:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.09,0:02:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没...什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.59,0:02:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么没什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.15,0:02:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不满身是泥么 没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.80,0:02:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 这附近有神社吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.56,0:02:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神社的话 穿过这灌木丛应该...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.83,0:02:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.08,0:02:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目 他怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.92,0:02:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛那么匆忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.00,0:02:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.20,0:02:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚的是...?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.61,0:02:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好强的风
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.24,0:02:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还真是个奇怪的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.61,0:02:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转学以来都没怎么说过话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.66,0:02:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总感觉有点难以接近啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.10,0:03:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「在干什么」吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.92,0:03:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然看不见「那个」 真令人羡慕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.44,0:03:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站～住～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.88,0:03:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从小时候开始
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.39,0:03:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就经常会看见奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.46,0:03:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那大概就是被称为「妖怪」的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.39,0:03:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然本来就没什么好感
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.26,0:03:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但自从搬到这里之后
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.94,0:03:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是有追缠着我的家伙出现
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.54,0:03:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我不甚烦扰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.83,0:03:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候 只要逃进神社的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.05,0:03:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.28,0:03:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.26,0:03:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于抓到你了 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.87,0:03:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.40,0:03:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快...还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.66,0:03:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快...快
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.68,0:03:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.79,0:03:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先等下嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.78,0:03:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果叫了你的名字就麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.27,0:03:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防万一先把他舌头拔了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.99,0:03:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把舌头?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.58,0:03:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好...好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.38,0:04:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.62,0:04:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 别让他逃了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.04,0:04:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.27,0:04:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.29,0:04:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么总是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.14,0:04:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是我心甘情愿想要看到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.38,0:04:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀? 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.19,0:04:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盘子只要三个就够了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.08,0:04:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃? 但是 那边那位客人...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.98,0:04:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子 今天又说了奇怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.41,0:04:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想引人注意吧 觉得寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.16,0:04:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是这样吗 还是让人觉得不舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.91,0:04:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 就在那儿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.67,0:04:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪儿?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.65,0:04:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有啊 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.33,0:04:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的啊 仔细看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.10,0:04:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧 就在那儿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.57,0:04:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那儿 不正盯着这边吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.61,0:04:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.71,0:04:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了有的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.53,0:04:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的...有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.28,0:05:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 看不到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.90,0:05:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.09,0:05:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.38,0:05:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个...不会是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.58,0:05:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔喔 破了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.54,0:05:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印着我的结界破了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.05,0:05:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结界?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.54,0:05:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不妙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.95,0:05:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.98,0:05:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.25,0:05:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噗!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.50,0:06:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是个人类 看到我却不害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.17,0:06:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胆子还真够大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.97,0:06:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 说点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.06,0:06:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我习惯了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.99,0:06:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 狂妄的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.95,0:06:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊? 你不是夏目铃子么?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.59,0:06:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到你了 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.84,0:06:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.32,0:06:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 原来不是么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.78,0:06:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目铃子是我外婆的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.20,0:06:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外婆? 怎么 你是铃子的孙子么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.24,0:06:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 仔细瞧瞧的话是个男孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.41,0:06:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用仔细看也知道是男孩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.49,0:06:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和人类不一样 我们妖怪是不在意性别的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.79,0:06:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识我外婆吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.62,0:06:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 以前她住在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.30,0:06:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个美人呐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.08,0:07:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 跟你一样看得见妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.72,0:07:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是周围的人都看不见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.86,0:07:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 没有人能够了解她
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.79,0:07:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她总是一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.42,0:07:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是 总是...独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.10,0:07:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.17,0:07:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.96,0:07:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子她开始拿妖怪解闷
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.02,0:07:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道「友人帐」吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.54,0:07:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友...人...帐?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.08,0:07:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 说起来外婆的...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.05,0:07:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.45,0:07:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来啦 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.40,0:08:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子婶婶 我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.11,0:08:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 脸色不好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.95,0:08:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.49,0:08:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里不舒服吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.87,0:08:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不不 没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.53,0:08:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制服上都是泥巴呢 发生什么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.51,0:08:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 就是摔了一跤
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.04,0:08:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摔跤了? 哪里摔的?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.38,0:08:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没受什么伤吧? 有没有哪里痛?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.25,0:08:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 让您担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.40,0:08:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.71,0:08:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的话就好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.46,0:08:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事的话别顾虑要说出来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.61,0:08:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.42,0:08:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活泼是很好 不过也要注意呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.75,0:08:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.22,0:08:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「被妖怪追着回来」这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.70,0:08:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能对塔子婶婶说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.99,0:08:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想给她造成不愉快的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.16,0:09:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于父母早逝 我一直辗转于亲戚们间
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.48,0:09:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没有血缘牵绊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.53,0:09:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却一直这样在这些与我相关的人中间生活着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.04,0:09:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住到现在这个家里是上个月开始的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.48,0:09:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里 是我的外婆曾经住过的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.43,0:09:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说去世的外婆也和我一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.18,0:09:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够看到常人看不到的「那些」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.00,0:09:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也因为这能力而被周围人所厌恶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.95,0:09:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继承的遗物里 应该有...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.19,0:09:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个吗? 那只招财猫所说的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.39,0:09:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.55,0:09:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那个给我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.44,0:10:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是你该持有的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.54,0:10:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把友人帐交出来!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.94,0:10:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志 刚刚的声音是怎么回事啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.42,0:10:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱...抱歉 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.35,0:10:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 那么我出去买点东西 就拜托你看家啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.61,0:10:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 请慢走
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.57,0:10:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜喵...快点把我弄出去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.51,0:10:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.14,0:10:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦不不 先把我弄出去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.19,0:10:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再把友人帐给我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.09,0:10:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂时还是别管它了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.41,0:10:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 快点弄我出去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.11,0:10:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了那个就回去哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.28,0:10:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你寄住在这里吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.77,0:10:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这破猫好烦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.16,0:11:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫破猫啊 真失礼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.23,0:11:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这招财猫才不是我本来的面目呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.87,0:11:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原本的样子那真是优雅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.45,0:11:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 你不是猫咯?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.41,0:11:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不是说了么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.17,0:11:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵～喵～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.17,0:11:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,45)}{\fs23}译注:逗猫棒 猫喜欢捕捉快速移动的物体 摇动逗猫棒能让猫兴奋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.79,0:11:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不就是猫么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.52,0:11:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵～?! 不不 不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.58,0:11:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是因为身体习惯了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.79,0:11:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样 吃完这个之后你就回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.33,0:11:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想惹麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.78,0:11:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.22,0:11:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我知道了你拿着友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.74,0:11:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且打破结界对我也有恩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.82,0:11:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后我就是你的保镖了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.44,0:11:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我「先生」就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.37,0:11:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么保镖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.52,0:11:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是那么危险的东西吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.49,0:11:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 你不知道吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.95,0:11:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐里写有被夏目铃子打败的妖怪们的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.95,0:12:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.50,0:12:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子她对每个遇到的妖怪提出挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.25,0:12:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为生来便具有强大的妖力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.77,0:12:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子逢战必胜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.11,0:12:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且让每个输的妖怪成为她手下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.63,0:12:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并把名字写在纸上
Dialogue: 1,0:12:13.45,0:12:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,45)}{\fs23}译注:妖怪背上字为「笨蛋」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.45,0:12:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些签名汇成的册子就是「友人帐」了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.95,0:12:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是妖怪的名字么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.56,0:12:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说 被持有着契约书的人叫到名字的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.22,0:12:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不能违抗其命令的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.56,0:12:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 有了友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.47,0:12:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能够统领那些夺走名字的妖怪们了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.29,0:12:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧 很危险吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.72,0:12:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓜子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.92,0:12:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粘在嘴巴旁边了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.70,0:12:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 啊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.46,0:12:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.22,0:12:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以猫先生你才想要这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.29,0:12:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 笨蛋 不要这么粗鲁地对待友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.56,0:12:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄破文字的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.63,0:12:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字的主人也会受伤的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.63,0:13:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.59,0:13:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说的话 猫先生的名字也在这里面吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.91,0:13:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.03,0:13:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在说这是要小心对待的东西而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.12,0:13:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.10,0:13:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算什么眼神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.12,0:13:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能会被区区铃子打败呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.66,0:13:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不是被封印了么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.64,0:13:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那那那 那个呢 就有诸多诸多缘由了...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.55,0:13:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 比起那个
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.19,0:13:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐的力量远远超出你的想象
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.60,0:13:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此 那些被夺走名字的妖怪们都拼命地追寻着铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.99,0:13:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 处境很危险哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.05,0:13:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在家吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.40,0:13:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 来了来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.05,0:13:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在家吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.59,0:13:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 家里人现在都出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.62,0:13:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 果然呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.06,0:13:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然回来了 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.96,0:14:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来 把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.53,0:14:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在家吗? 还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.05,0:14:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.51,0:14:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀呀呀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.88,0:14:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.40,0:14:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想去哪里?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.94,0:14:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫去哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.20,0:14:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快躲到那树丛里去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.29,0:14:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下伤脑筋了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.64,0:14:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是人类能对付的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.48,0:14:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于明白了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.74,0:14:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说 就给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.52,0:14:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.42,0:14:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为...为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.01,0:14:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区人类居然想要站在众妖之上吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.90,0:14:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能有那种想法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.82,0:14:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到底是为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.88,0:15:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说那东西除了那之外还有什么其他意义么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.97,0:15:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这跟猫先生您没什么关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.69,0:15:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不和你浪费时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.21,0:15:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.54,0:15:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不给
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.14,0:15:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是先生您想要拿去乱用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.64,0:15:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那当然 这么有趣的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.86,0:15:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.50,0:15:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快交出来 不然就压扁你了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.08,0:15:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个啊 友人帐对我来说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.54,0:15:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是外婆留下的重要的遗物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.27,0:15:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确 外婆似乎和人处得不好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.57,0:15:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得她的人也几乎没有了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.76,0:15:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她年纪轻轻就过世了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.19,0:15:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 作为唯一和她有血缘关系的我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.14,0:16:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想让这种羁绊断裂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.88,0:16:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我不认为这是别人的事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.10,0:16:09.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 先生 我想还掉它们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.52,0:16:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么做才好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.31,0:16:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还掉?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.68,0:16:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字啊 我想还给妖怪们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.09,0:16:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 不要啦 太浪费了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.67,0:16:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且里面也有些凶暴的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.08,0:16:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有多少条命都不够哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.91,0:16:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 有先生您陪着我不是吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.56,0:16:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子外婆没有完成的事 我想去完成它
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.87,0:16:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一我真的中途丧命的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.10,0:16:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐就让给你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.09,0:16:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,助我一臂之力吧 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.25,0:16:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 在你消失的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.58,0:16:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的能拿走友人帐吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.36,0:16:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 可以
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.62,0:16:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我就陪你一程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.28,0:16:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.01,0:17:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 铃子 看我把你舌头拔掉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.24,0:17:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.51,0:17:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要友人帐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.56,0:17:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 只要有了友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.91,0:17:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能成为这一带妖怪的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.18,0:17:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也想这样吧 斑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.87,0:17:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把你和我相提并论
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.09,0:17:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下等货色
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.73,0:17:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.77,0:17:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先想象对方的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.47,0:17:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开友人帐 用心呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.56,0:17:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「守护吾者 显现汝名」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.02,0:17:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚吧 别再出现在我眼前
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.03,0:17:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.81,0:18:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来 需要的是铃子的唾液和气息
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.60,0:18:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为亲人的你 应该办得到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.01,0:18:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撕下契约书咬在嘴中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.55,0:18:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用劲合掌 心神凝注 发力吐气
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.35,0:18:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好寂寞 好寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.55,0:18:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子好饿
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.90,0:18:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我的馒头啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.15,0:18:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个味道不怎么样哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.94,0:18:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个人类在干啥 真不要脸
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.62,0:18:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是想吃美味馒头的话 我推荐七辻屋的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.09,0:18:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七辻?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.14,0:18:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 和我比赛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.61,0:18:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你赢了 就请你吃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.66,0:18:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...能看见我?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.84,0:18:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 能看见
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.71,0:19:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怕我吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.38,0:19:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不怕
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.44,0:19:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我非常强
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.55,0:19:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.54,0:19:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那要开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.32,0:19:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.97,0:19:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.31,0:19:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我赢咯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.61,0:19:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是偷袭么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.82,0:19:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了就是赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.89,0:19:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 这么一来你就是我的手下啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.98,0:19:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手下?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.54,0:19:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.54,0:19:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脸颊上的伤痕是怎么回事?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.06,0:19:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 被人用石头砸了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.57,0:19:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我让人不舒服什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.23,0:19:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 你名字很漂亮呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.01,0:19:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然当了我的手下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.50,0:19:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫了你名字就要飞过来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.95,0:19:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.69,0:19:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子哟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.59,0:19:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.21,0:19:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再见咯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.13,0:19:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.17,0:20:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.83,0:20:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.27,0:20:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.64,0:20:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也不叫我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.23,0:20:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.44,0:20:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比以前更加...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.25,0:20:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给我 把名字还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.96,0:20:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然不管怎么等待 也不召唤我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.60,0:20:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「菱垣」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.62,0:20:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子 已经没关系了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.10,0:20:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经 一个人也没关系了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.42,0:20:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外婆她肯定不是孤独一人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.04,0:20:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 菱垣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.16,0:21:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心地善良的...外婆的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.94,0:21:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到铃子了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.93,0:21:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很过分吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.25,0:21:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能坚持下去吗 夏目?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.08,0:21:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 想做下去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.69,0:21:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.97,0:21:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我依然还是不怎么喜欢妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.22,0:21:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.11,0:21:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 先生 听说那边的馒头很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.10,0:21:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 去吃去吃
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.85,0:21:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不要乱动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.83,0:21:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是好是坏 这也是一次邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.86,0:21:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 但是 给猫吃甜的东西行吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.16,0:22:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了我不是猫!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.94,0:22:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我馒头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:36.07,0:23:41.90,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,540)}露神之祠
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.50,0:23:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字是?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.03,0:23:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫「露神」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.93,0:23:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆婆在拜你的祠堂哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.79,0:23:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直以来都看着她 听着她的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.36,0:23:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 如果她也能听到我的声音的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.02,0:22:12.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.02,0:22:12.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.96,0:22:19.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.96,0:22:19.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.92,0:22:26.39,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.92,0:22:26.39,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.39,0:22:33.32,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.39,0:22:33.32,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.08,0:22:44.37,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.08,0:22:44.37,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.37,0:22:48.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.37,0:22:48.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.76,0:22:58.22,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.76,0:22:58.22,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.22,0:23:05.86,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.22,0:23:05.86,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.86,0:23:12.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.86,0:23:12.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.92,0:23:20.28,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.92,0:23:20.28,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.28,0:23:28.00,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.28,0:23:28.00,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
