[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.11,0:02:55.08,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}人与妖的临界
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.97,0:24:15.98,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\pos(208,296)}困惑之时
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.77,0:01:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看见…妖怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.90,0:01:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.18,0:01:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.72,0:01:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀哦呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.19,0:01:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然会迷失到妖怪世界中来  真是不寻常的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.48,0:01:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪世界？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.04,0:01:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才能看得见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.92,0:02:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  就放你条小命  赶紧回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.25,0:02:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被抓到的话可就成了酒宴的下酒菜咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.45,0:02:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是刚刚我朋友被…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.96,0:02:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.47,0:02:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他的话会很麻烦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.50,0:02:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之避免进入这交界之地
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.29,0:02:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  有了有了…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.81,0:02:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.23,0:02:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有善良的妖怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.87,0:02:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢  那可说不准
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.59,0:02:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚说到了酒宴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.79,0:02:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被带去那的可能性比较大
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.55,0:02:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得想点办法混进去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.03,0:02:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能给我安静点吗  蠢货
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.05,0:02:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎欢迎…欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.43,0:03:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待主人驾到之前  贡奉之物暂陈列于这祭坛之上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.42,0:03:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此乃可喜可贺之庆典
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.42,0:03:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诸位敬请畅饮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.62,0:03:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贡奉之物…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.96,0:03:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放置于这的东西都是贡奉给御柱怪的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.97,0:03:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来这妖怪的数量太惊人了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.51,0:03:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要帮忙也是我自己的选择啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.84,0:03:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼他一定正在找我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.07,0:03:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他找上这里引起骚乱之前
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.58,0:03:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得想办法从这里挣脱出去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.55,0:03:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  这就是叫做夏目的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.03,0:03:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太小了  都看不太清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.32,0:03:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说只是个人类却拥有强大的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.76,0:03:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的身份暴露了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.68,0:03:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西很了不起吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.32,0:03:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御柱大人肯定会很高兴的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.25,0:03:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想尝尝鲜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.36,0:03:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是夏目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.25,0:03:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾在远处见着过
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.16,0:03:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  让我瞧瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.83,0:03:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙装睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.19,0:03:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.00,0:04:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  大家可别被骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.74,0:04:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个瓶子里的是假的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.03,0:04:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.66,0:04:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.91,0:04:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装在这个瓶里的才是真人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.22,0:04:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是有计划就交给他试试看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.90,0:04:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这田沼到底有多大本事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.67,0:04:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你怎么了  外袍去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.72,0:04:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是被谁抢走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.20,0:04:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.10,0:04:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果现在闹起来的话就不太妙了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.02,0:04:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  好好干
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.21,0:04:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易让我给逮到了传说中的夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.38,0:04:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来到这之后就听说已有人捷足先登了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.63,0:04:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这就是在指责我在说谎吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.83,0:04:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  虽说是为了出出风头
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.16,0:04:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然毫不羞耻地说谎话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.43,0:04:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是在说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.22,0:04:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就比比看到底谁的是真货
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.73,0:04:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.83,0:04:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小子  给我露露脸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.37,0:04:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.86,0:05:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小子  我说给我露露脸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.97,0:05:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.36,0:05:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要开罐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.02,0:05:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从他身上能闻到人类的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.57,0:05:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.13,0:05:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.34,0:05:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.29,0:05:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是爱添麻烦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.23,0:05:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.38,0:05:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我跑…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.49,0:05:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什  什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.60,0:05:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃走了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.32,0:05:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到会有人类混进来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.55,0:05:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.82,0:05:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是无法逃离出这座宅子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.80,0:05:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这里的话就该没问题了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.19,0:06:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过这般宽敞比在外目测得更为宽广
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.16,0:06:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许会变成麻烦事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.12,0:06:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.23,0:06:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  据说还在这宅子里面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.01,0:06:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说有个彩色又圆又胖的怪物跟在他身边
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.61,0:06:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干架不方便
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.18,0:06:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的话暂时应该能撑上一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.30,0:06:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.20,0:06:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  都说过不要接近这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.45,0:06:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.83,0:06:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个妖怪在我想接近这妖宅的时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.97,0:06:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.65,0:06:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶来这里是想要做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.55,0:06:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很想坦白呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.86,0:06:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然又要吵架了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.08,0:06:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且那才是我想要问的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.71,0:06:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.66,0:06:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是普通的孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.21,0:07:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他带到这里来可真不乖呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.93,0:07:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.99,0:07:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.23,0:07:07.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并非是夏目带我来的  是我擅自…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.94,0:07:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.10,0:07:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.27,0:07:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.70,0:07:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怨我不小心被困在瓶中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.08,0:07:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼你…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.48,0:07:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你多少领悟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.07,0:07:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过于接近妖怪而遗忘自己的名字是何等危险的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.67,0:07:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.20,0:07:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是何来历？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.22,0:07:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是名取周一
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.39,0:07:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二职业是驱妖师
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.74,0:07:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱妖师？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.99,0:07:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是总觉得在哪见到过  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.61,0:07:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公众的职业是演员
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.51,0:07:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  这次就要出演电影了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.36,0:07:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送你免费试映券好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.88,0:07:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.70,0:07:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是做这些事的时候吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.27,0:07:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得想办法先逃出去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.48,0:07:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是柊和瓜姫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.34,0:08:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来得正是时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.86,0:08:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩刚好需要面具和外套
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.78,0:08:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.99,0:08:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.95,0:08:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.36,0:08:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸色真不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.07,0:08:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识她们的吗  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.20,0:08:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.19,0:08:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.90,0:08:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来还没有请教姓名的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.64,0:08:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.72,0:08:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.07,0:08:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是感觉比较投缘不会拉他下水的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.20,0:08:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.57,0:08:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.04,0:08:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼君嘛  多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.54,0:08:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼他正不断接近这边的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.80,0:08:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.28,0:08:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿有很浓烈的人类的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.83,0:08:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这附近了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.65,0:08:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.48,0:08:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.48,0:08:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里啊  小屁孩们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.83,0:08:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.24,0:09:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你挣脱出来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.56,0:09:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼那小子果然有两下子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.43,0:09:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.39,0:09:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.45,0:09:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  太容易露馅了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.25,0:09:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那英俊的身姿很难行动下去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.96,0:09:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么呀  你变化成人形了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.84,0:09:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.20,0:09:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本变身是那些怪物和低等妖怪的伎俩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.22,0:09:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是这般高贵的我所做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.10,0:09:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但为啥是这般样貌
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.74,0:09:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比较熟悉的人类只有夏目和玲子而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.26,0:09:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以无论怎么变都会有些相似
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.01,0:09:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那叫做玲子的是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.10,0:09:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.21,0:09:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也打不破
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.73,0:09:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,设有结界吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.57,0:09:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有返回入口处了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.71,0:09:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  那看起来也不见得容易
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.14,0:09:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此话怎讲
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.62,0:09:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这里看看就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.40,0:09:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.37,0:10:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明没有楼梯没有高低差
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.12,0:10:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的窗户是一楼的风景
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.54,0:10:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边是二楼的风景
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.61,0:10:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是煞费苦心的布局啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.55,0:10:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是为了不让我们逃跑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.65,0:10:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽有这可能  但也过于兴师动众的了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.94,0:10:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说过什么贡奉之物的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.11,0:10:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不清楚最关键的御柱怪的去处
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.30,0:10:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么想都很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.78,0:10:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.12,0:10:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪恶的气息正不断地聚集起来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.68,0:10:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.35,0:10:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.11,0:10:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我就去那边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.81,0:10:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.59,0:10:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.64,0:10:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼你就留在这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.70,0:10:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你若是有个万一的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.43,0:10:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我不也说过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.92,0:10:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是我擅自闯进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.35,0:10:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然老师说这是因为混进了妖怪世界
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.16,0:10:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我同夏目一样能够看得清清楚楚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.23,0:10:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以想要出分力…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.30,0:10:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.73,0:10:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚有没有看到我的同伴经过这里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.59,0:11:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  没有任何东西经过这
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.04,0:11:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道先回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.85,0:11:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你在发抖…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.55,0:11:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  你的想法很让我高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.76,0:11:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是若因此让田沼你受伤的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.38,0:11:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那正说明妖怪的世界是如此危险
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.16,0:11:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生  这是…血迹…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.87,0:11:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计是被吃掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.75,0:11:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被吃掉了？ 什么？ 被谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.69,0:11:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御柱大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.46,0:11:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来是想趁它力量尚未复原前将它封印掉会比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.62,0:11:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是行不通了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.82,0:11:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  是这么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.38,0:11:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.97,0:11:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼猿它们派发传单并非是为了召集贡品
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.32,0:11:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是为了召集低级妖怪们聚集于此宅中
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.21,0:11:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是为了让御柱大人享用
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.78,0:12:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在无法离开而迷失于其中的低级妖怪们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.44,0:12:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个接着一个的被吃掉  它的力量也正逐渐恢复
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.40,0:12:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是棘手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.88,0:12:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麽会…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.11,0:12:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么想要离开这里的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.66,0:12:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么找到出口
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.50,0:12:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么在御柱怪完全恢复力量之前将它封印起来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.16,0:12:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这两条路可选
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.43,0:12:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.58,0:12:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.76,0:12:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.75,0:12:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定…一定会将田沼从这里带回去的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.04,0:12:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论发生什么事情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.76,0:12:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分成两组吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.27,0:12:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和夏目去找御柱怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.63,0:12:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪和田沼去找出口
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.48,0:13:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论找到与否  一小时后在这里集合  可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.75,0:13:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.03,0:13:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师  田沼就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.26,0:13:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要不做多余的事紧紧跟着我就不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.37,0:13:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个给你  是守护石
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.40,0:13:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！ 名取  你是觉得我无法信赖吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.96,0:13:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不给女性添麻烦是我处世原则
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.70,0:13:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真恶心！ 这只是暂时的姿态
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.65,0:13:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一小时后见
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.88,0:13:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是乱来的孩子也能交到些同样胡来的朋友呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.45,0:13:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是好笑的事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.45,0:13:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但刚才真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.75,0:13:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明被你救了还对你乱发火
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.38,0:13:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我说的话也不顺耳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.68,0:13:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有对他说过吧  和驱妖人认识的事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.09,0:13:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.64,0:13:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是你的朋友？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.70,0:13:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  正因为是朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.99,0:13:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.39,0:14:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个叫名取的驱妖人  也许是个好人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.83,0:14:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有些盛气凌人  稍微有些讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.71,0:14:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就是骨髓里都渗透那习性的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.02,0:14:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌人多的家伙就是那样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.16,0:14:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌人？ 是指的妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.39,0:14:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧  但只要是从事那种职业的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.92,0:14:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌人也不会只是妖怪而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.28,0:14:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  这边的世界也不容易呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.86,0:14:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  不要过分追究了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.47,0:14:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这种程度的家伙  一下子就会被吃掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.98,0:14:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然吃了那么多…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.99,0:14:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御柱怪那家伙应该已恢复不少力量了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.36,0:14:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种…  绝对无法跟塔子阿姨他们说的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.06,0:14:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以夏目才会…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.68,0:14:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定…一定会把田沼从这里带回去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.59,0:14:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.55,0:14:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.80,0:14:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  是怎样的表情？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.15,0:14:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说要帮忙  要借给他力量的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.81,0:14:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓶子里的夏目是什么样的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.41,0:15:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想着夏目是不是会因此而高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.95,0:15:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会稍微轻松一些
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.35,0:15:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.61,0:15:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己去问夏目  那种事我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.41,0:15:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.45,0:15:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.62,0:15:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是御柱怪那家伙的脚印
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.89,0:15:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个感觉是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.20,0:15:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那是田沼的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.47,0:15:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼…田沼！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.91,0:15:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是被袭击过了  但因这守护石的力量得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.12,0:15:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来吸入了太多妖怪的毒气快到极限了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.13,0:15:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.16,0:15:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  怎么谁都喜欢到处乱晃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.48,0:15:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.54,0:16:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.02,0:16:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么御柱怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.05,0:16:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该还在附近
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.16,0:16:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事到如此  就算找到出口也不能就这么回去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.91,0:16:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能去封印住它了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.87,0:16:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼！ 明明最初就是这么打算的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.54,0:16:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.05,0:16:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  准备封印…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.99,0:16:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…一直都在害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.96,0:16:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕哪天会发生这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.94,0:16:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.23,0:16:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼本是不会胡乱闯入这里来的那种人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.68,0:16:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我不同  一直慎重又深思熟虑
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.42,0:16:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为和父亲两个人生活  所以从不让人多操心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.28,0:16:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我在一起的时候也是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.71,0:16:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想说的话  也忍着咽到肚子里去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.00,0:16:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而我却把他带到这种地方来  不断地让他乱来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.61,0:16:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么做…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.95,0:16:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说  我已经不能再在这里…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.79,0:16:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.91,0:17:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目你很强大
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.88,0:17:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得同人交往既讨厌又麻烦  早就不顾及了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.32,0:17:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许不会进展顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.99,0:17:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是夏目你不能放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.46,0:17:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许会很艰难
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.30,0:17:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这是你所需要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.11,0:17:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要这些
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.96,0:17:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人  在楼上通路处发现御柱怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.70,0:17:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  柊你守在田沼身边
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.09,0:17:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  我去做封印它的准备
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.42,0:17:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会帮我的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.08,0:17:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  不行的话就由我去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.79,0:17:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我去  请让我去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.27,0:17:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窗户…这里的窗户打不开！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.95,0:18:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御柱大人  您肚子饿了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.88,0:18:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这边来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.60,0:18:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休想逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.18,0:18:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏于临界处的死灵幻影
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.37,0:18:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擒拿而后沉睡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.48,0:18:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,响应我的召唤！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.65,0:18:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切  就差一点主人就能完全恢复力量了  居然…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.28,0:18:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会就这么放过你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.68,0:18:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有人类  更不好的是驱妖人也在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.64,0:19:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.65,0:19:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是有人类？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.84,0:19:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶呀诶呀  所以说妖怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.68,0:19:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了！ 低级的家伙们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.26,0:19:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们只是被这些鬼猿骗到这里当御柱怪饵食的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.24,0:19:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.17,0:19:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那个就是御柱怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.17,0:19:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的结界已经失效了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.18,0:19:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该散会了  宴会结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.26,0:19:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在跑的话  我就放过你们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.36,0:19:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢吞吞的话就看我把你们吃个精光
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.74,0:19:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从宅邸出来的缘故  毒气也基本消散了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.03,0:19:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  因为要收拾残局  名取先生让你过去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.41,0:19:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.26,0:20:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.55,0:20:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.33,0:20:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.81,0:20:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.04,0:20:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有田沼我才能从瓶子里出来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.03,0:20:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能将御柱怪给封印起来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.73,0:20:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都多亏了田沼的帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.48,0:20:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的…请告诉我你真心的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.86,0:20:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.56,0:20:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的介入  是不是成为夏目你的负担了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.38,0:20:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是因为我而让你痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.99,0:20:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不是很擅长与人交往
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.45,0:20:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算有想问的事  也不知哪些是该问或不该问的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.68,0:20:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想帮助你却又不知道该怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.00,0:20:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.05,0:20:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果让你讨厌的话就告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.70,0:20:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想回答的问题不回答也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.53,0:20:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明把能看见妖怪的事告诉了我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.69,0:21:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你若后悔这么做了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.43,0:21:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我亦不想因此让我们之间产生隔阂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.03,0:21:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易你愿意对我敞开心扉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.06,0:21:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却感到难受
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.78,0:21:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.09,0:21:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么做才好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.64,0:21:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  田沼  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.40,0:21:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该做些什么才好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.17,0:21:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那大概是…名取先生放弃了的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.06,0:21:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子祖母想要走却无法走的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.68,0:21:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那条路我能走下去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.56,0:21:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.60,0:21:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.41,0:21:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天会来学校的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.11,0:21:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  得向你抱怨一下呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.74,0:21:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「想要抱怨的话就先平安地从瓶里出来再说」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.21,0:21:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么说过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.78,0:21:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.20,0:22:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  塔子阿姨他们说会晚点回来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.72,0:22:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿了  吃饭吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.62,0:22:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.90,0:22:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好累…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.29,0:22:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.60,0:22:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快起来  我会把奶汁烤菜吃掉咯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.35,0:22:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目你不可以放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.92,0:22:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许会很艰难
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.40,0:22:25.54,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.98,0:22:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这肯定是夏目你所需要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.46,0:24:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胆敢反抗的话  就算是猫我也会除掉
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.82,0:24:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是毫不留情
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.78,0:24:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一开始就毫无踌躇的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.66,0:24:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人也好妖怪也好  出生各自有命
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.33,0:24:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想变得想您一样强大
