[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.39,0:01:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.37,0:01:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的帽子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.94,0:01:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白白的好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.09,0:01:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像雪一样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.77,0:01:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人带你走吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.31,0:01:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 要来我家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.37,0:01:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.25,0:01:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给妈妈看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.32,0:01:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.69,0:02:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎哎 男孩子不可以动不动就哭!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.26,0:02:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在开始得一个人生活下去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.03,0:02:12.95,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狐狸的帽子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.06,0:02:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了 塔子婶婶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.44,0:02:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路小心 开心点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.27,0:02:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.06,0:02:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.14,0:02:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊? 是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.97,0:02:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学习合宿好像是去雁羽温泉的吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.62,0:02:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.14,0:02:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.51,0:02:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你们出合宿的费用
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.68,0:02:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事情就别在意了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.42,0:02:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是有点事想拜托你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.14,0:02:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在温泉附近山里的窑户那 帮我取下茶碗可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.14,0:02:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,45)}{\fs23}译注:茶碗 陶制用喝茶的碗 为茶道具中价值最高亦最为考究的一种
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.41,0:02:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们联络我说就快做好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.14,0:02:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能拜托你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.15,0:03:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以 滋叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.54,0:03:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是令人毛骨悚然的笑啊 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.43,0:03:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.01,0:03:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.30,0:03:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保镖跟着是理所当然的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.74,0:03:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这倒是啦...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.10,0:03:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 什么事这么开心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.71,0:03:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开心的事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.24,0:03:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是被人拜托事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.82,0:03:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「猛者遂灭 恰似风前之尘」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.82,0:03:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,45)}{\fs23}译注:出自「平家物语」 日本中世纪长篇历史战争小说 作者不详 \N主要叙述以平清盛为首的平氏家族的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.42,0:03:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 上午就学到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.66,0:03:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午饭之前都是自由时间
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.73,0:04:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好咯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.02,0:04:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么接下来要干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.63,0:04:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定先是温泉吧 温泉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.02,0:04:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.33,0:04:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.38,0:04:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点事情...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.30,0:04:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？ 是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.29,0:04:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...应该就是这一带吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.54,0:04:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.47,0:04:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胆小鬼小狐狸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.71,0:04:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在森林里晃荡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.49,0:04:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这没用的家伙 很碍眼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.53,0:04:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙...你这...你这...你这...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.19,0:04:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这森林滚出去 没用的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.52,0:04:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没用的家伙?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.61,0:04:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说了让你滚出去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.06,0:05:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.55,0:05:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁...是谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.40,0:05:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.85,0:05:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然欺负这样的小孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.75,0:05:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙是人类?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.71,0:05:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区人类竟敢藐视我们
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.05,0:05:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少嚣张!看我吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.99,0:05:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.39,0:05:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 没事就好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.62,0:06:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是那么爱管闲事啊 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.06,0:06:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个没办法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.05,0:06:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 还真是白走一趟了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.18,0:06:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然还要来一次
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.95,0:06:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.60,0:06:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说茶碗要到明天才能烧制好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.76,0:06:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类真是麻烦的生物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.12,0:06:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是个盛饭茶的器皿么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.78,0:06:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到家附近的超市买就好了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.03,0:06:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 就太直接了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.63,0:06:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体又不是器皿
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.63,0:06:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,45)}{\fs23}注意:夏目说的「直接」为惯用语「身も蓋もない」 含有「身体」一词 \N猫先生冷笑话发作 给分开解释了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.41,0:06:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.62,0:06:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道身体是器皿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.15,0:06:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然讨厌人类...但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.51,0:06:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 球过去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.26,0:06:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解了解
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.42,0:06:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NICE!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.67,0:06:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 别睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.49,0:06:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 痛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.15,0:06:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.53,0:07:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那粉笔是因为夏目你才被弹到的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.13,0:07:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.08,0:07:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚饭会是什么呐 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.92,0:07:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真期待呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.31,0:07:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目经常笑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.13,0:07:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是总觉得有点假
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.21,0:07:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说话...举止...气息...都是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.43,0:07:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得那是装出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.95,0:07:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.67,0:07:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是前段时间 前段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.65,0:07:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能他根本就不是人类吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.39,0:07:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实跟我一样只是幻化成人形
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.61,0:07:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一样孤单一人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.27,0:07:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.17,0:07:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一起住在这森林就好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.27,0:08:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.76,0:08:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真伤脑筋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.73,0:08:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天就要回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.93,0:08:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果无缘故地亲近了也很可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.58,0:08:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经迟咯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.54,0:08:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很吵哦 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.09,0:09:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超倒霉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.61,0:09:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子已经不用说去取茶碗了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.40,0:09:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连能不能回去上课都成问题啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.33,0:09:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.77,0:09:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.58,0:09:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.21,0:10:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.53,0:10:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有派上用场哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.94,0:10:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说「谢谢你」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.20,0:10:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不是没用的家伙了对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.80,0:10:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天去采蘑菇吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.83,0:10:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,采许多许多分给夏目吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.27,0:10:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.07,0:10:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小不点狐狸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.54,0:10:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.10,0:10:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不长教训的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.45,0:10:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了让你滚的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.27,0:10:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这...你这...你这...你这...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.65,0:10:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这森林里不需要没用的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.31,0:10:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.96,0:10:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 我已经不是没用的家伙了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.28,0:10:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 痛痛痛痛 这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.62,0:10:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小鬼 竟敢...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.29,0:10:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说过让你们住手了的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.88,0:11:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.03,0:11:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是昨天的?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.52,0:11:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是拳头不够吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.78,0:11:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.51,0:11:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.01,0:11:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您忘了吗 夏目铃子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.48,0:11:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您不是说到了春天就会归还我的名字吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.26,0:11:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.42,0:11:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老是做这种罪过的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.33,0:11:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,春天?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.40,0:11:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经是第几年的春天了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.15,0:11:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你吗 呼唤我的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.51,0:11:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 茶碗拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.62,0:11:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「收下吧 早蕨 此乃汝名」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.45,0:11:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  说夏目...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.44,0:12:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个持有友人帐的夏目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.76,0:12:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确实收到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.05,0:12:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐  我听说过
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.26,0:12:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写上名字的人会缔结主从的契约
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.29,0:12:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊  会被夺走名字的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.93,0:12:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊  快逃～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.24,0:12:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么啊  那些家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.21,0:12:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚归还名字的人怎么会再去夺走啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.00,0:12:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这上面写着我的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.51,0:12:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请收我当你的手下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.29,0:12:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会派上用场的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.68,0:12:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.12,0:12:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我弱小吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.52,0:12:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我没用?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.18,0:12:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想用这种东西来束缚你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.78,0:12:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是老大与手下的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.63,0:12:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.68,0:13:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得应该是别的不一样的羁绊哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.25,0:13:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个 真是漂亮的颜色啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.55,0:13:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去换衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.70,0:13:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熟人给介绍的好窑户
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.30,0:13:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为家人增加了所以想趁这个机会
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.69,0:13:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个 是你的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.21,0:13:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.71,0:13:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.01,0:13:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那小狐狸说的一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.12,0:13:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你指什么 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.46,0:13:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是能不能派上用场的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.00,0:13:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 完全搞不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.20,0:13:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 果然还是漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.14,0:14:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也想给夏目看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.21,0:14:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.90,0:14:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想见夏目...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.41,0:14:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩子不可以动不动就哭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.81,0:14:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经决定了要变强
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.71,0:14:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天我能帮到夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.10,0:14:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么想要见夏目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.84,0:14:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.34,0:14:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你似乎认识那个持有友人帐的夏目吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.28,0:14:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不能完全化为人形吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.71,0:14:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能给我足够吃到饱的鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.57,0:14:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你见到夏目的方法也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.63,0:15:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样 就会告诉我见到夏目的方法了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.80,0:15:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋小狐狸 你被骗了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.49,0:15:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为你这么笨所以才总是一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.39,0:15:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目早就把你给忘了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.39,0:15:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收下吧 小狐狸
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.60,0:15:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是只能维持一天人形的药
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.89,0:15:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能变成人的药?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.23,0:15:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想见的话 自己去见他就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.77,0:15:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么简单的问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.27,0:16:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 去见他就可以了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.58,0:16:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 好歹我也是狐狸呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.39,0:16:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去到人类的世界一定能找到夏目的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.79,0:16:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去了 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.22,0:16:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目一个人会不会寂寞呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.93,0:17:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.92,0:17:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.94,0:17:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 夏目的味道...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.85,0:17:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边这边 等下等下等下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.84,0:17:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想见你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.40,0:17:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 看着哪里走路啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.30,0:17:51.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 你在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.23,0:17:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.20,0:17:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 没事吧 你一个人吗 你妈妈呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.64,0:18:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一个人也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.47,0:18:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想见你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.38,0:18:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想见你 在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.93,0:18:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.11,0:18:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.71,0:18:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了来了 拉啊 快拉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.84,0:18:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大一条啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.34,0:18:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么又是夏目 钓了很多嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.35,0:18:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.03,0:18:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干吗吃起来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.79,0:18:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.30,0:18:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有 就在这附近
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.07,0:18:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能见到啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.78,0:19:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烤好了哦 贵志的马苏大麻哈鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.37,0:19:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 这真是好大条马苏大麻哈鱼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.41,0:19:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.63,0:19:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.76,0:19:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志吃河鱼的对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.19,0:19:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我什么都吃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.34,0:19:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不喜欢吃的就要说出来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.74,0:19:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滋叔叔他啊 不吃青椒的 像小孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.65,0:19:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上我小时候也不爱吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.43,0:19:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 看来有同伴了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.37,0:19:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.72,0:19:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我尝尝看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.16,0:19:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀～塔子 这马苏大麻哈鱼味道非常不错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.15,0:19:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯～那我也开动咯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.60,0:19:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃吧吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.48,0:19:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 怎么样?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.93,0:19:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃 真开心 吃到这么好吃的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.15,0:20:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 夏目很开心的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.26,0:20:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.23,0:20:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寂寞的...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.55,0:20:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寂寞的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.98,0:20:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.77,0:20:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.01,0:20:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那时候的小狐狸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.60,0:20:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.87,0:20:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是特地来见我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.96,0:21:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可爱的帽子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.10,0:21:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃完饭后一起回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.46,0:21:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得记下路呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.45,0:21:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次就由我去见你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.79,0:21:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是了不起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.90,0:21:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我即使寂寞也不敢走出那一步
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.13,0:21:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都没想过要做些什么去改变
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.10,0:21:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以错过了许多事物也不一定啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.88,0:23:51.00,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,540)}虚幻的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.82,0:23:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人曾经能看到妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.68,0:23:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心灵交融 最终变成了重要的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.76,0:23:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 有一天
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.51,0:23:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得看不到妖怪了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.78,0:23:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要那个人能幸福 我怎样都无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.24,0:23:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗 纪遥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.20,0:22:12.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.20,0:22:12.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.14,0:22:20.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.14,0:22:20.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:26.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:26.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.57,0:22:33.50,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.57,0:22:33.50,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:44.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:44.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.55,0:22:48.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.55,0:22:48.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:58.40,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:58.40,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:06.04,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:06.04,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:13.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:13.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.10,0:23:20.46,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.10,0:23:20.46,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.46,0:23:27.18,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.46,0:23:27.18,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
