[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.85,0:01:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.68,0:01:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你是来看萤火虫的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.71,0:02:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.07,0:02:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为听说快到萤火虫的季节了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.33,0:02:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.86,0:02:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 就时期和时间来讲似乎都早了点
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.54,0:02:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且最近数量似乎也在减少
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.73,0:02:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.05,0:02:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.68,0:02:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.74,0:02:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是附在那个人身上吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.43,0:02:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.60,0:02:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.02,0:02:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是人类却能看到我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.98,0:02:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.91,0:02:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个莽撞的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.33,0:03:05.26,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虚幻的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.13,0:03:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.79,0:03:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还跑来我这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.32,0:03:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是附身在刚才那人身上吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.73,0:03:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,附身?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.05,0:03:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是失礼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.58,0:03:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.77,0:03:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.68,0:03:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说那个人看得见妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.25,0:03:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经是过去的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.04,0:03:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他年轻时经常和我聊天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.30,0:03:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在一起很长一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.13,0:03:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.27,0:03:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他突然就看不到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.36,0:03:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后就没再交谈过
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.31,0:03:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「变得看不见」?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.35,0:03:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的事也会发生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.46,0:03:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些人的这种能力在成年后是会逐渐衰退的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.40,0:03:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.17,0:03:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这种事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.87,0:03:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我因为听说他最近就要结婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.61,0:04:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想着起码看下他盛装的样子 所以才过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.20,0:04:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我们的关系就好似你们一样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.04,0:04:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 我们可不是朋友关系
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.07,0:04:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是饲主和宠物的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.13,0:04:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.56,0:04:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么名字
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.41,0:04:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.01,0:04:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假面
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.96,0:04:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长发
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.31,0:04:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.28,0:04:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是沼女
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.25,0:04:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是下等妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.58,0:04:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本就没名字
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.97,0:04:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别戏弄我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.76,0:04:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就让我来给你取个名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.09,0:04:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就叫「卷卷面」怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.40,0:04:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得怎样  觉得怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.26,0:04:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然能再次和人类说话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.34,0:04:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 卷卷面
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.97,0:04:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是某种缘分吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.73,0:04:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卷卷面  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.90,0:04:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到婚礼那天为止就承蒙你照顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.47,0:04:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在问你觉得怎么样啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.60,0:04:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫「卷卷面」怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.78,0:04:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很吵啊 猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.11,0:05:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜...卷卷
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.83,0:05:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朴实却耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.17,0:05:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 已经睡着了吗 好无聊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.75,0:05:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你在听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.61,0:05:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 起来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.32,0:05:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.15,0:05:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.61,0:05:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦到有人在呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.28,0:05:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纪遥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.79,0:05:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纪遥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.17,0:05:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纪遥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.14,0:05:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.98,0:05:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要迟到了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.43,0:06:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.62,0:06:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.64,0:06:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「纪遥」怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.40,0:06:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.65,0:06:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.62,0:06:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要就叫「纪遥」?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.48,0:06:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随你的便吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.32,0:06:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得看不见妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.85,0:06:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的会有这样的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.29,0:06:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从前住在这森林里的某位山神
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.36,0:06:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一个人类女子相恋
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.26,0:06:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上总在这里幽会
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.37,0:06:39.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时 在黑暗中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.66,0:06:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这片沼泽的萤火虫们为他们照亮了夜路
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.40,0:06:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山神出于感激
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.45,0:06:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将这些生命短暂的萤火虫们变成了妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.20,0:06:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤火虫们很高兴 其中大多数都动身离开了沼泽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.55,0:07:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说这里的萤火虫就是当时留下来的那部分的子孙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.05,0:07:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 也就是传说而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.10,0:07:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.25,0:07:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂...喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.74,0:07:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.51,0:07:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好...好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.41,0:07:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是 昨天的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.65,0:07:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱...抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.16,0:07:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎被什么绊到了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.40,0:07:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵 真有精神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.15,0:07:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这沼泽里有什么东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.67,0:07:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问有什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.80,0:07:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.71,0:08:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不清楚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.33,0:08:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了萤火虫应该就是鲫鱼了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.64,0:08:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只妖怪是不会袭击人的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.83,0:08:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.72,0:08:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问不出来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.39,0:08:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「曾经你也看得见妖怪吗」这种问题
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.65,0:08:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在看得见妖怪的人去和他重提旧事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.08,0:08:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也只会给人家添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.01,0:08:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纪遥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.14,0:08:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人叫章史
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.81,0:08:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为看得见妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.50,0:08:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直被家人和周围的人们另眼相待这令他很痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.00,0:08:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他独自来这里哭泣时
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.90,0:09:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总是在旁偷偷看着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.52,0:09:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有天当他晚上过来时
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.45,0:09:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽然匆忙躲了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.40,0:09:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体却不小心发了光
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.18,0:09:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.42,0:09:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.00,0:09:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.36,0:09:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.50,0:09:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.75,0:09:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能稍微和我说说话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.59,0:09:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.24,0:09:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对人类...有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.41,0:09:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对妖怪没兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.27,0:09:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.67,0:09:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二天他也还是来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.02,0:09:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们聊了很多
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.14,0:09:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了好多好多的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.02,0:09:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时还一起去玩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.69,0:09:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的手感呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.74,0:10:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵 很舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.45,0:10:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.19,0:10:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.84,0:10:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有天
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.64,0:10:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的眼中不再映出我的身影
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.60,0:10:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算去触碰他 也不再被察觉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.30,0:10:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他来到沼泽 呼唤过我好几次
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.44,0:10:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却没有发觉我就站在他眼前
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.59,0:10:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会不会某天也不再看得见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.25,0:10:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「你会不会某天也不再看得见呢」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.93,0:10:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.96,0:11:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.25,0:11:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不正是我长久以来的愿望吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.67,0:11:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是一直  一直
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.60,0:11:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都在期盼着解脱的那一刻么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.72,0:11:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.28,0:11:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明看不到散发着微弱光芒的纪遥了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.22,0:12:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么还要去那片沼泽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.61,0:12:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 你也能看见妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.52,0:12:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.88,0:12:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前几天遇到的妖怪告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.03,0:12:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从前你也看得见
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.71,0:12:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时至今日
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.53,0:12:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都恍如隔世
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.87,0:12:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难受吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.13,0:12:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很难受
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.22,0:12:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为一直都是孤身一人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.61,0:12:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我和一个妖怪走近过
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.67,0:12:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢上了她
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.70,0:12:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没能说出口
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.66,0:12:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱她
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.70,0:12:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 有天我突然完全看不见妖怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.18,0:12:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切就在那时结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.04,0:12:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然怎么都无法忘记她
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.59,0:12:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也一直都没结婚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.21,0:12:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但终于...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.54,0:12:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是遇到了发自内心喜欢的人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.87,0:13:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个心地非常善良的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.22,0:13:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天后我们就要举行婚礼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.82,0:13:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后我就不会再来这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.01,0:13:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,章史先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.60,0:13:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.64,0:13:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 再见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.11,0:13:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.37,0:13:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.16,0:13:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纪遥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.14,0:13:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到重要的人了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.49,0:13:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经不再是独自一人了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.70,0:13:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纪遥 这样就好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.81,0:13:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.56,0:13:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了个平静的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.20,0:14:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那大概是来自纪遥的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.84,0:14:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.14,0:14:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.77,0:14:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤 你在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.01,0:14:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤 我看不到 你出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.45,0:14:52.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤 留在我身边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.36,0:14:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.62,0:15:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.17,0:15:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.10,0:15:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你讨厌我了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.95,0:15:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢...喜欢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.81,0:15:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.51,0:16:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.18,0:16:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.43,0:16:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是章史先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.79,0:16:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤 他是这么叫你的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.30,0:16:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了 也听到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.74,0:16:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是萤火虫妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.81,0:16:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在没有实体
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.10,0:16:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一次能变回普通萤火虫形态的能力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.77,0:16:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说那样做的话就没法恢复现在的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.09,0:17:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能以虫子的形态结束短暂一生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.45,0:17:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使那样也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.13,0:17:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算没有我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.23,0:17:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.09,0:17:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人也已经能露出笑容了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.51,0:17:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 哪怕只一次
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.76,0:17:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以虫子的姿态
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.58,0:17:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是想见到他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.58,0:17:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤 等下 等...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.56,0:17:35.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙 不会是想去沼泽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.22,0:17:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只沼泽里的大嘴怪虽不会袭击人却会吃萤火虫
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.38,0:17:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为它在那里徘徊四处找食
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.78,0:17:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这一带的萤火虫才会藏起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.93,0:17:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤 你在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.43,0:17:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干吗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.84,0:17:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太黑了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.97,0:18:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呿 真急人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.90,0:18:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐上来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.65,0:18:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.61,0:18:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住～手！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.53,0:18:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.73,0:18:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.76,0:18:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁刚刚逃过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.14,0:18:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个味道 不是她
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.87,0:18:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.27,0:18:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候母亲吓了一跳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.99,0:18:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.13,0:19:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.70,0:19:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实 真漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.34,0:19:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好象...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.80,0:19:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.04,0:20:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 沼泽的萤火虫们守护着的山神和恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.82,0:20:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们后来怎么样了?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.51,0:20:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就不清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.97,0:20:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和妖怪相比 人类的一生实在太短暂了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.89,0:20:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.62,0:20:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也会有失去能力的那一天吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.62,0:20:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去那单方面的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.40,0:20:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那些纷纷扰扰的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.95,0:20:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那对我来说会是解脱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.45,0:20:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.37,0:20:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时 小小的萤火虫似乎在低声轻语着什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.16,0:20:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我却不懂得它们的语言
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.52,0:20:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再会了 萤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.76,0:20:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人听得懂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.98,0:20:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望只要那个人能...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.74,0:21:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜 祝你们幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.34,0:21:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长 恭喜你 恭喜 祝你们幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.54,0:21:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得到却无能为力 真难受啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.66,0:21:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是笨蛋吗 又没有一一帮忙的义务
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.39,0:21:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪和人类终究是不同的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.51,0:21:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.53,0:21:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先说好 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.78,0:21:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你变得看不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.10,0:21:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在没得到友人帐之前我还是不会放过你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.88,0:21:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕某天妖怪从眼前消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.10,0:21:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但曾相逢的记忆是绝对不会消失的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.08,0:21:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 你可要当好我的保镖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.71,0:21:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么说好了 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.87,0:22:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕相遇再短 也绝不会消逝...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.23,0:23:51.00,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,540)}驱妖
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.60,0:23:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.85,0:23:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫名取周一
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.16,0:23:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君 能协助我进行驱妖的工作吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.97,0:23:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱妖?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.92,0:23:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你倒是散发着新手的妖气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.69,0:23:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我太耀眼了 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.88,0:23:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妖气啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.20,0:22:12.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.20,0:22:12.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.14,0:22:20.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.14,0:22:20.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:26.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:26.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.57,0:22:33.50,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.57,0:22:33.50,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:44.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:44.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.55,0:22:48.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.55,0:22:48.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:58.40,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:58.40,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:06.04,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:06.04,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:13.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:13.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.10,0:23:20.46,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.10,0:23:20.46,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.46,0:23:27.18,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.46,0:23:27.18,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
