[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.74,0:03:37.74,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}遥遥家路
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.00,0:22:36.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだうしろ姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.59,0:22:43.07,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.79,0:22:49.20,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}やさしさで胸がいたくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.73,0:22:56.60,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々がいとおしくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.79,0:23:09.86,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音(ね)に　夕闇に　懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.57,0:23:22.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも一緒だよ、と　叶わぬことくり返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:27.93,0:23:33.53,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}ぬくもりはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.23,0:23:39.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}あざやかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.58,0:23:46.82,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.37,0:23:56.57,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来にかえながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.00,0:22:36.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだうしろ姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.59,0:22:43.07,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.79,0:22:49.20,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}やさしさで胸がいたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.73,0:22:56.60,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々がいとおしくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.79,0:23:09.86,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音(ね)に　夕闇に　懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.57,0:23:22.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも一緒だよ、と　叶わぬことくり返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.93,0:23:33.53,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}ぬくもりはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.23,0:23:39.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}あざやかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.58,0:23:46.82,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.37,0:23:56.57,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来にかえながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.00,0:22:36.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.59,0:22:43.07,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.79,0:22:49.20,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.73,0:22:56.60,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.79,0:23:09.86,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下  回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.57,0:23:22.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离  辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:27.93,0:23:33.53,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.23,0:23:39.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.58,0:23:46.82,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.37,0:23:56.57,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.00,0:22:36.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.59,0:22:43.07,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.79,0:22:49.20,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.73,0:22:56.60,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.79,0:23:09.86,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下  回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.57,0:23:22.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离  辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.93,0:23:33.53,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.23,0:23:39.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.58,0:23:46.82,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.37,0:23:56.57,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.11,0:01:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.95,0:01:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.81,0:01:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.01,0:01:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要…回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.20,0:01:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切  竟然让那种下等妖怪乘虚而入
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.52,0:01:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这若是稍有差池怕会危及到生命
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.57,0:01:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我振作些  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.30,0:01:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.20,0:01:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能听到老师的声音  得回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.07,0:02:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  是去哪个家？ 在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.27,0:02:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处晃悠着做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.02,0:02:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目该不会是迷路了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.08,0:02:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就是寄住在三世子家的那个孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.02,0:02:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会是还没能记住回家的路吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.24,0:02:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑子真不好使
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.18,0:02:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让这太恐怖了我不敢过去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.54,0:02:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是我想去哪都是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.96,0:02:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要住下去…我也想要住下去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.08,0:02:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往回走了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.72,0:02:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要再去学校一次吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.63,0:02:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家真的都看不到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.55,0:02:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明有这么多恐怖的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.52,0:03:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真的迷路了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.56,0:03:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神社？ 竟然会在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.01,0:03:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真安静
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.60,0:03:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好  如果被妖怪追赶的话就逃到这里来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.94,0:03:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  就把这里当作秘密基地好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.85,0:03:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有谁来打搅  安静的…只属于我的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.88,0:03:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吃饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.19,0:03:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.94,0:03:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还剩下这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.87,0:03:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃干净
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.81,0:03:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.08,0:03:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是不想吃嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.26,0:03:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要走了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.00,0:04:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.03,0:04:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  三世子  要和贵志君一起去学校哟
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.42,0:04:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经和菜緒酱约好了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.94,0:04:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.93,0:04:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君  别太在意了  要多吃些哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.41,0:04:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.01,0:04:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真香
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.47,0:04:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来好好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.49,0:04:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想什么时候能吃一次看看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.19,0:04:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个不是夏目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.67,0:04:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.34,0:04:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  是三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.17,0:04:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.21,0:04:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你和夏目同居呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.50,0:05:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真害臊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.77,0:05:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真害臊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.39,0:05:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  给我住嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.39,0:05:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真害臊  真害臊  真害臊  真害臊…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.25,0:05:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.26,0:05:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.93,0:05:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.94,0:05:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得去道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.40,0:05:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明不是她的错  都怪我…来到了这个家里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.75,0:05:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吃饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.14,0:05:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又留下这么多！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.31,0:05:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子  怎么了？ 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.23,0:05:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.66,0:05:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吃饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.62,0:05:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.61,0:05:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.01,0:06:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  为什么那个孩子会来我们家
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.49,0:06:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子  睡觉前爸爸给你讲好多好多的故事好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.67,0:06:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你呢  明天就要和贵志君一起去学校哟
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.11,0:06:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三世子她在撒娇
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.02,0:06:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚就睡在我的房间里了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.07,0:06:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君你一个人不怕吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.73,0:06:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怕
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.59,0:06:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就晚安了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.92,0:06:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就看一眼没关系吧？ 就只是今天
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.10,0:06:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.99,0:07:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不行  不能再翻看了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.04,0:07:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要开始疼痛了  不能再看
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.14,0:07:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  我不寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.46,0:07:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  虽然已不再身边  但一定为我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.65,0:07:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.29,0:07:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.33,0:07:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走得离我更远点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.42,0:07:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你的家在哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.27,0:07:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真正的家呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.59,0:07:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是真正的家？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.29,0:07:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就是你父母所住的家
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.06,0:07:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得吗？ 你的爸爸和妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.66,0:08:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不记得我妈妈了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.62,0:08:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么爸爸呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.48,0:08:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸也…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.41,0:08:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是非常地非常的温柔！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.19,0:08:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定曾是那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.28,0:08:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.45,0:08:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明说是不记得但怎么又说得出口
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.81,0:08:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且那种口气算什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.91,0:08:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的爸爸才是最温柔的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.85,0:08:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的家？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.13,0:08:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪  明明说是不记得…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.69,0:08:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果回到真正的家里…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.21,0:08:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会能想起更多爸爸的事情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.05,0:09:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.61,0:09:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果想起很多事情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.14,0:09:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而化为更多的伤痛的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.92,0:09:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.30,0:09:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的家？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.07,0:09:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  夏目夫妇的家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.72,0:09:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像从馆花先生那收到过家庭住址
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.29,0:09:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.58,0:09:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要这做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.59,0:09:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…想要作为护身符
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.88,0:09:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这个吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.73,0:09:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离这里不远呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.34,0:09:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说城町的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.72,0:09:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是沿着城川河径直向西走
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.13,0:09:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛  又有小妖怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.55,0:09:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.01,0:09:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我替你吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.73,0:09:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.53,0:10:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小姑娘又剩饭了  真不是个好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.47,0:10:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我替你吃掉好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.37,0:10:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢  绝对不行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.53,0:10:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去一边去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.92,0:10:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好凶  好凶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.20,0:10:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走远点  走更远点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.82,0:10:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以给别人添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.67,0:10:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.39,0:10:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城町  是沿着城川河向西直走
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.84,0:11:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  现在几点了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.42,0:11:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得赶紧回去了  不然又给别人添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.29,0:11:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  只是打雷而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.14,0:11:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得赶紧回去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.92,0:11:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快！ 赶快！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.36,0:11:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.26,0:12:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.69,0:12:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.11,0:12:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惊扰大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.81,0:12:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能找到真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.72,0:12:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可怜  看来是吓坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.11,0:12:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.89,0:12:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君  你先进去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.02,0:12:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要去向大家道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.45,0:12:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和三世子先吃饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.47,0:12:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.73,0:12:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.14,0:12:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起…对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.26,0:12:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我爸爸妈妈非得去道歉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.85,0:12:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我爸爸妈妈要被指责呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.08,0:12:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是你有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.66,0:12:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我离开这
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.88,0:12:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙给我远离这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.63,0:13:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我离开…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.65,0:13:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城町…沿着城川河…径直向西…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.81,0:13:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里有我的家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.97,0:13:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家吧  回家吧…我真正的家里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.95,0:13:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已成虚无的家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.46,0:13:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸…爸爸…爸爸…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.49,0:13:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实已是无数次…无数次地呼唤过了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.96,0:13:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而果然仍旧无人会应答
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.42,0:13:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是如何的呼唤  企盼…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.05,0:13:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也会有遥不可及的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.68,0:13:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果那以后还是未能够抵达
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.58,0:14:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷失方向  精疲力竭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.31,0:14:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是决意放弃无法给与答复的呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.42,0:14:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悲伤的想要忘却的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.23,0:14:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我替你吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.56,0:14:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我画张嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.29,0:14:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  即便如此  那也是拼凑出现在的我的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.89,0:14:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是何等的伤痛  那也是我最重要的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.50,0:14:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.70,0:14:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记忆也好  内心也罢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.67,0:14:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都让我吃掉好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.68,0:14:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.04,0:14:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有声音
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.94,0:14:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.28,0:14:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.02,0:14:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.42,0:14:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.09,0:15:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路小心  贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.62,0:15:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  我要…回去！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.44,0:15:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.53,0:15:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  把它妖力打散了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.83,0:15:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不过是区区虫子一般
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.98,0:15:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.66,0:15:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您在呼唤我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.94,0:15:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了我的记忆吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.49,0:15:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你的记忆没有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.60,0:16:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正不过是在得到友人帐之前的交往而已
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.25,0:16:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城町  沿着城川河径直向西走
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.80,0:17:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.75,0:17:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我画的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.53,0:17:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是个乱来的小孩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.34,0:17:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明画在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.66,0:17:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸还没擦掉反而替我留下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.13,0:18:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.32,0:18:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有稍微想起些在这里的生活呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.47,0:18:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然基本上都记不起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.69,0:18:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多…很多的重要的回忆…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.22,0:18:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都被我忘得一干二净了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.48,0:18:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  这个院子里的某处有妈妈种下的花
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.83,0:18:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会是哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.61,0:18:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经完全分辨不出了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.25,0:18:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.48,0:18:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志  今年要是也开花就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.23,0:18:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够一直地一直地开花就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.99,0:19:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.68,0:19:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了  爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.16,0:19:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了  我的家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.61,0:19:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.50,0:19:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后  身体相当地疲乏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.73,0:19:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一味的赶路回家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.84,0:19:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没能吃上那家的乌冬面
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.25,0:19:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得的是老师竟然没有发脾气
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.82,0:19:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.89,0:19:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.68,0:20:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来  贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.24,0:20:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.48,0:20:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.26,0:20:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了  这次又是哪边？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.26,0:20:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想应该就在附近了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.71,0:20:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这已经是第三次了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.77,0:20:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.77,0:20:21.52,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波子汽水  波子汽水…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.75,0:20:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  先告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.59,0:20:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先告辞  先告辞！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.34,0:20:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波子汽水  波子汽水…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.61,0:20:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说…第六感觉应该是这边吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.20,0:20:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.05,0:20:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.98,0:20:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很不错
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.66,0:20:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.36,0:20:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.89,0:20:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们终于来了  辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.48,0:20:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛  被你们捷足先登
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.42,0:20:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可是详细调查过的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.50,0:20:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听夏目说你们今天会来就在这等着了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.81,0:21:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说有波子汽水涌出来的…就是这里了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.74,0:21:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么呢  不是通红的么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.64,0:21:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然的咯  生锈了呗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.57,0:21:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  只要运气不太坏  不会弄坏肚子的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.25,0:21:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  西村  你就先喝喝看看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.08,0:21:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头剪刀布来决定！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.02,0:21:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有过悲伤  有过难过的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.28,0:21:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这今后的日子里…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.05,0:21:31.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许还会再有那样的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.29,0:21:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.67,0:21:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  准备好了  要照了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.25,0:21:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  贵志  再靠近点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.89,0:21:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  笑笑  贵志君
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.21,0:21:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看  有没有拍进去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.71,0:21:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真令人期待
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.84,0:22:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚是…炸牛肉饼的蓝调
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.60,0:22:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滋叔叔  塔子阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.05,0:22:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…能够再照一张吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.93,0:22:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫五郎  要老实待着哟
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.11,0:22:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法忘却的…宝贵的日子
