[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.71,0:01:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天气完全转凉了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.98,0:01:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 山上的红叶一定会很漂亮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.20,0:01:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这两天挑个日子一起去双叶坝玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.43,0:01:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好提议啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.91,0:01:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我负责带些色色的东西过去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.61,0:01:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.74,0:01:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别理他啦夏目 那我就负责带点心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.87,0:01:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就带些喝的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.12,0:01:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目你就负责三明治
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.09,0:01:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.75,0:02:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 休息日的便当的话有点...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.51,0:02:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.61,0:02:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去拜托下塔子阿姨好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.77,0:02:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定会很乐意帮忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.18,0:02:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然我也会开心 塔子阿姨的三明治
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.75,0:02:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.79,0:02:21.86,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五日印
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.56,0:02:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见咯 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.05,0:02:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.99,0:03:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪...在吃妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.26,0:03:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.68,0:03:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到我了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.83,0:03:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要吃了你 吃了你!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.94,0:03:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.82,0:03:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你逃也没用
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.99,0:03:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要吃掉你 小子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.27,0:03:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会去吃你的!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.83,0:03:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.80,0:03:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来啦 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.53,0:03:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊? 怎么啦 脸色不太好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.89,0:03:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 没什么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.24,0:03:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好 要焦掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.06,0:04:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 你回来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.80,0:04:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.36,0:04:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔 好香的味道 今晚是炸墨鱼圈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.92,0:04:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墨鱼新鲜吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.16,0:04:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫是不可以吃墨鱼的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.27,0:04:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了我不是猫的吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.44,0:04:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 怎么了夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.02,0:04:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你手上的印记是?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.70,0:04:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先...先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.07,0:04:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.16,0:04:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的胳膊被诅咒了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.29,0:04:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诅咒?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.43,0:04:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.26,0:04:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是笑的时候么 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.96,0:04:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.13,0:04:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵～ 喵～ 喵～ 喵～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.55,0:04:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 竟敢对我的东西下手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.57,0:04:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是胆大包天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.54,0:04:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还说要吃掉你?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.12,0:04:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平时的话我还可能会感激它
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.27,0:04:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在我这样 友人帐被抢走岂不便宜它了么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.36,0:04:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.27,0:05:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没办法 要叫一个出来替我作你的保镖吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.29,0:05:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫...出来?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.75,0:05:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是用友人帐啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.81,0:05:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.08,0:05:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事也可以么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.82,0:05:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子曾自满地在我面前炫耀过
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.18,0:05:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.60,0:05:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样吧 然后你披上白布站到阵中心来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.33,0:05:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用来代替白色法袍
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.16,0:05:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道名字和长相就无法召唤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.42,0:05:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就试试召唤前段时间的「三篠」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.16,0:05:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 在阵中放下镜子和友人帐 然后滴一滴血
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.18,0:05:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.18,0:05:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来还需要一片指甲的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.52,0:05:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别以为和妖怪做交易不需要任何代价
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.79,0:05:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要开始了 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.13,0:05:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「守护吾者 现身吾前」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.53,0:05:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「汝名即...」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.74,0:06:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「三篠」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.75,0:06:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人 久日未见了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.74,0:06:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次没来得及归还你名字 真是不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.99,0:06:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三篠 有事想借助你的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.09,0:06:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请帮我一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.31,0:06:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 可以
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.67,0:06:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.17,0:06:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 印记比之前扩大了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.52,0:06:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 这是诅咒的印记 这可不好办
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.97,0:06:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我对诅咒也不熟悉 给您介绍其他人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.08,0:06:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是太谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.03,0:06:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.02,0:06:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可让妖怪瞧见您内心的弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.37,0:06:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.19,0:06:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪会映照出人心的软弱和阴影
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.12,0:06:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您是在用妖怪排遣寂寞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.26,0:07:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三篠 你这是对主人的态度么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.06,0:07:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太猖狂了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.05,0:07:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏你还敢说啊 斑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.17,0:07:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他沾上了诅咒 你这保镖当得还真是称职啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.93,0:07:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.05,0:07:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人 您要是想和这不倒翁猫分道扬镳的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.64,0:07:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随时欢迎来找我 由我来守护您吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.15,0:07:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.06,0:07:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是不倒翁猫啊 你这死木马
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.06,0:07:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是不倒翁 我原本那优雅的姿态...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.11,0:07:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我去叫「丙」过来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.64,0:07:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 什么? 你说丙?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.14,0:07:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识吗 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.69,0:07:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...那家伙是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.70,0:07:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.16,0:07:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...那家伙是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.86,0:07:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于召唤我了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.08,0:07:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我美丽的铃子哟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.03,0:07:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这目空一切的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.94,0:07:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最适合冷笑的嘴唇
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.74,0:08:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那头发是怎么了 又被人类找麻烦了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.04,0:08:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恨的人类啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.59,0:08:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些触怒你的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.33,0:08:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就由我丙来全部咒杀掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.26,0:08:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 没有胸
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.85,0:08:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈!?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.17,0:08:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什...什么? 男人!?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.30,0:08:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是「重度铃子控」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.90,0:08:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜 好恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.32,0:08:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且她还非常讨厌男人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.50,0:08:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 这声音是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.73,0:08:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是斑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.69,0:08:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.74,0:08:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噗! 哈哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.80,0:08:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 你那副可笑的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.07,0:08:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.54,0:08:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.11,0:08:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.94,0:08:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就这么想被铃子疼爱么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.97,0:08:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你冷静下丙 夏目都被你吓到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.80,0:08:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 这个假铃子到底是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.77,0:08:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是夏目铃子的外孙 夏目贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.93,0:08:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外孙? 铃子她人呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.10,0:09:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久之前就去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.18,0:09:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗...多么的短暂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.72,0:09:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才不喜欢人类
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.46,0:09:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别靠近我 臭男人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.78,0:09:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.50,0:09:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是为了铃子外婆而哭的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.80,0:09:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.09,0:09:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为三篠那家伙说夏目在召唤我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.35,0:09:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以...不小心就兴奋过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.52,0:09:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.63,0:09:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.90,0:09:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是「五日印」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.83,0:09:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「五日印」?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.39,0:09:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法移动的妖怪会在路过的人身上种下印记
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.16,0:09:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,印记会在五天内吸尽那人的精气
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.20,0:10:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或将他引到印记主人身边被吞食掉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.58,0:10:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长此这般 印记主人最终将得到重获自由的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.34,0:10:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪 记不清是从哪里进去的了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.60,0:10:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你估计是进到了人类无法进入的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.49,0:10:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里遇到了印记的主人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.60,0:10:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 虽然很麻烦 但我会帮你调查下的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.86,0:10:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你就先回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.49,0:10:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情变得麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.33,0:10:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.48,0:10:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像不是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.05,0:10:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个或许会不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.03,0:11:02.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 你的胳膊怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.39,0:11:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被树枝刮到了 不要紧的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.37,0:11:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 要是化脓的话就糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.54,0:11:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.81,0:11:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 我还是很精神的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.70,0:11:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行哦 给我看...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.80,0:11:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.75,0:11:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真伤脑筋啊 果然又扩大了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.43,0:11:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这影子感觉好像「玛丽」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.77,0:11:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「玛丽」? 那是什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.74,0:11:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是说一个不明底细的东西会逐渐接近的有名怪谈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.71,0:11:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有电话打来说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.04,0:11:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我是玛丽 现在在门口」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.58,0:11:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过了一会儿 电话又会响起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.70,0:11:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去接的话 对方会说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.90,0:12:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我是玛丽 现在在玄关口」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.34,0:12:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和这个印记有什么关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.64,0:12:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.35,0:12:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明长了副和铃子一样的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.33,0:12:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别给我露出那种郁闷的表情嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.43,0:12:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.00,0:12:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道印记主人的真实身份了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.75,0:12:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是只被长年封印的强力邪鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.40,0:12:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它使用五日印来狩猎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.68,0:12:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点点地积蓄力量
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.84,0:12:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像再吃一个就能解除封印了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.30,0:12:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再吃一个? 是说我吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.78,0:12:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 逐渐重获力量的邪鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.13,0:12:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为等不及要解开封印 于是就先让影子跟过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.90,0:13:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那影子会通过印记来吸取你的精力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.73,0:13:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后使自己的行动越来越敏捷
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.50,0:13:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然现在动作还很迟缓 也才刚刚找到家里来而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.10,0:13:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一旦被那影子碰到就完了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.26,0:13:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 好大!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.82,0:13:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔 因为受到诅咒的波及
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.33,0:13:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖力变得不稳定了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.51,0:13:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 可恶 可恶 可恶...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.67,0:13:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.25,0:13:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.13,0:13:38.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志 你回来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.06,0:13:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.48,0:13:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪了 明明有听到声音的...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.29,0:13:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来吃掉那个影子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.98,0:13:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有印记的家伙是碰不到它的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.42,0:13:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么不好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.25,0:13:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五日印的效力还有四天
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.26,0:14:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段时间里你只要拼命逃开就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.60,0:14:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要逃开就行了吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.23,0:14:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有四天
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.68,0:14:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.58,0:14:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让他们担心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.33,0:14:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 待在一起的话不知道会发生什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.86,0:14:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半夜溜出去露宿 早上再悄悄回去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.57,0:14:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子婶婶他们应该不会发觉的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.99,0:15:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 死玛丽终于还是进到家里了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.49,0:15:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要回家比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.76,0:15:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸好明天开始就是连休了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.80,0:15:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 你难道在和外国人谈恋爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.02,0:15:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,International～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.65,0:15:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 塔子婶婶吗 我是贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.05,0:15:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后的三天我会住在朋友家
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.99,0:15:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不...是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.03,0:15:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 谁的家啊 就是那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.46,0:15:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 大家都在等我 先挂了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.25,0:15:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.89,0:15:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子婶婶会担心的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.78,0:15:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在一起的话会给他们添麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.86,0:15:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和铃子不同
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.19,0:16:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢人类吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.75,0:16:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候不喜欢与人多接触
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.13,0:16:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 遇到了那些善良的人们后
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.91,0:16:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂得了人的温柔体贴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.90,0:16:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想再逃避了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.12,0:16:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想变得温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.10,0:16:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是个男人却说得这么娘娘腔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.74,0:16:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.35,0:16:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.54,0:16:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.05,0:16:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.49,0:16:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.75,0:16:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么这次就暂且让式神来保护你吧 如何
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.03,0:16:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式神?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.38,0:16:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是能驱除影子的卷轴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.05,0:16:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来教你召唤方法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.47,0:16:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会很辛苦 要试试看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.49,0:16:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以你的体力 只有一次成功的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.94,0:16:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会召唤出大型式神呢 还是不上台面的小东西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.55,0:16:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 丙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.00,0:16:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜哇 为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.72,0:17:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明那么像铃子 为什么却是男人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.43,0:17:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很辛苦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.48,0:17:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在正式召唤前稍微休息下吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.13,0:17:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你抓几条鱼来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.88,0:17:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想...回到家里去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.91,0:18:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追来了吗 卷轴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.80,0:18:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要吃掉你 小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.34,0:18:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休想得逞!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.56,0:18:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.89,0:18:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 用这个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.08,0:18:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「光 自来处来」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.45,0:18:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「驱除阴影者!」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.17,0:18:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.95,0:19:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊 好小
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.46,0:19:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你的式神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.92,0:19:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 恢复原样了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.62,0:19:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 已经结束了 你的咒印也消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.18,0:19:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.10,0:19:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.74,0:19:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.10,0:20:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到你 我就知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.45,0:20:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「想要保护重要的人」 「不想给人添麻烦」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.65,0:20:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你心里尽是这样的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.41,0:20:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不懂得好好照顾自己的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.80,0:20:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最讨厌了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.55,0:20:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.98,0:20:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 真是了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.31,0:20:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我无礼试探了下夏目大人您
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.44,0:20:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将我的名字交付给人类究竟是不是个正确的决定
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.28,0:20:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试探?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.43,0:20:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用青蛙将您引诱到那邪鬼身边的正是我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.67,0:20:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三篠 你!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.43,0:20:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果您被吃掉的话 一切也就到此为止了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.08,0:20:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时友人帐就由我来接管
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.34,0:20:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么!?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.62,0:20:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么结论呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.23,0:20:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不适合
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.99,0:20:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 很有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.03,0:20:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很中意您 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.99,0:20:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂且就先把名字交付于您吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.70,0:21:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也并不讨厌被人召唤
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.70,0:21:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.27,0:21:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 如果是夏目你的话 被召唤也无妨
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.62,0:21:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 厌烦人类了的话随时都可以来我这里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.97,0:21:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.14,0:21:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到哪里去了!?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.74,0:21:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都那么问你要联络方式了!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.63,0:21:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对...对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.58,0:21:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我到那儿坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.91,0:21:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.97,0:21:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知不知道我有多担心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.65,0:21:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去朋友家住是没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.44,0:21:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是也得告诉我住址啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.77,0:21:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一有什么事的话要怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.31,0:21:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 我整晚上都担心得...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.63,0:21:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都睡不着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.92,0:21:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了 回到我自己的家了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.04,0:21:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有在听吗 贵志!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.87,0:21:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我有在听
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.68,0:22:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到了 和温暖体贴的人们一起生活的...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.03,0:22:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个家
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.10,0:23:51.00,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,540)}秋之夜宴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.68,0:23:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋日的深夜
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.06,0:23:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热闹的祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.75,0:23:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为天空着色的花火
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.07,0:23:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有在这小镇上遇到的善良的人们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.86,0:23:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了他们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.36,0:23:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有什么能做的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.02,0:22:12.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.02,0:22:12.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.96,0:22:19.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.96,0:22:19.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.92,0:22:26.39,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.92,0:22:26.39,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.39,0:22:33.32,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.39,0:22:33.32,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.08,0:22:44.37,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.08,0:22:44.37,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.37,0:22:48.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.37,0:22:48.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.76,0:22:58.22,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.76,0:22:58.22,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.22,0:23:05.86,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.22,0:23:05.86,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.86,0:23:12.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.86,0:23:12.92,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.92,0:23:20.28,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.92,0:23:20.28,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.28,0:23:28.00,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.28,0:23:28.00,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
