[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.15,0:02:03.15,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}玻璃的对面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.05,0:24:16.02,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\pos(178,296)}人与妖的临界
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだ　後姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}優しさで　胸が痛くて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々が人を惜しくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音に　夕闇に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも　一緒だよと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}叶わぬ事　繰り返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}温もいはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}鮮やかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来に変えながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 1,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:03.49,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.26,0:23:09.96,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:16.55,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.78,0:23:23.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.51,0:01:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧！又来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.02,0:01:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你过于在意飞车了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.51,0:01:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果移动那里的话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.11,0:01:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,角道那就有机可乘了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.67,0:01:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.91,0:01:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就分出胜负了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.59,0:01:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说夏目…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.07,0:01:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.47,0:02:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将军
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.71,0:02:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  刚才的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.75,0:02:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不能悔棋的是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.91,0:02:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到最后掉以轻心了嘛  北本
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.65,0:02:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真啰嗦  太过得意了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.74,0:02:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明才赢了这一次
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.19,0:02:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就按约定  请吃烤玉米咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.98,0:02:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就选苹果糖好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.94,0:02:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么连你都得请
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.81,0:02:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我和夏目的比赛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.52,0:02:30.05,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  比得怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.84,0:02:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  赢了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.95,0:02:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.17,0:02:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说夏目…你让田沼陪你练习了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.02,0:02:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  稍微练了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.26,0:02:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼也一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.19,0:02:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北本说他请客哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.82,0:02:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.56,0:02:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个季节也会有庙会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.32,0:02:53.87,Banner,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苹果糖  章鱼烧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.48,0:02:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是小规模而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.70,0:02:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是供奉着御柱大人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.83,0:03:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  御柱大人是后山的那个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.88,0:03:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了  刚烧好的两支玉米
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.83,0:03:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  教练费
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.27,0:03:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就不客气了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.87,0:03:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的份自己去买
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.11,0:03:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  小气
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.90,0:03:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.53,0:03:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  得赶紧的了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.16,0:03:24.61,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么声音
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.34,0:03:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  这个感觉是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.65,0:03:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.25,0:03:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.91,0:03:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.30,0:03:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.06,0:03:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算我不小心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.67,0:03:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但真没想到人类会拥有这么强大的妖力
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.36,0:03:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好  就把这个人类小孩带回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.40,0:03:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！ 等等  这是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.25,0:03:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.62,0:04:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.10,0:04:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.25,0:04:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  怎么了  身体不舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.28,0:04:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有一点贫血
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.40,0:04:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉北本  难得替我买吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.82,0:04:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢  身体不舒服的话就回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.62,0:04:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.68,0:04:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.24,0:04:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…难道说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.67,0:04:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.66,0:04:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.38,0:04:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.16,0:04:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  没什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.76,0:04:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢  不好意思  走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.41,0:04:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温暖而又愉悦的每一天
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.10,0:04:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近仅是像那般微不足道的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.86,0:04:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也会让我踌躇不已
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.73,0:04:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.62,0:04:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.66,0:04:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又在外面瞎晃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.70,0:04:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窗户就这么敞开着
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.06,0:05:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本还想问问老师有关那传单的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.58,0:05:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他或许会知道些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.13,0:05:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玻璃瓶？ 怎么了  从哪里…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.50,0:05:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妖怪扔进来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.62,0:05:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.40,0:05:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庙会最棒
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.18,0:05:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目那家伙  还在外面瞎晃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.79,0:05:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  到处乱跑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.21,0:05:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  趁现在喝一杯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.28,0:05:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.08,0:05:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是错觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.33,0:05:47.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师！ 猫咪老师！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.92,0:05:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目吗  在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.77,0:05:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里  我在这里  猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.47,0:05:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.70,0:06:00.52,Banner,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}ナツメ酒：枣果酒。棗（なつめ）同夏目同音
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.70,0:06:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目在枣果酒里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.81,0:06:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  是这边
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.21,0:06:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这是…怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.45,0:06:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一不小心被吸进来了  快帮我打开
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.02,0:06:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来像是妖怪的瓶子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.92,0:06:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可真是紧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.16,0:06:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.56,0:06:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比想象中结实啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.79,0:06:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.06,0:06:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.09,0:06:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手  会连我都被压碎的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.18,0:06:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如何
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.81,0:06:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热啊  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.10,0:06:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.46,0:06:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.45,0:06:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说你没法四处乱跑是好事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.40,0:06:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说绝对不行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.82,0:06:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.64,0:06:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的世界里会报警引发不得了的骚乱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.26,0:06:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个瓶子看样子只有它的主人才能打开
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.70,0:06:58.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强行打开的话你会有生命危险
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.29,0:07:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓶子的主人在哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.14,0:07:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.57,0:07:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只好四处寻找了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.91,0:07:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四处寻找？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.67,0:07:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找到之前我该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.44,0:07:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说塔子阿姨他们也知道我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.16,0:07:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.18,0:07:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志君  差不多可以吃饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.88,0:07:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.15,0:07:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕人类听不到现在的你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.08,0:07:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也看不到你的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.95,0:07:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样…  那样的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.53,0:07:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚吃炸里脊排啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.55,0:07:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这欠我份大人情咯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.18,0:07:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本我是不太擅长这个的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.11,0:07:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但像我这样的大妖怪的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.81,0:07:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你打算做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.78,0:07:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.47,0:08:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来如何
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.72,0:08:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这么问…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.51,0:08:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.58,0:08:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.24,0:08:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是从来没摆过的姿势
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.08,0:08:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不太明白
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.93,0:08:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得有点恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.86,0:08:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.15,0:08:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  一模一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.59,0:08:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 我长那样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.38,0:08:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志  饭要凉了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.26,0:08:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了来了  现在就来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.67,0:08:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是晚饭  别跑啊  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.95,0:08:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让您久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.99,0:08:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶呀  那是什么瓶子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.79,0:08:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在意  不  请不要在意
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.14,0:08:48.56,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的看不见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.81,0:08:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能替我从冰箱里拿出滋的啤酒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.68,0:08:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行行~
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.57,0:08:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么拉长语气说话  像小孩子一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.07,0:09:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊  老师  绝对不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.82,0:09:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  肚子饿坏了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.64,0:09:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为才刚要长个子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.42,0:09:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽  不  美味
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.04,0:09:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么狼吞虎咽  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.18,0:09:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽没有副食稍显冷清
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.52,0:09:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过比起以往吃的要好百倍
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.94,0:09:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以别说多余的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.71,0:09:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一碗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.42,0:09:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.45,0:09:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真少见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.39,0:09:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  明天我们会晚点回家
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.08,0:09:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.58,0:09:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该说「是这样吗」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.23,0:09:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.29,0:09:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才接到电话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.15,0:09:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾受过关照的一位先生摆头七
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.64,0:09:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我和滋一起过去帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.64,0:09:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.15,0:09:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  老师  等话说完了再吃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.82,0:09:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天的晚饭我会先做好奶汁烤菜
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.74,0:09:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热一热就能吃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.01,0:09:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.04,0:10:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  饱了饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.82,0:10:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天塔子阿姨他们不在可以说是不幸之大幸了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.25,0:10:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得想法在那之前从这里出去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.66,0:10:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天的奶汁烤菜何时做好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.68,0:10:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心奶汁烤菜之前先帮我想想办法
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.29,0:10:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说这样下去  不光吃饭厕所也…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.26,0:10:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.22,0:10:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还不是很饿
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.59,0:10:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然  看起来没有通气口
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.50,0:10:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕瓶子里面应该和妖怪的世界相连
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.35,0:10:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪们肚子不会饿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.46,0:10:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有些只要不发觉肚子饿就不用摄食的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.12,0:10:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本质上是和人类不同的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.27,0:10:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天已经很晚了  睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.38,0:10:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.09,0:10:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧  我已经想好对策了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.40,0:10:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.09,0:11:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连对方是怎样的妖怪都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.25,0:11:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的能找到瓶子的主人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.67,0:11:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么声音
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.10,0:11:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦太好了  真的抓到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.49,0:11:18.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在把他带回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.67,0:11:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个妖怪…是庙会那时的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.64,0:11:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.05,0:11:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然  我就知道一定会来拿回瓶子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.41,0:11:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.77,0:11:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓶子里的是我的猎物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.38,0:11:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快把他放出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.59,0:11:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是敬献给御柱大人的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.74,0:11:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准你捣乱  怪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.94,0:11:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御柱?!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.50,0:11:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把瓶子打开
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.34,0:11:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃得真快
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.55,0:11:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得救了  猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.15,0:11:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是没能从瓶里出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.47,0:12:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妖怪刚说了御柱大人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.72,0:12:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.99,0:12:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在去庙会的时候西村他们有说过
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.47,0:12:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后山上的什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.45,0:12:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后山？ 哪儿的？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.82,0:12:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.41,0:12:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,具体就不太清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.45,0:12:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥没去问清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.95,0:12:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去问西村他们的话或许就能…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.82,0:12:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实如果去学校的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.70,0:12:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能得到一个叫做便当的东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.46,0:12:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那个就成交
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.14,0:12:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没有问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.11,0:12:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.11,0:12:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.62,0:12:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要迟到了  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.34,0:12:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炸鸡块啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.68,0:12:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得等到中饭时间才能吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.09,0:12:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们中午也会要出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.33,0:12:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来后要好好吃饭看好家门哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.78,0:12:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.74,0:12:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.74,0:12:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不…好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.25,0:13:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.80,0:13:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便当便当  便当便当…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.20,0:13:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仍旧尽是些穿着相似衣服的家伙走来走去的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.82,0:13:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少管这些了  就只要打个招呼就行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.58,0:13:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说多余的话  跟西村问清楚了就回去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.80,0:13:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.13,0:13:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  哈欠真大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.32,0:13:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西村
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.96,0:13:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我过来下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.60,0:13:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在那磨磨蹭蹭的了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.54,0:13:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点过来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.56,0:13:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  再温和一点  以笑脸迎人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.59,0:13:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰啰嗦嗦的真烦人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.78,0:13:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…难道你生气…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.09,0:13:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.84,0:13:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.82,0:13:57.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有些事情想要问问你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.81,0:13:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来过来~
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.83,0:14:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  要不要去下保健室？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.01,0:14:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.57,0:14:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  礼貌点  客气点
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.09,0:14:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御柱？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.23,0:14:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是  他在哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.25,0:14:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后山
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.47,0:14:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后山的哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.21,0:14:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前提到过的那个是指的什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.82,0:14:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不晓得  具体细节我不太清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.60,0:14:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙是笨蛋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.89,0:14:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以都说别说多余的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.65,0:14:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北本的话或许会知道点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.41,0:14:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御柱？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.56,0:14:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  之前提到过的那个是指的什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.04,0:14:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.32,0:14:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  冷静下来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.39,0:14:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不太清楚详细经过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.33,0:14:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过听女生们谣传说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.94,0:14:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后山有那个叫做御柱的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.26,0:14:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女生里有谁可能知道具体内容？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.43,0:14:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女生里有哪个家伙会知道？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.86,0:14:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家伙？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.47,0:14:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少钻我牛角尖了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.79,0:15:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在相当地不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.97,0:15:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.09,0:15:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜大概会是笹田
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.78,0:15:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很喜欢这种话题
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.11,0:15:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.25,0:15:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师你该见过她很多次了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.77,0:15:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.47,0:15:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  冷静下来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.41,0:15:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽量避免过激行为
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.76,0:15:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田  笹田纯在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.35,0:15:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小纯她说要去还书  所以去图书室…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.49,0:15:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还了书以后  说要去理科室拿资料
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.57,0:15:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,资料送到后说去职员办公室…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.32,0:15:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来三年级的课要用到  就让她拿过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.20,0:15:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她回到自己班级里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.63,0:15:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君  你在找我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.68,0:15:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  要礼貌些  要温柔些
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.07,0:15:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.66,0:16:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  对了  今早见到一只和你家八怪猫很像的猫呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.91,0:16:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是肥肥的丑八…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.67,0:16:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话要跟你说…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.54,0:16:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.33,0:16:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在马上…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.18,0:16:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…等下…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.80,0:16:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…等等…班上同学们都在看着…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.47,0:16:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师给我住手  快放开手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.20,0:16:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.75,0:16:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是御柱？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.29,0:16:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.01,0:16:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃…  那个…夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.09,0:16:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…看起来很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.95,0:16:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师!!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.84,0:16:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么意思…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.85,0:16:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说「好香」的意思是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.85,0:16:58.08,Banner,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}日语中「香」和「好吃」音同
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.51,0:17:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饱了  饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.74,0:17:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  如果变回原来的样子的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.06,0:17:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天发生的事情要如何做解释才好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.02,0:17:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少管那些  现在该关心御柱的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.57,0:17:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连我的便当都吃得一干二净
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.59,0:17:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据笹田所述
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.20,0:17:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传言说这后山上有座封印着叫做御柱的家伙的神庙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.20,0:17:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近因为施工而遭到破坏的一块巨石
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.65,0:17:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是那神庙的说法正传得沸沸扬扬
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.09,0:17:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说被封印着的妖怪复苏后重现于世了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.47,0:17:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.05,0:17:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.23,0:17:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神野御柱大人复活
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.75,0:17:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻求庇佑的下等妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.55,0:17:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,携带敬奉之物集聚一堂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.17,0:17:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若这就是在妖怪间广为流传着的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.53,0:17:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说明一旦其力量复原的话  也是相当了不得的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.26,0:17:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要接近的比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.94,0:18:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我会变怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.80,0:18:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该瓶子的主人并非是御柱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.75,0:18:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是鬼猿
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.30,0:18:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能抓住他的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.74,0:18:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.42,0:18:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.78,0:18:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.13,0:18:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西村和北本都说你就像变了一个人似的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.04,0:18:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.18,0:18:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个瓶子是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.17,0:18:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.22,0:18:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天身体不佳  先回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.57,0:18:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头见  田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.60,0:18:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.97,0:18:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也别太靠近后山了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.65,0:18:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.55,0:18:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个瓶子里装的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.39,0:18:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  这里面装着相当有趣的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.42,0:18:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣的东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.75,0:18:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼你…或许是看不到的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.75,0:18:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是夏目吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.95,0:19:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你要说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.53,0:19:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很奇怪吗  田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.19,0:19:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是何来历
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.62,0:19:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目才不会那么说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.50,0:19:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目他怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.84,0:19:08.54,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.83,0:19:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是妖怪吗  到底是什么家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.68,0:19:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.03,0:19:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是想要给你点忠告  就闹成这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.42,0:19:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直觉准的家伙就是麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.08,0:19:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那么想要知道我的真面目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.56,0:19:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.13,0:19:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇…胖太
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.65,0:19:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  混蛋  中年猫咪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.37,0:19:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥要把田沼给牵扯进来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.98,0:19:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是牵扯进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.55,0:19:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是他自己找上门来的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.24,0:19:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怨你说些让他起疑心的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.36,0:19:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么！ 都怪你说这说那的弄得乱七八糟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.72,0:19:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让我滚滚你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.11,0:19:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来好像只是猫在玩弄着空瓶子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.41,0:19:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目真的就在那里面吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.39,0:20:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  看不到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.04,0:20:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.27,0:20:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便一提  夏目现在正是满脸恶相
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.61,0:20:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在生气吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.68,0:20:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用我说明原因了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.79,0:20:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  确实呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.81,0:20:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在的我又听不到夏目的意见
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.33,0:20:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要帮忙也是我自己的选择啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.11,0:20:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换作夏目  若我也遇上同样的事情的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.50,0:20:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也一定会这么做的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.77,0:20:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  田沼  不可以这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.35,0:20:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要抱怨的话  就先平安地从瓶里出来再说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.91,0:20:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为我担忧的这份心情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.93,0:20:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越是浓烈越是让人担忧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.24,0:20:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不由觉得或许以后会演变成无法挽回的过错
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.74,0:20:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  还真够闹腾的呢  咪咪老师您啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.76,0:20:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田她正严重地花痴中
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.89,0:20:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪夏目他在一旁废话连篇  才没法解释清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.19,0:20:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么打算怎么做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.61,0:20:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捕获该瓶子的主人鬼猿
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.91,0:21:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过守株待兔也无妨  对方一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.24,0:21:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来前方很可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.50,0:21:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么东西在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.11,0:21:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了吗  给我等等
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.16,0:21:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…有什么东西在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.79,0:21:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  已经够了  住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.49,0:21:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼猿的目的是这个瓶子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.55,0:21:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赶紧放下这个瓶子离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.59,0:21:21.18,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个感觉是什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.58,0:21:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.75,0:21:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  田沼  就在你身后
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.75,0:21:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那是什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.84,0:21:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉有些晕眩
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.29,0:21:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.87,0:21:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.82,0:21:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.73,0:21:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.74,0:21:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,异样…哪怕能察觉出什么异样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.66,0:21:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.12,0:21:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.84,0:21:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.03,0:22:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.20,0:22:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是什么地方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.77,0:22:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校的后山里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.44,0:22:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该没有这座石阶的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.91,0:22:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看见…妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.65,0:22:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.49,0:24:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  别乱来了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.45,0:24:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你若有个三长两短的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.87,0:24:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要去救回夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.82,0:24:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都因为我  把田沼给牵扯进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.76,0:24:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开不了门
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.08,0:24:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是被关起来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.30,0:24:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很奇怪的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.73,0:24:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许会变成相当棘手的事情
