[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.08,0:01:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生～
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.95,0:01:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生～
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.87,0:01:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 跑哪里去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.31,0:01:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好...痛痛痛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.64,0:01:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么有去七辻屋的近路
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.39,0:01:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本没条像样的路嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.63,0:02:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好天气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.06,0:02:13.91,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秋之夜宴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.66,0:02:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目这家伙 都说了要好好跟着我了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.11,0:02:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是彻底走散了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.08,0:02:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.78,0:02:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让我等他个五秒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.21,0:02:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.98,0:02:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.89,0:02:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.18,0:02:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.77,0:02:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 什么啊 原来是只猫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.20,0:02:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别吓我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.22,0:02:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 这只笨肥猫 记得应该是夏目家的...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.02,0:03:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵喵先生吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.91,0:03:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵喵先生 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.38,0:03:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵喵...?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.14,0:03:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个让人叫起来不好意思的名字啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.89,0:03:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫「胖太」可以吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.41,0:03:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 胖太 快起来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.68,0:03:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 胖太
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.73,0:03:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我猫先生 笨蛋!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.06,0:03:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 记得是叫田沼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.86,0:03:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是个傻瓜 还蛮能干的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.32,0:03:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.96,0:03:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.94,0:03:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.11,0:03:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说话了!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.82,0:03:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.28,0:03:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还没从夏目那里听说我的真实身份
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.63,0:03:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你原来是妖怪吗 胖太
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.07,0:03:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是猫先生啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.71,0:03:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.45,0:03:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大体上说来是的 但我是妖怪中非常高贵的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.50,0:03:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别随便把我和那些小妖怪们相提并论
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.39,0:03:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我第一次...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.52,0:03:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.68,0:04:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我第一次和妖怪说话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.20,0:04:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 你并不是完全能看到妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.32,0:04:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以夏目才没告诉你我的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.80,0:04:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为告诉你也没什么用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.41,0:04:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.12,0:04:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.21,0:04:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是夏目的什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.17,0:04:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他的先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.33,0:04:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我的手下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.97,0:04:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手下?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.15,0:04:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没做什么对夏目不好的事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.81,0:04:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.43,0:04:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论怎么看 做手下的都是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.22,0:04:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有威胁他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.18,0:04:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙! 那跟你说清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.06,0:04:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你知道了我的真实身份
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.90,0:04:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就不得不杀你灭口了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.38,0:04:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.10,0:04:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么啊 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.49,0:04:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏...夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.30,0:05:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只猫 怎么会跟你在一起的?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.60,0:05:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 先生他 算是保镖那样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.33,0:05:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.88,0:05:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想说的话没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.63,0:05:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.76,0:05:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有点复杂 我也不知道该怎么说明
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.56,0:05:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个 也不是想对田沼隐瞒什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.19,0:05:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 也不是 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.60,0:05:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实是想要隐瞒的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.49,0:05:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和田沼你普通地进行交谈
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.04,0:05:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不想给你留下不快的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.42,0:05:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有不快的回忆吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.88,0:05:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 看啊 我抓到条大的了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.12,0:05:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.92,0:05:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 也不全是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.76,0:06:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.01,0:06:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.23,0:06:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天晚上有祭典活动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.98,0:06:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是秋季祭典吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.61,0:06:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 去看看吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.94,0:06:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在准备中啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.98,0:06:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备中也没关系 快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.04,0:06:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等下啊 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.62,0:06:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去神社的话我正好顺路 我陪你们一起吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.83,0:06:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.29,0:06:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 还没开始吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.17,0:06:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不是说了还在准备中了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.76,0:06:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为起码露天摊点已经开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.38,0:06:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.47,0:06:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.10,0:06:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 还没开始就来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.07,0:06:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有认识的人在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.52,0:06:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.65,0:06:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这边帮忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.13,0:06:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 受人拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.19,0:06:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.28,0:07:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有吧 就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.66,0:07:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有? 有什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.14,0:07:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装傻了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.41,0:07:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说这种热闹的场合他们最爱聚集起来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.78,0:07:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还在说这个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.92,0:07:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过...确实
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.75,0:07:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边有很多妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.22,0:07:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说中了吧 有什么样的妖怪在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.83,0:07:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小纯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.51,0:07:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 帮我把这个搬进神社前殿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.72,0:07:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.14,0:07:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.77,0:07:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 搬到前殿就拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.02,0:07:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来搬?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.22,0:07:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点啦 我现在正在聊天中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.94,0:07:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被人拜托的是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.60,0:07:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跟班长顶嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.20,0:07:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你们不是一班的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.95,0:07:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我来搬吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.66,0:07:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君可不能去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.33,0:07:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小纯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.45,0:07:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 现在这个人就来搬
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.70,0:07:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.74,0:07:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.01,0:07:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微等我下 马上就回来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.40,0:07:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.00,0:07:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.43,0:08:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祭典的话 夏目肯定也会来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.63,0:08:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.48,0:08:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天完全是狐狸形态吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.60,0:08:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.11,0:08:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.45,0:08:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干的好事啊 小东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.13,0:08:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不是我干的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.95,0:08:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的样子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.71,0:08:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类是看不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.76,0:08:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好过分
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.01,0:08:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家辛苦准备的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.25,0:08:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙 可不会饶了你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.00,0:08:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的不是的 不是我干的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.72,0:08:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别乱动 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.69,0:08:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.73,0:08:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.19,0:08:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有点过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.24,0:08:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你谁啊 跟你没关系吧 快滚开
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.94,0:09:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你亲眼看到这只小狐狸打翻铁桶的?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.95,0:09:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...虽然没看到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.82,0:09:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这里只有这只狐狸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.87,0:09:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是风刮倒的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.13,0:09:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快放手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.22,0:09:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔 他能看到我们 怪物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.73,0:09:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 大麦茶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.47,0:09:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.98,0:09:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空得让人吃惊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.44,0:09:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不会啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.15,0:09:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好到时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.15,0:09:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天花板上的角落
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.28,0:09:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天花板?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.57,0:09:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.20,0:09:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.20,0:09:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是水池的倒影吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.62,0:10:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.46,0:10:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庭院里根本没什么水池
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.10,0:10:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以天花板上的水纹大概只有我们能看见
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.39,0:10:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.69,0:10:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊...没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.52,0:10:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 真是不可思议
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.20,0:10:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼是看不到水池的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.33,0:10:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.66,0:10:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.74,0:10:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.67,0:10:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被他们逃了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.93,0:10:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目家的大丑猫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.59,0:10:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有它在的话 夏目君就一定会回来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.01,0:10:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.26,0:10:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 有绳子吗 要尽量粗的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.43,0:11:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 快住手 那不是胡子啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.19,0:11:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是肩胛骨 快住手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.33,0:11:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.28,0:11:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用客气
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.12,0:11:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能听懂我说的话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.00,0:11:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.37,0:11:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识夏目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.67,0:11:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不认识
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.62,0:11:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 夏目也能听懂我说的话哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.46,0:11:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是来见他的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.92,0:11:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 因为他肯定会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.18,0:11:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 能见到就好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.59,0:11:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那就这样 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.81,0:11:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.56,0:11:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.56,0:11:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去跟着那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.28,0:11:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.15,0:11:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.58,0:12:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太大意了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.38,0:12:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微冷静点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.09,0:12:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志真是的 要直接去祭典的话说下就好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.05,0:12:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志可不是小孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.85,0:12:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 要是有什么事的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.57,0:12:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是爱操心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.15,0:12:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真那样的话 猫五郎会来通知我们的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.11,0:12:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可别乱开玩笑 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.16,0:12:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志来这里多久了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.38,0:12:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来大概都是些不好的回忆吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.25,0:12:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是对我们太见外了 那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.01,0:12:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子能做些任性的事 对我来说更安心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.50,0:12:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心过头 可不是家人会做的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.14,0:12:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.20,0:13:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来得稍微早了点呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.07,0:13:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.48,0:13:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.08,0:13:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 是失物吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.08,0:13:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来送过去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.08,0:13:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是捡到的失物吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.71,0:13:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 由我们来保管
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.00,0:13:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就拜托你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.13,0:13:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.54,0:13:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这个是失物
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.22,0:13:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.10,0:13:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫猫 你怎么了 被抓住了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.61,0:13:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么坏事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.90,0:13:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好! 民子来救你出去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.45,0:13:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃走了!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.38,0:14:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微来帮我下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.13,0:14:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在呢 胖太
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.72,0:14:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.43,0:14:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胖太?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.38,0:14:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 抱歉 是我取的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.47,0:14:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不分头找找?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.79,0:14:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 能帮忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.44,0:14:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.78,0:14:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找不到呢 丝巾袋子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.78,0:14:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不起来在哪里丢的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.45,0:14:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里面放着那么重要的东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.08,0:14:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 非常重要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.33,0:14:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 去那边再找找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.89,0:15:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑哪里去了啊 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.18,0:15:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.85,0:15:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 夏目 你果然来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.69,0:15:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 猫先...不 有看到我家的猫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.11,0:15:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只肥猫? 没看到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.24,0:15:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.28,0:15:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它逃走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.20,0:15:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.11,0:15:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.03,0:15:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.86,0:15:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.54,0:15:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.21,0:15:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔 我的回转烧呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.37,0:15:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚不是给你了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.37,0:15:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没拿到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.83,0:15:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你了啊 快付钱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.09,0:15:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没拿到付什么钱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.22,0:15:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么?!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.26,0:15:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.97,0:15:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 多少钱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.10,0:15:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 在干什么啊 那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.23,0:15:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.11,0:16:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.07,0:16:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面究竟装着什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.91,0:16:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是药
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.62,0:16:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,药?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.12,0:16:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短时间里能幻成人形的药
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.12,0:16:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是动物的样子的话会给夏目添麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.29,0:16:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 是这么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.92,0:16:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 那我去给你... 喂!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.34,0:16:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这被食物的香味引诱而来的小狐狸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.01,0:16:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行啊 去 去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.47,0:16:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.35,0:16:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.42,0:16:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.73,0:16:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.58,0:16:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目君
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.15,0:16:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它跑进去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.12,0:16:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.07,0:16:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我让它回山上去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.08,0:16:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.75,0:16:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.07,0:16:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.25,0:16:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.50,0:16:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锅子 煮开了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.17,0:16:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.79,0:17:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪啊 火明明关小了的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.30,0:17:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.42,0:17:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样子跑到人群里不是很危险吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.52,0:17:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.68,0:17:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.52,0:17:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你拿来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.49,0:17:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.20,0:17:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.71,0:17:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊 你在这的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.80,0:17:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生也在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.21,0:17:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 来见几个人的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.25,0:17:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是受他之托跟着这孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.38,0:17:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没防备啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.05,0:17:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在人群聚集的地方和我说话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.03,0:17:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会被人非议的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.26,0:17:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.97,0:17:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 我能见到你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.52,0:17:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个滥好人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.67,0:18:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.83,0:18:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是刚才的小狐狸吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.51,0:18:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.82,0:18:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于自由了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.54,0:18:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是夏目这家伙 竟然都不来救我 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.21,0:18:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.87,0:19:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丑猫
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.62,0:19:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO～～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.63,0:19:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一带还真是有点冷啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.63,0:19:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.02,0:19:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过很安静
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.06,0:19:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.64,0:19:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.64,0:19:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目你能看到庭院里的水池吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.77,0:19:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只能看到天花板上的倒影
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.36,0:19:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子阿姨知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.15,0:19:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能看到妖怪这些
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.92,0:19:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.33,0:19:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不信任他们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.33,0:19:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.13,0:19:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们都很善良
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.79,0:19:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以只要我说出来的话肯定都会接受的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.25,0:19:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 正因为这份善良
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.09,0:19:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想到我至今为止的遭遇
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.43,0:19:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们肯定会难过的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.68,0:19:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这或许只是我自己的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.77,0:19:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还是不希望那样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.23,0:20:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望他们能一直微笑着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.77,0:20:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.58,0:20:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比预想的要壮观啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.78,0:20:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为在乡下会有点寒碜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.30,0:20:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.57,0:20:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.70,0:20:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.96,0:20:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 其实我看不到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.93,0:20:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.10,0:20:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说 有个大家伙挡在我前面
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.93,0:20:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家伙? 妖怪吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.86,0:20:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 不过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.56,0:20:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道很漂亮的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.55,0:20:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这家伙看得那么入迷
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.28,0:20:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微走走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.15,0:20:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许会有夏目也能看到的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.99,0:20:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.35,0:21:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.94,0:21:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的话能看得很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.81,0:21:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.42,0:21:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒影中的鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.51,0:21:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际是什么颜色的?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.80,0:21:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是红色的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.98,0:21:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红色
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.45,0:21:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.78,0:21:31.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里吗 你这薄情的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.95,0:21:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.11,0:21:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然把重要的保镖丢在一边
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.69,0:21:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙真是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.98,0:21:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烟花又升起了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.97,0:21:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能听到冬天临近的脚步声
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.18,0:21:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这秋日的夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.01,0:22:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这里还是那么温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.12,0:22:12.67,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.12,0:22:12.67,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.06,0:22:20.02,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.06,0:22:20.02,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.02,0:22:26.49,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.02,0:22:26.49,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.49,0:22:33.42,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.49,0:22:33.42,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.18,0:22:44.47,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.18,0:22:44.47,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.47,0:22:48.67,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.47,0:22:48.67,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.86,0:22:58.32,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.86,0:22:58.32,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.32,0:23:05.96,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.32,0:23:05.96,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.96,0:23:13.02,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.96,0:23:13.02,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.02,0:23:20.38,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.02,0:23:20.38,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.38,0:23:28.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.38,0:23:28.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
