[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.17,0:03:10.17,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1}人非人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.96,0:24:15.96,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1\pos(160,296)}除妖人
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.01,0:01:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.04,0:01:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是烤鱿鱼  烤鱿鱼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.58,0:01:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日祭快到了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.70,0:01:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你光看干什么  快买  买给我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.12,0:01:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘  会被人听到的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.41,0:01:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪可是不能吃鱿鱼的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.23,0:01:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  我才不是猫咪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.88,0:01:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想夺去中年人对鱿鱼的爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.95,0:01:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别净说些让人不想再抱住你的发言
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.90,0:02:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  要好好地嚼哦  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.67,0:02:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烤鱿鱼最好吃的地方还属鱿鱼须呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.76,0:02:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鱿鱼…啊等等  鱿鱼等等啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.16,0:02:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中年之星
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.12,0:02:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中年之星到底是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.74,0:02:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  抱歉了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.20,0:02:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  没什么  我才要抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.26,0:02:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？血
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.26,0:02:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是血
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.73,0:02:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在了…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.48,0:02:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那人是妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.45,0:03:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,油纸伞…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.07,0:03:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.29,0:03:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.45,0:03:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在磨蹭些什么  快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.72,0:03:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.99,0:04:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是  因为你的到来我才恢复了意识
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.32,0:04:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此彼此啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.36,0:04:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是丢脸呢  居然被女人抱着
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.95,0:04:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…话说回来她是妖怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.78,0:04:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你还真是重呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.27,0:04:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且体温也很高…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.87,0:04:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难道是…人类！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.63,0:04:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？现在才发现…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.54,0:04:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.77,0:04:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来接  我来接  我来接
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.18,0:04:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不住了  没想到你是人类  不禁吓了一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.18,0:04:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.36,0:04:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  所幸落在了一个很柔软的靠垫上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.46,0:04:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  我可不是靠垫
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.47,0:04:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目？你难道就是那个友人帐的持有者？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.29,0:04:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你会更有型一些呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.14,0:04:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点跪下  说出你的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.34,0:05:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  那是我的祖母
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.01,0:05:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  不过即便孱弱夏目也还是夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.84,0:05:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  我有个请求
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.41,0:05:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能否借我一臂之力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.35,0:05:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.40,0:05:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近这一带不断有妖怪身负重伤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.04,0:05:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且全身的血液都被吸走
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.58,0:05:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我为调查犯人而走遍森林的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.83,0:05:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了同伴们  我想查清那究竟是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.07,0:05:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能借我一臂之力的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.35,0:05:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢货  不要乱说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.95,0:05:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可没有义务帮助她  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.83,0:05:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对方是夺取血液的猎奇犯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.73,0:05:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果处理得不好而牵连了塔子阿姨们的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.47,0:05:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.07,0:06:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  我并无意让您为难
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.16,0:06:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想来并未有何理由让身为人类的你也牵连进来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.01,0:06:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不住了  忘了这些吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.98,0:06:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你的同伴们怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.06,0:06:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被袭击了之后没事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.83,0:06:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说  同伴们是家人一般的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.81,0:06:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少那些仅存的同伴们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.58,0:06:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须要保护他们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.93,0:06:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.80,0:06:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.36,0:06:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经下决心不去趟这浑水了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.69,0:06:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无论趟不趟这趟浑水都显得这么消沉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.05,0:06:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一直嘻嘻哈哈着的玲子大相径庭呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.12,0:06:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.12,0:06:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志  差不多该吃晚饭了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.25,0:06:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  马上就去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.06,0:07:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽是这么说  你还是在消沉着对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.79,0:07:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次不去管这件事真是做对了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.31,0:07:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.11,0:07:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙说妖怪们的血被夺走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.84,0:07:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么犯人便不一定是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.66,0:07:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说过人类中也有人用妖怪的血来施展法术呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.81,0:07:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.25,0:07:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓伤时的那种手感
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.90,0:07:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那的确与其说是妖怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.30,0:07:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所珍视着的究竟是人类还是妖怪？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.48,0:07:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做个决定如何
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.06,0:07:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.36,0:07:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  蠢货住手  难得决定不管这些事…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.90,0:07:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  但这是我的秉性  你就放弃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.58,0:07:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到人类在不断猎杀妖怪并夺取它们的血液
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.70,0:07:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我便不能再袖手旁观了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.77,0:08:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  夏目老大真是感谢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.14,0:08:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到天气会变得这么热
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.52,0:08:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一不小心就走出了河
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.91,0:08:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点哦  如果我没经过这里的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.97,0:08:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可就会被晒干了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.70,0:08:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么继续刚才的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.22,0:08:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到过有人在夺取着妖怪的血
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.06,0:08:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.72,0:08:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操纵巨大而可怕的黑影袭击妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.46,0:08:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着和服的人一直站在旁边看着
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.23,0:08:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着和服的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.54,0:08:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是人类吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.61,0:08:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没看清脸  但大概是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.87,0:08:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然  袭击妖怪的是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.83,0:08:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要做那种事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.38,0:08:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师…刚才那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.59,0:08:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手臂上有一道伤痕
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.69,0:08:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是偶然的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.63,0:09:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我昨天抓伤的就是个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.92,0:09:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.63,0:09:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的那个家伙是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.89,0:09:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一种极为不详的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.14,0:09:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我追上去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.18,0:09:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.46,0:09:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.36,0:09:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  真是令人操心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.80,0:09:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.85,0:09:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵  你看得见妖怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.85,0:09:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还带着一只很有趣的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.48,0:09:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.00,0:09:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可真是失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.02,0:10:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字是的场静司
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.71,0:10:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.07,0:10:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除妖的的场一族
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.08,0:10:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说他们为了驱除妖怪而将妖怪作为诱饵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.03,0:10:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且触及一些过分的法术
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.83,0:10:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那时的的场一族的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.58,0:10:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人就是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.36,0:10:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人就是的场
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.54,0:10:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是那个时候冲进来的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.04,0:10:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你做了过分的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.87,0:10:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为你是妖怪的残党
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.14,0:10:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  该如何称呼你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.12,0:10:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报上名字会有麻烦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.09,0:10:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你在收集妖怪的血…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.80,0:10:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底知道多少
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.81,0:10:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们好好聊聊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.28,0:11:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.59,0:11:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  总之…把那个…像沙袋一样的东西给扔掉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.08,0:11:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么！谁像沙袋来着！喂  混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.71,0:11:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底哪里像！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.38,0:11:20.63,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说到底哪里像了！喂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.69,0:11:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纸人  这个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.49,0:11:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤势肯定很严重  不好好休息一下的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.75,0:11:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退下  的场的仆人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.20,0:12:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我名取的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.55,0:12:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决不允许你们对他乱来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.05,0:12:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.61,0:12:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去告诉你们的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.63,0:12:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了  柊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.80,0:12:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤得很严重  但稍加休息便能痊愈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.85,0:12:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但能平安无事真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.93,0:12:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  这不都怨你的纸人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.91,0:12:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这都被压扁几次了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.19,0:12:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  为何会来这
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.65,0:12:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说的场在这附近有些动静
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.45,0:12:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同为除妖人  有些在意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.24,0:12:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是在收集妖怪的血液
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.71,0:12:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了某个术式
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.98,0:12:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  所以才放心不下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.38,0:12:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真没有变呢  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.11,0:12:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  确实让人担心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.24,0:12:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要稍微调查一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.43,0:12:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.79,0:12:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁叫总是让你来帮我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.06,0:12:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次就让我来帮你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.35,0:13:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.58,0:13:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免费的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.64,0:13:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不计报酬也行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.76,0:13:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.45,0:13:09.63,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.93,0:13:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样羽之妖怪就交给了柊照看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.02,0:13:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和名取便开始调查这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.84,0:13:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是的场还真年轻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.07,0:13:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说是首领
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.69,0:13:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为应该是更老滑头一些
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.28,0:13:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪不过是我的小弟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.79,0:13:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来捣乱的家伙统统用席子卷好丢河里去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.40,0:13:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年纪轻轻就带眼罩  留长发  打油伞
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.39,0:13:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扮还真是异类
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.94,0:13:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是有各种原因的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.72,0:13:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如长发  把头发给妖怪的话  会让交涉更为容易
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.51,0:13:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼罩也是…有很多原因吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.93,0:13:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天之前我会去稍微调查下的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.08,0:13:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你就先回去休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.48,0:13:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.62,0:13:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我们走吧  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.94,0:14:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取家的小少爷在叹气  真是少见
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.72,0:14:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七濑女士
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.38,0:14:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有何贵干
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.03,0:14:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我听说你在工作的时候出错了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.51,0:14:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还抢我们的饭碗  真不像你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.26,0:14:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不算是失败啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.41,0:14:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有妖怪出没的旧门确实封印了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.91,0:14:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的妖怪也驱赶掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.53,0:14:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱赶？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.26,0:14:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你变仁慈了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.46,0:14:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是像的场一族那般强大的驱妖人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.98,0:14:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力有不逮啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.57,0:14:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这讽刺听起来还真是没有魄力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.71,0:14:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而感觉像是想要隐瞒些什么似的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.08,0:14:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是老样子呢  七濑女士
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.39,0:14:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对顶级的除妖一族有什么好隐瞒的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.83,0:14:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.77,0:15:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是说并非是不想我们接近那个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.44,0:15:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才抢了我们的工作的咯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.40,0:15:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我一定要那么做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.35,0:15:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.43,0:15:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有摄影的工作  就先告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.82,0:15:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你常提起夏目玲子的孙子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.29,0:15:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近都没怎么见过面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.44,0:15:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住在哪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.68,0:15:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是个人隐私哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.37,0:15:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取  当家的正在那个城镇里调查
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.51,0:15:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要妨碍他
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.69,0:15:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家的首领可是急性子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.62,0:15:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近习惯了同人类之间的温情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.77,0:15:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉有些过于依赖他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.45,0:15:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明还隐瞒着友人帐的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.31,0:15:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却还让人家帮我忙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.78,0:15:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来得好好跟名取道谢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.53,0:16:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被吃掉吧  被吃掉吧  被吃掉吧  被吃掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.23,0:16:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.72,0:16:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.60,0:16:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.72,0:16:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是我之前驱除掉的\N那纸面妖怪的碎片还粘在衣服上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.24,0:16:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是妖怪但这是由人所创造的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.55,0:16:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由人…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.05,0:16:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用纸做出能够收集妖气的面
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.58,0:16:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以收集来的妖气汇成身体成为人偶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.34,0:16:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计是受到你和我的妖气影响而复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.95,0:16:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是我还是最高级的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.41,0:16:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人所创造出来的妖怪  正是因此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.18,0:16:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才会从那妖怪身上感受到恶意吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.85,0:17:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.41,0:17:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨夜外出调查还没回来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.66,0:17:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说通宵了？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.21,0:17:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何为了妖怪这般付出…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.41,0:17:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己不也是为了妖怪在东奔西走
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.01,0:17:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是名取他…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.51,0:17:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取大概是觉得是自己打草惊蛇了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.73,0:17:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇…难道说指的是的场
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.79,0:17:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.36,0:17:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  要抽身就只有现在了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.33,0:17:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是妖怪还能保得住你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.73,0:17:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对手若是人类的话就另当别论
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.46,0:17:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是的场那小子  可是相当棘手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.57,0:17:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.33,0:17:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.80,0:17:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  已经来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.74,0:17:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.13,0:17:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没睡过吧  稍微休息下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.32,0:17:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.97,0:17:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彻夜未眠也不会影响我这优雅的笑颜
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.45,0:17:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就放心好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.19,0:17:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这简直就是在通宵过后才会有的不正常发言啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.17,0:18:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  我怎么听起来就跟平常一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.06,0:18:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调查了事件发生地  发现是渐渐从西向东走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.02,0:18:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而事件最初的发生地是在这
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.05,0:18:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种地方竟然有村落
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.08,0:18:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微去打听一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.41,0:18:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是名取先生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.49,0:18:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都很关注你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.91,0:18:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.14,0:18:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.49,0:18:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  就在那
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.55,0:18:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  快跑啊  没用的家伙们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.04,0:18:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲向乌冬面
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.53,0:18:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清汤乌冬面  三份
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.60,0:18:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.37,0:18:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有哦  这附近有没有什么特别的传言呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.68,0:18:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别的传言？ 指的是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.37,0:18:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比方说有怪物出没的地方什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.51,0:18:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的陌生人在附近转悠什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.19,0:18:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.92,0:18:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了…除开这个人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.67,0:19:03.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到奇怪的人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.49,0:19:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这屋后的旅馆里住着一名半边脸被长发遮住的客人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.70,0:19:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.13,0:19:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然就察觉到了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.10,0:19:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵咪偶尔也有一手嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.34,0:19:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫做偶尔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.95,0:19:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  感觉过于容易了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.16,0:19:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉像是陷阱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.45,0:19:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实啊  但是…总觉有些…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.39,0:19:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…总之去看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.38,0:19:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实住着这样的客人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.85,0:19:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.55,0:19:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在找离家出走中的弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.90,0:19:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以请务必对我们的事保密
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.61,0:19:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.38,0:19:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请稍等片刻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.89,0:19:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  您好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.45,0:20:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  什么  山崩
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.26,0:20:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果  我和名取只能等道路恢复畅通才能回去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.58,0:20:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  只能在这里借住一宿了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.34,0:20:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.34,0:20:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天就能回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.36,0:20:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只好在貌似住着的场的小旅馆里借宿一宿
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.19,0:20:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取他好慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.82,0:20:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不好被的场给抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.25,0:20:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉到有相当糟糕的气息在聚集
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.60,0:20:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是去哪呢  对手可是的场
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.49,0:20:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那花拳绣腿哪有可能起得了作用
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.81,0:20:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.70,0:20:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我替你去看看好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.01,0:20:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以在我回来之前
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.40,0:20:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是谁都别开门
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.04,0:20:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  老师您也多加小心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.36,0:20:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这门到底怎么搞得
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.26,0:21:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果最没用的还是我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.31,0:21:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚的那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.82,0:21:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.17,0:21:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.74,0:21:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底打算做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.23,0:21:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转转悠悠的真碍眼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.29,0:21:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再这样死缠不休的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.90,0:21:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了的场我就拿你的血做供品了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.05,0:21:25.50,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的场的…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.94,0:21:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做供品？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.12,0:21:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.85,0:21:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你的妖力还挺强的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.16,0:21:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽不知你是何来历
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.01,0:21:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对那些只尝过下级血的妖怪来说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.82,0:21:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你算是美味的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.24,0:21:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美味？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.41,0:21:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底打算做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.43,0:21:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么不好意思我来取你的血了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.57,0:21:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我住手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.35,0:21:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是想要妖力强大的家伙的血
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.08,0:22:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师和名取该会很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.62,0:22:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又见面了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.01,0:22:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天猫咪没跟着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.31,0:22:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住他
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.67,0:24:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了  夏目不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.38,0:24:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪你磨磨蹭蹭的  要怎么负责啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.88,0:24:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不也是只是坐在别人身上啥事都不做
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.30,0:24:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真好意思说
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.41,0:24:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  顺便也替你换个脑袋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.99,0:24:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  这次容我暂借夏目君一用
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.19,0:24:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失策啊
