[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.65,0:02:08.65,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1}虚伪的友人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.92,0:24:15.96,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1\pos(205,296)}年幼时光
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}なくした温もりを一つ一つ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色取り取りの君のカケラは　笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出の作り方も　まるでうまくならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れに　タダ身を任せて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこに行けばいい　この闇の先でまだ
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな　君のカケラ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}なくした温もりを一つ一つ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色取り取りの君のカケラは　笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出の作り方も　まるでうまくならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れに　タダ身を任せて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこに行けばいい　この闇の先でまだ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな　君のカケラ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.56,0:01:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋糕吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.82,0:01:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是滋先生的生日呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.31,0:01:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志  回来的时候能顺便买来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.16,0:01:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要什么样的蛋糕？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.25,0:01:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢  因为是生日就买草莓奶油蛋糕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.90,0:01:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买三个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.52,0:01:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.31,0:01:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要四个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.00,0:01:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪可不能吃甜食哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.21,0:01:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是猫咪！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.34,0:01:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是深爱着甜食的招财猫！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.70,0:02:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些吵嚷却也平静的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.10,0:02:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个甜点师在法国修行过
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.37,0:02:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做的东西相当好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.70,0:02:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.24,0:02:19.04,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\an4\fs30\b0\shad0\1c&H868686&\bord0\pos(154,90)}河
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.24,0:02:19.04,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\an4\fs30\b0\shad0\1c&H868686&\bord0\pos(240,185)}超市
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.24,0:02:19.04,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\an4\fs30\b0\shad0\1c&H868686&\bord0\pos(540,220)}可爱的森林
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.61,0:02:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱的森林？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.23,0:02:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇特的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.49,0:02:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是北本家附近的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.10,0:02:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.59,0:02:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确是和名字完全相符的可爱店铺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.76,0:02:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.22,0:02:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有男生的话很难进去的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.14,0:02:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了  对我来说难度太大了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.01,0:02:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平常就抱着猫咪的你有什么好害臊的？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.26,0:02:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.62,0:02:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让滋先生他们吃到好吃的蛋糕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.39,0:02:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.26,0:02:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.39,0:03:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是夏目贵志吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.12,0:03:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于找到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.83,0:03:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.47,0:03:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目的熟人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.00,0:03:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一带不常见的校服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.99,0:03:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.24,0:03:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你原来在这里交到朋友了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.49,0:03:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你是什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.39,0:03:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  抱歉  我是榊西高中的柴田
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.90,0:03:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和夏目同一个小学的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.19,0:03:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.09,0:03:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.26,0:03:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是记得很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.17,0:03:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是个奇人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.21,0:03:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能稍微陪我走一趟吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.26,0:03:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.98,0:03:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这里讲也没关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.40,0:03:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  西村  北本  回头见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.72,0:03:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.06,0:03:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想带我去哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.92,0:04:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊  以前说过一些奇怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.50,0:04:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是能看见一些大家看不到的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.53,0:04:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.52,0:04:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.45,0:04:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙又在说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.74,0:04:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人会传染的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.94,0:04:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗子…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.40,0:04:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.81,0:04:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脸色都变了  是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.19,0:04:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是些孩提时的玩笑  有什么好当真的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.82,0:04:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.09,0:04:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还会去见你的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.46,0:04:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那些事是真的  所以不想被现在的朋友知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.36,0:04:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我撒谎的技术真是越来越差了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.88,0:04:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  你带钱了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.01,0:05:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你究竟是想去哪…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.73,0:05:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦死了  闭上嘴跟我走就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.47,0:05:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好多蚊子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.65,0:05:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么非要到这种地方来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.86,0:05:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘  她来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.31,0:05:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.38,0:05:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.27,0:05:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.46,0:05:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样的女孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.99,0:05:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通的长发女高中生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.12,0:05:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.64,0:05:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是人类吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.51,0:05:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要笑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.47,0:05:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的话能看得出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.06,0:05:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真的是不是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.48,0:05:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么看都是一个普通人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.39,0:05:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要问这种事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.03,0:05:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴田
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.97,0:05:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.12,0:06:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种地方做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.50,0:06:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是你的朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.05,0:06:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  他是夏目  我以前的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.60,0:06:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.51,0:06:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你配合我一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.73,0:06:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们感情真好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.53,0:06:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之后
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.60,0:06:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个叫村崎的女孩和柴田聊了一会儿便回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.59,0:06:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人关系非常亲密
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.01,0:06:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴田似乎喜欢那女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.05,0:06:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽说些奇怪的话  真是对不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.56,0:06:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是帮了大忙了  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.64,0:06:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟是怎么回事  你把那女孩当做妖怪了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.94,0:06:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是有些奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.24,0:06:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  你是不是觉得我很傻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.24,0:06:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是  我并没有觉得你傻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.71,0:07:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  都已经日落了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.67,0:07:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不赶快的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.81,0:07:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.74,0:07:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋糕！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.00,0:07:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  什么事情啊  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.60,0:07:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  好漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.21,0:07:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个蛋糕可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.45,0:07:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.32,0:07:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后在附近找了许多蛋糕店
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.49,0:07:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但奶油蛋糕都卖完了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.00,0:07:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果只有我一个人的话可能会找不到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.18,0:07:31.46,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.97,0:07:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了柴田帮我一起找
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.73,0:07:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.05,0:07:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志买过来的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.00,0:07:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.54,0:07:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.62,0:07:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜点和盐烤的东西混着吃  味道还真特别
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.87,0:07:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  再去给我烤一根来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.61,0:07:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,累死了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.92,0:08:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了  眼睛都睁不开来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.63,0:08:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪里了  又沾到妖怪的气味了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.44,0:08:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪？不  那是一个女孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.17,0:08:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？这里是哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.21,0:08:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个女孩  在吃些什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.10,0:08:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…柴田！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.40,0:08:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么又来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.78,0:08:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪老师你说了些奇怪的话  让我很在意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.86,0:08:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概在这附近吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.66,0:08:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.45,0:08:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天没有注意到  这公园还真是诡异啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.40,0:08:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.36,0:09:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻起来好像很好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.70,0:09:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然是妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.18,0:09:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢  就算不是那个家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.64,0:09:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了你也行啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.35,0:09:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  被白色肥猪一样的东西咬了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.00,0:09:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.46,0:09:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.81,0:09:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的人类孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.57,0:09:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果暴露了我的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.05,0:09:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追到天涯海角我也要把你吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.58,0:09:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别给我嚣张了  这家伙可是我的储备粮啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.06,0:10:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是这附近的花木幻化而成的妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.14,0:10:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扮成人的样子是准备骗了人类再把他们吃掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.56,0:10:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么柴田…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.68,0:10:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在被骗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.82,0:10:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贪婪的妖怪很容易露出破绽
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.36,0:10:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那小子大概也感觉出她和普通人有些不同
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.43,0:10:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才来找你商量的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.18,0:10:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了吗  校门口那里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.19,0:10:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了  是在等谁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.79,0:10:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我们学校的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.52,0:10:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴田
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.86,0:10:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.77,0:10:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里做什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.47,0:10:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好丑的肥猫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.94,0:10:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去去  一边去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.13,0:10:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这只丑肥猫
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.92,0:10:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  柴田  这只丑肥猫是我家的猫…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.47,0:11:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特意来我这  有什么事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.41,0:11:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是关于这之前的那个女生…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.74,0:11:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真是很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.58,0:11:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你做了些奇怪的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.66,0:11:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在那个公园遇见她的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.23,0:11:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初是在我一个人闲逛的时候出现的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.48,0:11:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后我便常常跑去见她
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.05,0:11:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是住址电话  甚至连学校都不跟我说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.40,0:11:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为她讨厌我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.43,0:11:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那眼神果然还是喜欢我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.87,0:11:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  柴田
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.97,0:11:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女孩…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.43,0:11:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很冷…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.75,0:11:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是平常说话的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.18,0:11:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是在牵着她的手看花朵和落日的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.56,0:11:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的手一直是那么的冰冷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.53,0:11:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚遇见她的时候也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.53,0:12:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我是妖怪的话你会怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.96,0:12:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很傻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.86,0:12:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我还是非常地不安
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.54,0:12:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就想到了你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.97,0:12:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴田  那女孩…不是人类…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.92,0:12:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不可以和那女孩…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.08,0:12:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.78,0:12:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我弄错了  那女孩不是人类…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.68,0:12:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那究竟是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.35,0:12:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这之前不是说她就是普通的女孩吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.12,0:12:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.43,0:12:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女孩…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.79,0:12:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  给我闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.03,0:12:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴田
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.30,0:12:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.68,0:12:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然是个大骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.76,0:13:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.71,0:13:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.31,0:13:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便现在被当作骗子也不能继续在这伤心了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.45,0:13:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振作起来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.16,0:13:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽全力做好…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.95,0:13:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心吧  这些天她是不会出现的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.92,0:13:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  你不知道下手轻重吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.11,0:13:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说过叫你不要随便进去的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.84,0:13:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天没有蛋糕吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.45,0:13:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.74,0:13:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个…那妖怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.56,0:13:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说她不会出现  是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.94,0:13:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是像我这般高级的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.23,0:13:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不过是小角色
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.49,0:13:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要再次以人形显现估计需要三天左右
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.83,0:13:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天…也就是说还有时间
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.56,0:13:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.15,0:13:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经回去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.95,0:13:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  从后门走的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.74,0:13:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.02,0:13:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经替你说了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.38,0:14:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.96,0:14:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是真的没关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.14,0:14:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来相当担心柴田你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.50,0:14:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是好好聊一下比较好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.84,0:14:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是朋友吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.25,0:14:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是…那家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.20,0:14:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前不被人所信任还一直被欺负
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.41,0:14:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底打算怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.07,0:14:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,监视那只妖怪不让柴田去见她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.33,0:14:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.15,0:14:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有义务要为那种小鬼做到这地步吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.83,0:14:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是个讨厌的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.37,0:14:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不是个坏家伙  大概…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.78,0:14:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没辙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.06,0:14:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就用蛋糕和鱿鱼干作为这次的报酬吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.83,0:14:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个味道…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.82,0:14:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.99,0:14:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.71,0:14:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特意过来让我吃掉的么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.64,0:14:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天傍晚我已经告诉柴田你不是人类了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.89,0:15:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是等着吃掉他  他也不会来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.72,0:15:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该放弃他了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.22,0:15:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.86,0:15:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.05,0:15:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就是没能让他相信你咯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.84,0:15:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果柴田相信你的话那么一切就该结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.69,0:15:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.41,0:15:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为没有被接受才会想做点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.53,0:15:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就这样若无其事地过来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.90,0:15:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.36,0:15:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  在哪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.67,0:15:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快放手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.69,0:15:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种小角色只要我把她吃了就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.50,0:15:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.91,0:15:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.83,0:15:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能否再等我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.14,0:15:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底该怎么办  再等等
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.94,0:15:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对柴田来说她很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.81,0:15:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你这滥好人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.87,0:15:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是让她给跑掉了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.52,0:15:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快追
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.35,0:16:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掉下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.00,0:16:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是变虚弱了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.42,0:16:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变虚弱了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.34,0:16:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就说她熬不久了才不去管她的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.81,0:16:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.48,0:16:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.94,0:16:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.45,0:16:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是山藤？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.88,0:16:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.92,0:16:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经醒来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.14,0:16:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.65,0:16:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别碰我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.94,0:16:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,低等的人类  如果你触碰到我  便吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.42,0:16:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了以后会感觉好一些吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.98,0:16:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.46,0:16:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过比起坐等消失来说还不如吃些人类
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.96,0:16:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说维持着人类外形
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.79,0:16:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是力量早就衰弱了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.50,0:16:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在我疲惫不堪盘坐休息时
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.63,0:17:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴田便过来找你说话了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.88,0:17:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想着这猎物不错
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.43,0:17:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是累得连吃掉他的力气都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.88,0:17:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说好三天后再相见
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.88,0:17:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天后那个笨蛋人类乖乖地来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.83,0:17:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那家伙不但神采奕奕还非常地话多
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.93,0:17:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连吃掉他的机会都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.61,0:17:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以又约好再见面
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.99,0:17:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是这般…无论见了多少次面
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.10,0:17:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.75,0:17:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有吃掉他的空闲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.87,0:17:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实昨晚柴田来过了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.22,0:17:44.09,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.26,0:17:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.82,0:17:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎  你在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.02,0:17:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我无法维持人类的外形
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.55,0:17:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.80,0:17:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.00,0:17:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  这个时间来…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.16,0:18:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是有妖怪出现了怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.76,0:18:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.64,0:18:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  要不要出来散个步
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.73,0:18:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前提到的那条河边上的山丘
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.95,0:18:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.60,0:18:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是今天不太舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.65,0:18:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能推到其他的日子？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.12,0:18:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.54,0:18:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约好了  村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.00,0:18:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  约好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.43,0:18:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候柴田应该已经知晓我的真身了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.68,0:18:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.61,0:18:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离开他  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.91,0:18:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰到她可是会被吃掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.83,0:18:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是想要那么做
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.77,0:18:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来办不到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.69,0:18:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙是柴田的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.84,0:18:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是吃掉了的话肯定会被他讨厌的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.10,0:18:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持下…我这就去抓鱼…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.19,0:18:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.72,0:19:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴田
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.80,0:19:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.07,0:19:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并非不相信你所说的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.79,0:19:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是现在…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.94,0:19:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是村崎给你的信
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.12,0:19:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎  你见到她了？她在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.60,0:19:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别罗嗦了  快收下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.33,0:19:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能否替我将这个交给柴田？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.18,0:19:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试着写了封信
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.09,0:19:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见面的话会有留恋
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.16,0:19:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是离别的赠言和我的内心所想
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.34,0:19:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为无缘无故被牵连进来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.13,0:19:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为我说你是骗子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.46,0:19:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是我没有相信你所说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.73,0:19:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会是这种涂鸦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.23,0:19:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个文字
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.90,0:19:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经够了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.72,0:19:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我错了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.65,0:19:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.81,0:19:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不相信我也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.55,0:20:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是只有这封信请收下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.45,0:20:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.97,0:20:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.05,0:20:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴田
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.75,0:20:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要见到村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.61,0:20:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边走
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.16,0:20:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村崎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.14,0:20:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以来这里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.67,0:20:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是都写了我要去远方所以见不着面了么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.81,0:20:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…我们约好了的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.82,0:20:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带我走吧  柴田  就像以前一样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.23,0:20:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.94,0:20:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴田
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.78,0:21:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.63,0:21:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柴田
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.55,0:21:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.05,0:21:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.13,0:21:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我说出了那么过分的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.30,0:21:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还一直陪我到最后
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.12,0:21:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.88,0:21:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样  村崎去了遥远的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.98,0:21:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好凉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.49,0:22:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.41,0:22:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个事情不准跟其他人说
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.52,0:22:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.08,0:22:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哭了的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.47,0:22:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.44,0:22:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛  这个答复  超级拽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.00,0:22:20.21,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 从一开始柴田你就…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.98,0:22:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从孩提时代起就很想要个朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.72,0:22:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是人还是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.49,0:22:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是如此的温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.05,0:22:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照亮着我的内心
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.47,0:24:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总是孤单一人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.08,0:24:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总是独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.14,0:24:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个孩子总是满目落寞
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.85,0:24:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时的我还不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.84,0:24:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是谁的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.16,0:24:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连我自己的也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.52,0:24:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是想喝酒想得不行了
