[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.42,0:03:09.38,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0002,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}被供奉的神灵
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.92,0:24:15.98,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\pos(238,296)}一张照片
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだうしろ姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}やさしさで胸がいたくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々がいとおしくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音(ね)に　夕闇に　懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも一緒だよ、と　叶わぬことくり返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}ぬくもりはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}あざやかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来にかえながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだうしろ姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}やさしさで胸がいたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々がいとおしくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音(ね)に　夕闇に　懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも一緒だよ、と　叶わぬことくり返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}ぬくもりはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}あざやかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来にかえながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下  回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离  辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下  回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离  辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.66,0:01:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.93,0:01:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.00,0:01:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大事不妙了  这不是丰月大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.42,0:01:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  闯大祸了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.76,0:01:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下  好像有点奇怪  那真是丰月大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.84,0:02:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹿角假面  没有错
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.82,0:02:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  微微有些人类的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.03,0:02:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类?!  怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.94,0:02:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说人类在糊弄我们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.40,0:02:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫醒他确认一下
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.28,0:02:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无礼之徒！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.02,0:02:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明知我是丰月神还如此野蛮
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.25,0:02:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是得到了不月神的认可吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.97,0:02:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是丰月大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.85,0:02:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若真是丰月大人  请让我们一睹尊容
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.77,0:02:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.87,0:02:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.23,0:02:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓起来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.03,0:02:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摘下假面
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.47,0:02:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃走了  快追！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.60,0:02:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下  人类能操控那般的妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.79,0:02:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么真的是丰月大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.48,0:02:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是确实有人类的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.24,0:03:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.26,0:03:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不月大人  那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.00,0:03:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.59,0:03:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事  只是肩膀擦伤
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.16,0:03:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了柊没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.80,0:03:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找个地方休息一下就会醒来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.93,0:03:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  那到刚才那栋宅邸里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.41,0:03:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当我是出租车吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.21,0:03:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  放下柊之后再去河边搜索一次
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.55,0:03:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.87,0:03:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被河水冲走的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.83,0:03:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到了一丝气息
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.31,0:03:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…也许就是丰月神
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.56,0:03:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓紧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.69,0:03:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上前去会合
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.69,0:03:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.70,0:04:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的同伴…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.93,0:04:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有大碍
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.57,0:04:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.59,0:04:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.17,0:04:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的同伴无恙真是万幸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.48,0:04:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请赶快去找丰月大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.51,0:04:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁夏目不在我有一事想要确认
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.45,0:04:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.92,0:04:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月神真的是被封印了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.16,0:04:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您这是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.86,0:04:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是什么时候被封印的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.27,0:04:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待到如此紧要关头才来拜托夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.54,0:04:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更早行动不也是可能的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.51,0:04:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用他强大的妖力和心地善良
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.29,0:04:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该不会是在图谋什么坏事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.96,0:04:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非丰月神其实早就不在了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.84,0:05:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时光流逝所受信奉渐衰而力量减弱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.31,0:05:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就被驱妖人所退治了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.20,0:05:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是如黑衣众所说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.13,0:05:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厌倦了照料这片土地和你们而离开了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.89,0:05:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苦恼于被抛弃了的你们
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.27,0:05:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是打算让夏目成为真正的丰月神
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.93,0:05:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  这真是个好主意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.51,0:05:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.64,0:05:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了  开个玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.00,0:05:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是丰月大人是真的被封印起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.63,0:05:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是三年前的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.58,0:05:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.30,0:05:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拖到这种时候是因为我等误会了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.18,0:05:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,误会了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.81,0:05:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在月分祭上获胜的神灵会住进深山里的祠堂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.67,0:06:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守护着整座山和村庄
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.02,0:06:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实人们不再信奉神灵
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.28,0:06:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不难猜测其每日都是无聊中度过
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.82,0:06:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那时  一名不谙世事的驱妖人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.63,0:06:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入了这片妖怪密布的森林之中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.23,0:06:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而将偶遇的丰月大人封印了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.58,0:06:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许只是为了试试身手而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.51,0:06:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等四处寻找封印的石头
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.16,0:06:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那不过是个低级的驱妖人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.76,0:06:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印也只是个小把戏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.52,0:06:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位大人应该能解开那种封印才对
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.48,0:06:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此我等以为大人是厌倦了祠堂里的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.05,0:06:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想在封印中暂做休息
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.03,0:06:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待到欢愉的祭典来临之际定会再现身
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.47,0:07:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我等一边保护祠堂一边等候着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.19,0:07:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在丰月大人复出之后就想说以此次祭典为终
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.12,0:07:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等使命结束了我们就再次踏上旅程
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.78,0:07:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许正如您所说的  可能早就解除了封印
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.75,0:07:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许早就离开了这片土地
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.35,0:07:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…可是也不一定就离开了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.70,0:07:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许封印比想象中更坚固
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.46,0:07:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他正等着你们的救援
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.41,0:07:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真的是会丢下你们离开的主人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.60,0:07:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若一旦决意要追随他的话  就要相信你的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.93,0:07:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.44,0:08:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.20,0:08:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.58,0:08:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她暂时安心地休息一会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.70,0:08:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这附近吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.35,0:08:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.16,0:08:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在河底吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.31,0:08:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我想应该没有掉进河里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.09,0:08:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目真是厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.74,0:08:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被河水冲走的时候也能感受到气息
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是驱妖人的话就像是嗅到钱的气味一般吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.15,0:08:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.66,0:08:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想要能干的助手啊  但也不想失去重要的友人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.01,0:08:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.55,0:08:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是那个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.96,0:08:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个吗  真难办啊  那种地方没法下去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.18,0:08:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的  也许老师可以
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.73,0:08:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.16,0:08:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  你来看一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.33,0:09:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然有妖怪在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.04,0:09:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂时撤离
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.86,0:09:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真难办啊  根本无法接近
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.61,0:09:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够抵御一次妖怪的獠牙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.16,0:09:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏这才得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.53,0:09:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了夏目  我想到一个好主意
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.76,0:09:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把那家伙吃了  你把它的头拿回去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.57,0:09:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都会膜拜你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.76,0:09:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的神明可不妙啊  会被拒之千里的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.78,0:09:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我天职  改不回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.24,0:09:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来即便是找到丰月神
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.53,0:09:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但让不月神抢先抓住妖怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.16,0:09:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我们输
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.92,0:09:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正只要是你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.98,0:09:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假若丰月神输了就毫无顾忌的寻求我的帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.03,0:09:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就算是本大爷我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.01,0:09:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若与神明作对也是会遭到报应的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.42,0:10:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实如此
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.23,0:10:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.80,0:10:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说猎捕回去的方法并非唯一
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.28,0:10:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有为封印不月神而事先准备好的咒术同瓶子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.54,0:10:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这收押妖怪后带去的话总比只有头要强
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.08,0:10:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.91,0:10:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.33,0:10:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.11,0:10:36.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.14,0:10:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覆盖亘古之地的有灵之物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.50,0:10:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,束缚此物以得安宁
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.29,0:10:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请现形
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.55,0:11:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.31,0:11:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.92,0:11:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.09,0:11:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生  谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.49,0:11:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来一定…一定能成功
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.59,0:11:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也要谢谢猫咪老师借予我妖力…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.59,0:11:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.77,0:11:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂在那里  快点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.89,0:11:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的光是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.48,0:11:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有不祥的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.42,0:11:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从哪传来的…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.24,0:12:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  拿着瓶子去三隅之原
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.66,0:12:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来拖住他们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.51,0:12:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.59,0:12:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽力前去刚才的悬崖那把丰月神找出来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.17,0:12:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的哦  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.91,0:12:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都已经努力到这份上了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.94,0:12:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差一点点…一定可以成功的  快去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.95,0:12:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  名取先生也请小心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.98,0:12:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  刚才有什么东西从那里跳出去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.45,0:12:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你过去的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.03,0:12:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.14,0:12:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类为什么会出现在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.15,0:12:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在策划什么阴谋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.04,0:12:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要祛除不月神吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.94,0:12:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说祛除神灵有些棘手  和你们玩玩倒是可以
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.77,0:12:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.37,0:12:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人都好慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.27,0:13:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去岂不是分不出胜负了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.77,0:13:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  快点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.40,0:13:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若如流传所述
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.52,0:13:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不月神嬴了的话这座山就会荒芜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.68,0:13:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太可怕了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.16,0:13:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.04,0:13:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟目前为止丰月神都没有输过
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.55,0:13:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽说如此
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.02,0:13:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.69,0:13:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.47,0:13:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哪一位？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.46,0:13:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鹿角的头冠  是丰月神大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.71,0:13:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了哦  是丰月神大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.22,0:13:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月神大人的样子有点奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.31,0:13:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全身脏兮兮的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.68,0:14:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那简直像是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.14,0:14:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月我…先回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.81,0:14:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  先出示猎物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.16,0:14:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如假包换
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.18,0:14:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜者  丰月神
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.78,0:15:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.43,0:15:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.30,0:15:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不月神大人他…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.34,0:15:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不月神大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.42,0:15:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…不是丰月
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.52,0:15:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.43,0:15:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.15,0:15:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是人类的孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.83,0:15:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.96,0:15:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们人类心血来潮想要战胜我们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.76,0:15:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不久又驱逐我们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.16,0:15:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅如此  该不会是祛除了丰月吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.55,0:15:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.03,0:16:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是本大爷我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.17,0:16:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若与神明作对也是会遭到报应的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.09,0:16:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.55,0:16:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜生  如此无礼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.76,0:16:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.61,0:16:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.91,0:16:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  拿着这个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.34,0:16:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目的话…一定可以解开这个封印
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.80,0:16:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是…丰月神
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.45,0:16:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月神  请醒醒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.60,0:17:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是…丰月神的记忆？ 是在做梦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.32,0:17:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比想象中人还要少的小型祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.56,0:17:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…但是…很温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.03,0:17:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承蒙照顾了  人类的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.94,0:17:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何这般表情？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.26,0:17:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.78,0:17:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如你所想
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.96,0:17:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错…我的力量几乎已经枯竭了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.42,0:17:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连那样的封印都解除不了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.26,0:17:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说要在祭典上取胜了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.18,0:17:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连保护这座山和森林的力量都…早就没有了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.97,0:17:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此…那么就结束这个祭典了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.63,0:17:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  就此结束吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.28,0:18:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话  我们就毫无理由再来这座山了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.94,0:18:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留在这枯竭是你的自由…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.96,0:18:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愿否同我一起离去？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.15,0:18:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不月…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.27,0:18:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧  丰月大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.65,0:18:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定会保护您的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.71,0:18:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  来 去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.40,0:18:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人  谢谢您
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.56,0:18:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.82,0:18:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.00,0:18:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先不要急着动身
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.03,0:18:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月神大人他们…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.44,0:18:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.76,0:19:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是丰月神和不月神的迁徙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.15,0:19:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.28,0:19:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个一定是神灵
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.91,0:19:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很不可思议呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.27,0:19:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看似对立的两列队伍
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.91,0:19:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在却闪耀着同样的光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.21,0:19:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失在同样遥远的天空中
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.11,0:19:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.71,0:19:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  做到了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.09,0:19:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  名取先生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.61,0:19:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取先生能来真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.91,0:19:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有我一个人肯定无法取胜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.15,0:19:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人的话  一定…办不到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.74,0:20:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.30,0:20:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错呢  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.24,0:20:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样  月分祭落下了帷幕
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.19,0:20:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我因为疲劳  睡了几天几夜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.37,0:20:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被老师喋喋不休地抱怨个不停
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.53,0:20:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  你这个家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.11,0:20:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是去插手一些无聊的事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.40,0:20:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束后因为疲劳竟然还发烧了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.08,0:20:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师…你好重…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.48,0:20:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.15,0:20:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是春天的风
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.45,0:20:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等退了烧…偶尔我也去见一下名取先生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.43,0:20:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  贵志君  已经没事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.52,0:21:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我去散散步
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.36,0:21:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太勉强哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.35,0:21:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.38,0:21:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有时依旧会因为想法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.76,0:21:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和行为不同而犹豫不决
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.89,0:21:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也感觉正因为不同才能互补
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.43,0:21:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三隅的妖怪们好像是要继续保护丰月神的祠堂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.70,0:21:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.98,0:21:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名取不用祛除神灵而成功稳住局面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.34,0:21:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并未驱灵反而还提升了驱妖师的名望
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.74,0:21:38.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那臭小子还真能算计啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.58,0:21:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤势…已经好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.24,0:21:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  不是什么很重的伤
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.41,0:21:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.17,0:21:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是你帮我画的符咒…起作用了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.06,0:21:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那本来就是柊替我画的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.86,0:21:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  那个完全照描也起作用吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.87,0:22:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊  刚才的道谢我收回
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.17,0:22:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  来了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.87,0:22:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.42,0:22:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有想问的和想说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.41,0:22:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来自己去问吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.81,0:22:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.46,0:22:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  抱歉  等很久了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.53,0:24:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在看什么  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.75,0:24:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母的相片
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.49,0:24:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然还有这种东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.32,0:24:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候拼命地想要忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.10,0:24:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  你看  没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.80,0:24:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是一味地逞强  会变成豆芽哦
