[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes



[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.4,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H55C5DECA,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.1,1.5,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,MS Gothic,14,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,9,15,15,9,1
Style: EDch,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00000000,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0,1,15,15,9,1
Style: EDjpb,MS Gothic,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,9,16,15,10,1
Style: EDchb,方正兰亭黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EEEEEE,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,16,15,8,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.37,0:03:03.38,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur2\shad2\bord1}现影之物
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.05,0:24:16.02,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1\pos(177,296)}归宿
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 1,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 1,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 1,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 1,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}答えのない日々に　溜め息漏らすたび
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}本当の僕はもう　見えなくなちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}耳を澄ましても　聞こえない君の声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}追い駆けて　今日も歩き続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}伝えられずにいった思いは　時を経て蛹になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}羽広げ　やがて飛び立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}忘れない大切な　ひとつ　ひとつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}届くかなこの思い　どうか　いつか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}ちっぽけなこの僕にできること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}少しずつでも伝えてみたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:22.60,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}在未知的每一天里  每当我唉声叹气的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.82,0:00:29.89,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}我便无法看清真实的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.09,0:00:37.03,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}就算去努力倾听  也无法听见你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.33,0:00:44.00,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}迈开步伐  今天也在继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:51.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法向你传达的思念  日久便化作虫蛹尘封了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.85,0:00:59.35,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}张开翅膀  定将高飞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.77,0:01:06.76,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}无法忘却的那一个又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.99,0:01:14.25,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}或许会传达给你的这份思念  是怎么样的  又会在何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:20.57,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}小小的我也有可以办到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.87,0:01:29.50,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur5}想要一点点的传达给你
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}失くした温もりをひとつひとつ並べて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}色とりどりの君の欠片は笑った顔を描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}思い出のつくりかたも　まるで上手くならないままに
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}足早に過ぎる時の流れにただ身をまかせて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}どこへ行けばいい　この闇の先でまた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}何度さよなら言えばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}深い心の奥で光った
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}遥かな君の欠片
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 1,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 1,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 1,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:42.76,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}将失去的温暖一片片拼凑起立
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.85,0:22:56.37,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}你那五彩斑斓的碎片描绘着笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:10.27,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}还是无法用自己的手去制造回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.08,0:23:25.81,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}只能置身于时间的洪流之中随它摇曳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.81,0:23:32.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}该去何方  这黑暗的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.67,0:23:38.71,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}要说多少次的再见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:45.94,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}在内心深处闪烁出光芒的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:53.21,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\be1\blur3}是你那遥远的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.44,0:01:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼被妖怪附身
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.23,0:01:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是在找齐镜子的碎片之前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.96,0:01:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不打算离开
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.98,0:01:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不时刻关注着田沼的话让人担心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.56,0:01:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是决定借宿他家了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.94,0:01:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你家长呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.24,0:01:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸又出差了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.04,0:01:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.19,0:02:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  田沼小子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.75,0:02:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那栗子  给我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.98,0:02:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.27,0:02:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说白天收集齐的镜子的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.94,0:02:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经收集了多少了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.40,0:02:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么多  能看见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.96,0:02:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目真了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.26,0:02:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只知道那里有些什么而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.07,0:02:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.98,0:02:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.50,0:02:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别那么随心所欲地拿出来玩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.59,0:02:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是别随随便便地利用田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.45,0:02:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是  把我的栗子还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.95,0:02:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  把我的栗子还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.81,0:02:41.50,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,栗子  栗子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.75,0:02:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我被附身的话或许更好一些吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.50,0:02:44.05,small,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,栗子  喂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.28,0:02:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  镜子跑进眼睛里了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.11,0:02:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.41,0:02:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镜子自身会想要复原
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.23,0:02:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因如此才会产生共鸣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.07,0:02:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要求你去拾起它
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.18,0:02:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧收集齐也就完事了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.88,0:03:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊  夏目你偶尔会遇到这种事情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.79,0:03:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.65,0:03:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被妖怪拜托去做什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.74,0:03:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是偶尔是经常
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.36,0:03:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.14,0:03:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.60,0:03:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙是滥好人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.11,0:03:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法无视妖怪们的请求的性格
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.41,0:03:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明拒绝就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.42,0:03:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.76,0:03:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.95,0:03:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.90,0:03:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.37,0:03:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永别了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.22,0:03:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.94,0:04:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是…附在田沼身上的妖怪的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.42,0:04:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别过来是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.08,0:04:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了什么对不起你的事情了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.29,0:04:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  就别再靠近我了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.25,0:04:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.72,0:04:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永别了  永别
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.58,0:04:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你偷窥我的梦了  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.01,0:04:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那就是你所寻找的友人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.37,0:04:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个妖怪好像重病在身
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.65,0:04:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有铜镜的话就能治好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.21,0:04:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那病相当麻烦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.87,0:04:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有…有没有能够救助他的办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.87,0:05:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要治愈那家伙的疾病吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.28,0:05:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.53,0:05:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是没有办法
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.36,0:05:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.94,0:05:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  但是啊  不费尽周折可是到不了手的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.51,0:05:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很辛苦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.57,0:05:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很冷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.88,0:05:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息下就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.78,0:05:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们就来替你取暖
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.09,0:05:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你滚烫的热水
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.07,0:06:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们的手心之中沉睡就好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.87,0:06:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何如此执着
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.85,0:06:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说你想要拿走我们的镜子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.39,0:06:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休想得逞
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.50,0:06:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休想得逞
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.70,0:06:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休想得逞…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.40,0:06:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真愚蠢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.86,0:07:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里可没有哟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.68,0:07:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被糊弄了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.67,0:07:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.75,0:07:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.92,0:07:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的太阳升起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.25,0:07:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的镜子就要现形了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.77,0:07:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.73,0:07:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪？ 你在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.40,0:07:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到能够医治你疾病的办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.44,0:07:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.85,0:08:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼  你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.94,0:08:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我难道又…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.82,0:08:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那声响是从正殿那边传来的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.55,0:08:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小偷…不太可能吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.31,0:08:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从外面打破的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.42,0:08:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个时节外面的野熊也会有些恶作剧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.53,0:08:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.40,0:08:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.89,0:08:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能够看见那家伙所看到的东西的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.12,0:08:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许也就能够理解他到底想要做什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.92,0:08:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.95,0:08:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能做得到么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.83,0:08:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为借我身体一用的谢礼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.16,0:08:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借你我的眼睛一用也无妨
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.86,0:08:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.67,0:08:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.62,0:08:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.02,0:08:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目他能看到这种东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.09,0:09:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.56,0:09:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在学校四处游荡的那个大锤妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.29,0:09:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目他所看到的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.05,0:09:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有这种东西四处飘荡的世界吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.56,0:09:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼你也能够看到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.23,0:09:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她把眼睛借给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.46,0:09:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了  镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.84,0:09:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毁掉你  然后拿出它
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.84,0:10:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这小角色竟敢向我的镜子出手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.75,0:10:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少在这挡道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.09,0:10:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我退下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.56,0:10:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田…田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.34,0:10:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.04,0:10:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.98,0:10:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我适可而止点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.62,0:10:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让田沼看见妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.84,0:10:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.80,0:10:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但让田沼遭受这样的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.75,0:10:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镜子很重要的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.78,0:10:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有更重要的朋友在吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.21,0:10:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我而言田沼是最重要的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.61,0:10:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再让他这么乱来的话  我绝对不原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.42,0:10:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离开田沼附到我身上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.40,0:10:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会帮助你去找镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.27,0:10:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开田沼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.92,0:10:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他自己想要看见妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.29,0:11:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有关妖怪的事情你基本上闭口不谈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.41,0:11:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是没有必要说出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.68,0:11:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是你太善良了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.14,0:11:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便明白是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.32,0:11:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你若不说出来的话  我们还是什么都不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.84,0:11:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的事情仍旧不明不白
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.59,0:11:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明就在身边却仍旧不知晓
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.26,0:11:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的朋友也什么都没告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.50,0:11:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都不说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.46,0:11:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身负重病也不坦白
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.25,0:11:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了不传染给我而离开了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.34,0:11:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些随着风声传进我耳里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.50,0:11:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然跟我说了也改变不了什么事实
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.88,0:12:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后我费尽心思才弄到手的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.62,0:12:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够根除疾病的镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.60,0:12:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后就是找到他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.28,0:12:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  镜子啊  不赶紧找齐它的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.42,0:12:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.15,0:12:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不赶紧找到的话就为时已晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.48,0:12:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不住了  人类之子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.05,0:12:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的我已用尽全力停留在这个身体中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.48,0:12:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不住了  人类之子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.11,0:12:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.04,0:12:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一点点…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.81,0:12:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是八原
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.48,0:12:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那般小妖怪竟然能进入寺庙境内
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.56,0:12:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫咪老师
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.15,0:12:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前都跑那去了  刚才可是千钧一发
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.32,0:12:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在观察那大锤妖怪到底是什么来历
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.63,0:12:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过在我想出手救助之前
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.89,0:12:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙替我赶走那妖怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.73,0:13:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也赶紧睡觉去吧  夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.63,0:13:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来站岗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.76,0:13:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎能总是被这么无聊的东西死缠着
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.47,0:13:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天就做个了结吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.64,0:13:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.61,0:13:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过在那之前  替我把田沼带到被子那里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.67,0:13:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.66,0:13:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得去收拾那窗户的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.21,0:13:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人情可大着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.37,0:13:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七品屋的馒头可不够分量啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.99,0:13:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这没有关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.59,0:13:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好重啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.84,0:13:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子你太重了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.47,0:13:39.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我减肥去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.66,0:13:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我一样…变得灵巧些
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.48,0:13:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  你们俩都还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.93,0:13:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.56,0:13:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来不太妙嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.81,0:13:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记不太清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.69,0:13:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像从口里吐出什么很夸张的东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.09,0:13:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你吃什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.32,0:14:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  不是那么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.08,0:14:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  夏目君  这个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.60,0:14:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我参照家里的资料做的护身符
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.75,0:14:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不知能否起到作用
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.26,0:14:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但什么都不做反而更难过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.00,0:14:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很精巧  真不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.87,0:14:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是还是希望你能带着它
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.68,0:14:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了  多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.09,0:14:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通宵未眠替我做的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.09,0:14:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有那么拼命
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.84,0:14:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多轨你还真是容易成熊猫眼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.22,0:14:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我的手工能够更灵巧一些就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.70,0:14:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是手工问题  是欣赏水平的问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.32,0:14:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要这么说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.70,0:14:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可就不给你这被附身者用的护身符了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.43,0:14:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  也为我做了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.24,0:14:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  这个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.16,0:14:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢…哇
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.72,0:14:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得很恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.70,0:14:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有办法  是这么记载着的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.81,0:14:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大半夜一个人做这个也是很害怕的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.29,0:15:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感激不尽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.52,0:15:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么今天就赶紧做个了结吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.02,0:15:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过猫咪老师呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.11,0:15:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说自己一人在学校周边找找看看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.37,0:15:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你们给我好好找妖怪的镜子的碎片啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.90,0:15:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  干活
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.90,0:15:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛痛痛痛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.60,0:15:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.23,0:15:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来那家伙说过
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.85,0:15:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碎片喜欢藏进闪闪发光的东西之中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.79,0:15:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.16,0:15:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.34,0:15:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  疼痛消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.22,0:15:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来得去各种地方找镜子了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.14,0:15:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样放学后还得继续呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.92,0:15:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.96,0:15:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.69,0:16:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在这附近也有妖怪在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.05,0:16:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  小家伙们的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.52,0:16:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.12,0:16:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.71,0:16:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目每天都看着这样的东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.40,0:16:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.52,0:16:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.20,0:16:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你所见到的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.51,0:16:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.15,0:16:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们开始去找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.63,0:16:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找不到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.22,0:16:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该有的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.55,0:16:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛痛痛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.33,0:16:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.57,0:16:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真是个不错的镜子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.86,0:16:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制作者的手工真是太耀眼了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.79,0:16:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的呢  到底是产自哪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.93,0:17:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还真是个无语的借口啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.65,0:17:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来校内的镜子都检查过了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.92,0:17:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后就是闪光的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.30,0:17:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个相当闪亮的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.15,0:17:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.03,0:17:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在闪光呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.03,0:17:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这附近
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.48,0:17:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.77,0:17:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这附近吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.21,0:17:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.79,0:17:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是很痛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.13,0:17:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那应该是还有咯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.87,0:17:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.71,0:17:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.08,0:17:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢了  多轨
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.95,0:17:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不疼了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.14,0:17:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  我这就去拿毛巾
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.85,0:17:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.17,0:17:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.25,0:17:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被附身的可是我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.41,0:18:02.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是为了我自己
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.40,0:18:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目经常会有这样的想法吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.90,0:18:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  总是不能好好地说清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.19,0:18:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.30,0:18:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕  不安什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.08,0:18:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要表达那些有些困难
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.80,0:18:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.27,0:18:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很难
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.32,0:18:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  笨蛋小子们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.85,0:18:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狸猫…不是  是胖太啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.01,0:18:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.24,0:18:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师  你拿着什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.46,0:18:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  拿着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.59,0:18:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.15,0:18:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我稍显实力的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.41,0:18:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要找到这碎片  简直像在砂砾中找寻沙子一样简单
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.14,0:18:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.97,0:18:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.94,0:18:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.81,0:19:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们给我认真干活去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.68,0:19:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从砂砾中找寻沙子怎么听起来感觉很强大
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.10,0:19:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实没啥特别意义吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.73,0:19:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.27,0:19:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  拿上这个走人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.95,0:19:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.85,0:19:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,镜子  我要！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.45,0:19:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.89,0:19:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.20,0:19:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.45,0:19:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来  交给我  镜子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.67,0:19:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  这个镜子我可不会轻易放手
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.70,0:20:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来  疾病也能被驱除掉了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.59,0:20:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.23,0:20:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.68,0:20:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  得赶紧去找我朋友了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.75,0:20:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后替他驱除疾病再畅谈一番
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.29,0:20:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能否找寻得到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.77,0:20:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重病…说不定
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.55,0:20:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位友人已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.11,0:20:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有必要满脸忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.35,0:20:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我想要去找寻而已
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.78,0:20:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是怎样的结局在等待着我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.83,0:21:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不跟他抱怨一番的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.30,0:21:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就无法释怀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.44,0:21:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再会了  人类之子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.57,0:21:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若还有机会相互交心  不必恐惧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.82,0:21:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那又是件很难的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.83,0:21:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因如此才会有失败
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.26,0:21:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也会有很难得的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.38,0:21:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样田沼被附身事件总算是圆满解决
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.59,0:21:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  已经走掉了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.50,0:21:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也得通知多轨一声
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.45,0:21:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.13,0:21:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许有点对不住在替我担心的夏目你们
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.03,0:21:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是挺开心的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.03,0:22:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看到夏目所看到的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.76,0:22:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那个妖怪也有了很多交流
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.30,0:22:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交流过是指…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.69,0:22:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有被灌输什么奇怪的思想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.41,0:22:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目真的是很辛苦呐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.62,0:22:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.87,0:22:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也不尽是些辛苦的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.43,0:22:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.50,0:22:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.12,0:24:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候那个人若没有来见我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.18,0:24:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的我…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.25,0:24:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢寂寞的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.32,0:24:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着就觉得有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.01,0:24:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  夏目  你这是去哪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.78,0:24:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次有人跟我说希望我过去
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.31,0:24:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能随便就跟陌生人走
