[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,134
Style: zhu_bt,方正隶变_GBK,47,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H5A000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,16,134
Style: title,方正楷体_GBK,60,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ly,华文楷体,40,&H00E9FEEE,&HF0000000,&H0A0D150F,&H3C427370,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,1,10,30,9,134
Style: ly_ed,华文楷体,40,&H000E1216,&HF0000000,&H32FFFFFF,&H5AFFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,1,10,10,9,134
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,48,&H000E203B,&HFF000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H5A939897,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またそんな顔して\N仍是那副表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.51,0:00:09.42,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唇かみ締めて\N紧咬着的双唇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:13.40,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱さを隠してるけど\N掩饰着的软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.41,0:00:20.79,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その瞳の奧\N眼眸深处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.19,0:00:25.23,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うずくまる君が\N蜷缩着的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.24,0:00:29.19,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の心なら\N若是真实的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.20,0:00:36.61,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思って\N思念着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.61,0:00:37.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣いて\N哭泣着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.73,0:00:38.72,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人で\N独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.73,0:00:39.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安で\N不安着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.66,0:00:40.75,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで\N为何
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.76,0:00:41.66,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いの\N总将伤痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.67,0:00:42.86,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持ってんだ\N深埋心底
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.87,0:00:44.59,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕に そっと 預けてよ\N静静地侧身于我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.60,0:00:52.00,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直ぐじゃ無理と思うのならば\N即便无法立刻成真
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.29,0:00:56.65,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少しずつでいい\N慢步前行足以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:01:00.54,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翼の無い僕等はきっと\N你若只是孤执地认定
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:04.11,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛べないと決め付けてるだけ\N没有羽翼的我们注定无法飞翔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.12,0:01:08.08,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声の限り君を呼ぶよ\N用尽全力来将你呼唤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.09,0:01:12.49,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷わないように\N无须继续彷徨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.50,0:01:16.21,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フワリ心舞い上がれ\N心儿悠然轻漾
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:19.80,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの風に乗せて\N伴乘着清风
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:23.04,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:28.77,ly,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いっせいのせ\N我们齐声吟唱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.15,0:01:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看见妖怪 这对大家还是保密的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.81,0:01:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 有把伞在飞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.48,0:01:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伞? 哪里哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.67,0:01:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 就在那
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.31,0:01:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说哪里 哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.91,0:01:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.16,0:01:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.47,0:01:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是我看错了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.85,0:01:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.35,0:02:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再见咯 夏目 明天见
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.03,0:02:02.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.21,0:02:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得见我吗 人类啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.61,0:02:19.58,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱之琴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.83,0:02:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就是你了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.47,0:02:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不想欺负人类 不过也没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.00,0:02:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的身体我就收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.62,0:02:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住...住手
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.04,0:02:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 把身体交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.98,0:02:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.35,0:02:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了让你住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.64,0:02:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是猴急啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.40,0:02:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.41,0:03:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 这富含钙质 吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.81,0:03:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.26,0:03:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 我居然犯这种错误
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.40,0:03:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区一个人类还蛮厉害的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.22,0:03:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 无论如何你这副身体我要定了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.96,0:03:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.17,0:03:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 铜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.58,0:03:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位人类啊 请原谅他的无礼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.91,0:03:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他这都是为了我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.06,0:03:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,葫芦里传出了声音?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.31,0:03:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱 别说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.86,0:03:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会累着的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.93,0:03:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.15,0:03:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.39,0:03:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱 我有听过这名字
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.59,0:03:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说在聚集了高贵妖怪的梦幻之乡「磯月森林」中
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.61,0:03:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个叫浅葱的美丽苍琴师
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.56,0:04:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个浅葱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.32,0:04:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 但她因为病痛已经无法再弹琴了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.47,0:04:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是被送回了故乡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.05,0:04:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本是那么爱笑的她
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.69,0:04:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在完全失去了活力
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.35,0:04:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 人类啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.11,0:04:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了浅葱暂且把你那身体借给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.93,0:04:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦 如果你不服从
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.32,0:04:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就把你的耳朵和鼻子扯下来吃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.86,0:04:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把身体交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.62,0:04:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 低等的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.89,0:04:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.16,0:04:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 被狸猫咬了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.31,0:04:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥 你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.34,0:04:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑什么 地藏!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.35,0:04:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍不留神和妖怪扯上关系就准没好事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.44,0:04:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更何况要把身体借给他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.59,0:04:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本是那么爱笑的她
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.74,0:04:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是总觉得...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.35,0:04:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.49,0:05:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我～回来～了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.13,0:05:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊 猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.75,0:05:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是天亮才回来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.78,0:05:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 你的头发...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.03,0:05:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.44,0:05:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼珠的颜色似乎也成蓝色的了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.60,0:05:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.12,0:05:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 变回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.98,0:05:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是错觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.76,0:05:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 早上好 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.95,0:05:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 早安
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.04,0:05:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早...早上好 北木
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.10,0:05:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓...吓了我一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.87,0:05:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一瞬间还以为我认错人了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.09,0:05:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 看他们两个呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.17,0:05:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.99,0:06:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 谢谢你的字典
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.88,0:06:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.20,0:06:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮了我大忙哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.81,0:06:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.52,0:06:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 掉了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.45,0:06:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 田沼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.45,0:06:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.96,0:06:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊...不 刚刚那一瞬把夏目你看成女生了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.99,0:06:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 是错觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.82,0:06:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对...对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.79,0:06:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先不说北木  连田沼都有感觉到什么的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.95,0:06:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.27,0:06:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做了什么吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.09,0:07:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁你睡着的时候 我把浅葱放进你的身体里了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.32,0:07:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎同化得很顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.02,0:07:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂时就麻烦你帮忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.78,0:07:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上的蓝色头发和眼珠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.95,0:07:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来都是被附身的表现啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.13,0:07:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.54,0:07:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我让他不要这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.84,0:07:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也没办法去制止 非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.63,0:07:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这声音...你就是浅葱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.47,0:07:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要责怪他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.52,0:07:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.71,0:07:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 你用不着道歉的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.11,0:07:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.12,0:07:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她从你身体里出来的方法?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.63,0:07:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 除了头槌之外
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.63,0:07:50.87,zhu_bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs30}译注:第6话中猫先生曾用自己的脑袋飞撞夏目 使附身的燕从中脱离 故戏称「头槌」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.87,0:07:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 那只有实现浅葱的愿望了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.17,0:07:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要她心情得到舒解自然会从你体内分离出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.06,0:08:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但说是愿望...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.47,0:08:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再啰嗦下去也无济于事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.33,0:08:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快做完回去吧 人类哟
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.28,0:08:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别命令我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.13,0:08:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底从哪儿来的 叫什么名字
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.95,0:08:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不会把我的名字告诉人类
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.09,0:08:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那从现在起你就叫「蛇目」了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.93,0:08:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇目伞的蛇目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.93,0:08:20.67,zhu_bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs30}译注:蛇目伞传说是古代医生等比较多使用 此伞大小很适合遮2个人 叫蛇目的原因是因伞面上有一圈白色的条带 有点类似蛇的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.77,0:08:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇...蛇目?!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.67,0:08:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑来迎接我们 辛苦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.30,0:08:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可恶的狸猫...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.88,0:08:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱的名字啊 太好了呢 蛇目先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.29,0:08:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱 怎么连你也...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.52,0:08:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧 这不是很有趣嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.21,0:08:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.58,0:08:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好恶心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.22,0:08:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚...刚刚身体被控制了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.39,0:08:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 一不小心就...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.65,0:08:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.73,0:08:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白啦明白啦 我会帮忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.17,0:08:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弹完琴后就能离开我的身体吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.46,0:08:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那当然
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.51,0:09:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.80,0:09:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是要从制琴开始么?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.89,0:09:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 因为那是种特别的琴
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.32,0:09:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有种额头上有白线 长得和鲤鱼一模一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.74,0:09:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字叫「线引」的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.04,0:09:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是要去抓它
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.71,0:09:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说为什么要捉鱼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.99,0:09:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 别跟我顶嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.22,0:09:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛一脸郁闷的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.07,0:09:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是干劲十足啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.32,0:09:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿哟 嘿哟 嘿哟 嘿哟
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.38,0:09:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,累死了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.07,0:09:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}快出来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.43,0:09:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.00,0:09:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦...不
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.99,0:09:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}线引
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.53,0:09:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱你和蛇目先生...是什么关系呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.12,0:09:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在交往么?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.83,0:09:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.28,0:10:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇目先生他是撑伞人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.98,0:10:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撑伞人?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.87,0:10:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在磯月森林中
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.64,0:10:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聚集了被掌管森林的壬生大人看中的有才能的人们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.51,0:10:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里 为了不让壬生大人和那些人受到伤害
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.43,0:10:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他们撑伞 以保镖的身份护卫大家的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.26,0:10:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是蛇目先生的职责
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.94,0:10:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇目先生身手非常好的哟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.58,0:10:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,磯月森林是个非常美丽的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.36,0:10:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像梦境一样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.61,0:10:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想永远待在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.94,0:10:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为自己能永远陪伴在壬生大人身旁的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.45,0:10:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远...永远...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.77,0:11:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不能弹琴就被赶了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.34,0:11:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是个心胸狭窄的神明啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.84,0:11:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.51,0:11:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是壬生大人收留了无家可归的我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.37,0:11:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍受不了变得毫无用处的自己而逃离那儿的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.11,0:11:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了 是「线引」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.32,0:11:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.84,0:11:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看 这根线就是用来做弦的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.55,0:11:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那材料收集就算到此结束了吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.66,0:11:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没 接下来是琴身
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.82,0:11:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.88,0:11:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去找树桩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.61,0:11:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是要被刚破土而出的竹子所贯穿的树桩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.42,0:11:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再等一下...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.08,0:11:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再等一下就能让你弹琴了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.65,0:12:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇目先生真的是对浅葱...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.66,0:12:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么湿成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.43,0:12:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.78,0:12:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 毛巾毛巾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.33,0:12:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好 贵志如果感冒了就...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.79,0:12:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.86,0:12:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿嚏
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.29,0:12:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.80,0:12:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给 好好擦干
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.97,0:12:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连头发都湿透了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.12,0:12:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想永远待在那里 永远...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.94,0:12:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去洗澡吧 去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.22,0:12:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗澡水正好刚烧好 快去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.71,0:12:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...可以在这里待到什么时候呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.32,0:13:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.58,0:13:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.67,0:13:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 这是浅葱的...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.97,0:13:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇目先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.41,0:13:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵醒你了吗 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.42,0:13:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 不过浅葱还睡着
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.91,0:13:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么想说的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.92,0:13:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱的手指已经不能弹琴了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.56,0:13:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一种身体会像干裂的泥土般逐渐剥落的病
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.57,0:13:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经无法恢复了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.60,0:13:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 附到其他人身上时可以减慢恶化的速度
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.59,0:13:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很感谢你 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.79,0:13:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最后一次看到她的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.24,0:13:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她在壬生大人面前幸福地弹奏曲子的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.86,0:13:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那次演奏中
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.59,0:14:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的皮肤突然开始剥落
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.46,0:14:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至连雪白修长的手指
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.24,0:14:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和光彩照人的脸颊也...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.18,0:14:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在她仰慕不已的壬生大人面前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.79,0:14:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天就是满月了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.69,0:14:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通往磯月森林的道路会暂时开启
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.61,0:14:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后 哪怕是最后一次
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.14,0:14:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让她再在壬生大人面前弹奏
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.15,0:14:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那时为止 请您务必帮我...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.89,0:14:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.04,0:14:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇目先生你为什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.09,0:14:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么那么的...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.64,0:14:36.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.12,0:14:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 铜
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.18,0:14:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...只不过是个撑伞人罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.92,0:15:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 还真是难找啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.00,0:15:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}在哪儿!出来呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.71,0:15:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完...完全找不到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.06,0:15:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里真的会有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.42,0:15:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在找什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.49,0:15:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长着竹子的树桩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.46,0:15:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个的话 就在那灌木丛中间
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.26,0:15:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.54,0:15:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.60,0:15:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦? 刚刚我在和谁说话?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.26,0:15:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你了 告诉你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.21,0:15:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为代价我要你的肠子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.78,0:15:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.23,0:15:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 和奇怪的妖怪说话了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.74,0:15:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目 你有在认真找吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.06,0:15:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好 夏目 就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.81,0:15:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 马上动手制作吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.95,0:16:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体开始觉得有点不舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.65,0:16:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种略带热度的倦怠感
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.16,0:16:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是浅葱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.49,0:16:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然这么的虚弱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.90,0:16:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果还要弹奏苍琴的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.08,0:16:18.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱她的生命会...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.39,0:16:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您没事吧 非常抱歉 都因为我的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.49,0:16:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 我还没征求过你的意见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.96,0:16:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.59,0:16:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱你自己也想弹琴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.42,0:16:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能再一次
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.73,0:16:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让我再有一次机会的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.90,0:16:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.48,0:16:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不聪明 手指也很僵硬 可能弹不好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.50,0:16:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此也没关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.38,0:17:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱 你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.18,0:17:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铜他一直...一直都对你...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.68,0:17:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好啦 夏目 快起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.09,0:17:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 还来得及 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.31,0:17:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铜 怎么了 到底要做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.69,0:17:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱 现在的话通往磯月森林的道路还开启着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.52,0:17:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 然后 给壬生大人...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.45,0:17:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.79,0:17:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照约定我来要你的肠子了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.70,0:17:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是那时候的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.66,0:17:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铜
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.23,0:18:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.34,0:18:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琴...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.62,0:18:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱的...蛇目的...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.61,0:18:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.27,0:18:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.32,0:18:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.51,0:18:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.73,0:18:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.02,0:18:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那妖怪已经被我赶走了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.62,0:18:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.69,0:18:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完好无损 是你保护了它
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.85,0:18:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.76,0:18:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能站起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.36,0:18:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点的话 可能还能来得及
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.62,0:18:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的话我就背你过去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.25,0:18:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇目先生你才是 都伤成这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.10,0:18:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.42,0:18:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.75,0:19:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能够实现的话 哪怕再弹一次也好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.96,0:19:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直...一直都只在为那位大人弹奏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.36,0:19:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.75,0:19:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能再一次让我弹奏苍琴的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.05,0:19:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要为温柔且珍贵的友人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.56,0:19:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了你而弹奏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.84,0:19:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铜 能倾听我的琴声么?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.00,0:19:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从远处传来了乐声
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.42,0:19:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从未听到过的美妙音色
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.44,0:20:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那音色却是从我的指缝间流出
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.82,0:20:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,融入空气
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.86,0:20:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仿佛坠入空中般地
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.39,0:20:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅葱离开了我的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.97,0:20:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你添麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.80,0:20:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后你有什么打算?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.69,0:20:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带着浅葱回到她的故乡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.30,0:20:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.04,0:20:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只是 沉沉地沉沉地睡着了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.27,0:20:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 再会了 浅葱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.32,0:20:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再会了 蛇目先生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.89,0:20:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.06,0:21:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见咯 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.39,0:21:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪里了啊 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.41,0:21:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在人家那么危急的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.30,0:21:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满足了吗 你个滥好人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.93,0:21:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我饿了 去买馒头回来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.41,0:21:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七辻屋还没开哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.34,0:21:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵 你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.34,0:21:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫先生你有想要永远停留的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.85,0:21:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种东西我一生都不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.34,0:21:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.78,0:21:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.85,0:21:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前也是一直这么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.70,0:21:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 笨蛋 别抱我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.58,0:21:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快放手 放手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.44,0:21:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试着弹了下他们留下的琴
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.18,0:21:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却无法再发出那么美妙的音色了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.87,0:21:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那音色 不是由我的手指
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.88,0:21:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是她的心灵所弹奏出的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.14,0:21:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃早饭了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.90,0:21:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.08,0:23:50.04,zhu,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(260,540)}猫咪无聊帐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.77,0:23:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 先生 你做了什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.73,0:23:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会做那种事情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.40,0:23:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装傻 给我出去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.96,0:23:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 出去就出去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.16,0:23:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目你这笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.88,0:23:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我就掉进坑里了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.94,0:23:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 天上掉下只小白猪
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.20,0:22:12.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色づく西空に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.20,0:22:12.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,染色西空边
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.14,0:22:20.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差し込み一筋の陽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.14,0:22:20.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一抹斜阳倾洒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:26.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕立の雨上がりに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.10,0:22:26.57,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕傍骤雨微歇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.57,0:22:33.50,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気付く 夏の匂い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.57,0:22:33.50,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽觉初夏气息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:44.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひしめく 光が照らす思いに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.26,0:22:44.55,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光影斑驳 感怀忆处
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.55,0:22:48.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳を澄ませば
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.55,0:22:48.75,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧耳聆听
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:58.40,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞こえし友の面影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.94,0:22:58.40,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻见友人踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:06.04,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏夕空 薫り立つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:23:06.04,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏日夕空 清香满溢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:13.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鮮やかな過ぎ去りし日々
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:13.10,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忆流金岁月依旧鲜明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.10,0:23:20.46,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心のまま笑いあった
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.10,0:23:20.46,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾相视而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.46,0:23:27.18,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの夏の思い出よ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.46,0:23:27.18,ly_ed,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不散的夏日回忆
