[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,1
Style: OP_jp,方正楷体_GBK,33,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,45,1
Style: OP_ch,方正楷体_GBK,36,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,5,1
Style: ED_jp,方正楷体_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,45,1
Style: ED_ch,方正楷体_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,5,1
Style: bt,方正楷体_GBK,55,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H32A8D0C8,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhu,方正隶变_GBK,33,&H00E8EEF4,&HF0000000,&H1E23384E,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text



Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.12,0:01:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊? 是登雪山啦 登雪山
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.18,0:01:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.76,0:01:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边欣赏着积雪覆盖的群山
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.35,0:01:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边沿着铁道漫步实在太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.74,0:01:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 天空好高
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.93,0:01:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来好老气
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.63,0:01:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 你怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.38,0:01:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.57,0:01:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 你们在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.68,0:01:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.42,0:01:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸色很差哦 是不是发烧了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.57,0:02:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 可能有点睡眠不足吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.83,0:02:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊 要注意身体哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.26,0:02:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.73,0:02:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.13,0:02:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.26,0:02:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.18,0:02:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.98,0:02:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.23,0:02:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们俩都看不到的话 是妖怪么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.05,0:02:37.03,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约定之树
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.70,0:02:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七辻屋的羊羹也不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.14,0:02:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早点尝尝就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.71,0:02:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于吞下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.82,0:02:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.29,0:02:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,37度多
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.50,0:02:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还是赶紧睡下比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.03,0:03:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经吃过药了 只要安静地休息会儿就会没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.19,0:03:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想给塔子婶婶添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.78,0:03:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 你要到什么时候才会明白啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.95,0:03:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.02,0:03:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.73,0:03:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 从刚才起就一直有人在偷窥哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.35,0:03:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷窥?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.62,0:03:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那孩子 是刚才的...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.14,0:03:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有够迟钝
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.60,0:03:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烫!!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.01,0:03:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再问一次
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.70,0:03:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么跟着我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.20,0:03:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了友人帐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.93,0:03:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是听不懂人类的语言
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.50,0:04:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.24,0:04:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说话我们怎么知道你想干嘛呢 快说点啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.36,0:04:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 真...真对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.37,0:04:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.03,0:04:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不记得我了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.38,0:04:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.74,0:04:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我不是铃子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.48,0:04:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.69,0:04:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子早就死了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.70,0:04:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.93,0:04:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈!?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.74,0:04:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打击太大 直接石化了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.77,0:04:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是麻烦的家伙 受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.28,0:04:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.04,0:04:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是夏目铃子的外孙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.90,0:05:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.95,0:05:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然个性阴郁 但还是有点能力的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.64,0:05:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「个性阴郁」就多余了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.30,0:05:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.67,0:05:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 现在就把名字还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.63,0:05:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「守护吾者 显现汝名」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.94,0:05:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.26,0:05:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有写着这家伙名字的那一页
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.65,0:05:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是说没有订立契约咯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.84,0:05:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,660)}那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.86,0:05:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 友人帐有反应
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.93,0:05:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该有订过契约
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.38,0:05:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是脱落遗失了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.31,0:05:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.76,0:05:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是铃子的话完全有可能
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.17,0:05:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...我的名字应该不在那里面
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.74,0:05:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.07,0:05:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是在其他地方
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.20,0:05:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他地方?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.90,0:05:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就早点说啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.83,0:06:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印名字的纸被绑在树枝上了?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.65,0:06:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 她说「50年后就还给你」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.70,0:06:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子外婆 为什么要做这种事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.42,0:06:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真像铃子的作风
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.12,0:06:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过她让你等 你还真的就等了50年
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.99,0:06:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是率真到近乎愚钝的境界啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.62,0:06:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真对不起 猫先生大人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.11,0:06:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要用这么奇怪的称呼 听着很不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.99,0:06:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把「大人」去掉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.26,0:06:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.04,0:06:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我「大先生」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.60,0:06:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.20,0:06:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从没想过自己想办法拿回名字的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.63,0:06:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子说 如果中途拿回名字的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.35,0:06:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会引起海啸 世界灭亡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.75,0:06:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.83,0:06:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 你被戏弄了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.17,0:06:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过看着这家伙也稍微能理解铃子的心情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.97,0:06:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.69,0:06:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 绑着契约书的树是哪棵呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.73,0:06:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 确实应该是这附近的 不过...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.42,0:06:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「确实」 是啥意思 你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.27,0:06:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了就会很在意 所以尽量不去接近它
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.75,0:07:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那该不会是说...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.50,0:07:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以50年来都不曾靠近过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.06,0:07:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶!?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.68,0:07:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,50年...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.41,0:07:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这儿搁了半个世纪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.10,0:07:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.76,0:07:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过了50年的话 树都长起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.49,0:07:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绑着契约书的树枝也长得很高了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.52,0:07:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是找不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.97,0:07:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 那样我会很为难的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.06,0:07:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但话说回来 这森林里到底有多少棵树啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.22,0:07:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.52,0:07:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就放弃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.17,0:07:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.02,0:07:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在好好的就足以说明契约书也没事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.87,0:07:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后就这样放着也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.12,0:07:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你就死心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.69,0:07:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.54,0:07:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 我会死心的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.04,0:07:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就对了 好 回去吃羊羹咯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.39,0:07:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的要放弃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.71,0:07:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.88,0:08:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再试着找找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.02,0:08:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许找着找着就突然能想起什么 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.52,0:08:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.89,0:08:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受不了 你这烂好人要做到什么时候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.71,0:08:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不会帮忙的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.17,0:08:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,田沼?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.58,0:08:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不 是在找东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.30,0:08:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦你真不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.56,0:08:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.20,0:08:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是没希望了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.97,0:08:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾叶 不是才刚开始找吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.83,0:08:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也能看见就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.16,0:08:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.87,0:08:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个眉清目秀的美少年哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.86,0:08:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.50,0:08:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是女孩子太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.86,0:08:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则就会有心不甘的回忆了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.57,0:08:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 说起女孩子...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.49,0:08:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我说你们 再卖力点找啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.31,0:08:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.23,0:08:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是按你所说的在找嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.55,0:09:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是没错 可是都围在同一个地方找不是没意义了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.85,0:09:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然说不要围在一起 你就别掺合进来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.57,0:09:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就快散开 不要围在一起散开去找啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.37,0:09:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本想他们可以帮上忙的 没想到变那么吵
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.57,0:09:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是班长的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.85,0:09:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有的事 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.15,0:09:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 他们一定没想到要找的是妖怪的东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.11,0:09:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笹田
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.14,0:09:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.07,0:09:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现蜂巢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.97,0:09:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我认真找!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.15,0:09:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.91,0:09:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 只是大家...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.74,0:09:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么多人来帮忙 觉得很奇怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.11,0:09:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是听说 人类之间是非常冷漠的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.66,0:09:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是听谁说的?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.16,0:09:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是夏目铃子说的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.98,0:09:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 在这儿 在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.78,0:09:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丙?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.82,0:09:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.83,0:09:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这臭猪要我来帮忙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.66,0:09:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥? 傻瓜在做傻事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.63,0:09:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是说那就随你们咋样了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.21,0:09:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.98,0:09:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要一副诚恳道谢的样子 真不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.83,0:10:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 就是你吗 被铃子诅咒了的那个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.33,0:10:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是诅咒就有点...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.70,0:10:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上不就是被诅咒了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.50,0:10:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不要欺负他了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.30,0:10:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 这一带就交给你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.94,0:10:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 怎么...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.68,0:10:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.32,0:10:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了? 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.96,0:10:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.53,0:10:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们就此告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.17,0:10:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你们担心了 真是不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.73,0:10:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们不好 没注意到夏目不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.15,0:10:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.07,0:10:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过已经在好转了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.12,0:10:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,药也吃了 接下来好好睡一觉就会好了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.18,0:10:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过明天可能要跟学校请假
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.40,0:10:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我会转告老师的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.40,0:10:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明可以跟我们说一声的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.16,0:10:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.84,0:11:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 太过逞强才会这样的 这个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.61,0:11:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.76,0:11:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.82,0:11:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.80,0:11:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是找不到的东西 因为这个夏目才...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.66,0:11:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我不提起这些就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.20,0:11:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再说一遍看看
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.12,0:11:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.97,0:11:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为夏目是因为谁变成这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.41,0:11:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.34,0:11:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.60,0:11:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是希望你能明白夏目的心意
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.51,0:11:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说出让他的努力付诸东流的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.62,0:11:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再这么说的话 可饶不了你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.44,0:11:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明不擅长与别人交往
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.17,0:11:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可一旦别人有事 便会挺身而出
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.24,0:11:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这孩子和铃子真是太像了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.48,0:12:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好无聊的一天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.11,0:12:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打扰下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.87,0:12:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.91,0:12:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我迷路了 能告诉我怎么出这个森林么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.26,0:12:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类? 竟然能看见我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.50,0:12:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 就拿她解闷
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.38,0:12:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来 我给你带路
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.02,0:12:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 帮了我大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.45,0:12:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是男人的话就推到沼泽里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.44,0:12:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个漂亮的姑娘呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.40,0:12:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带到森林深处再丢下不管 让她大哭一场
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.19,0:12:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.92,0:12:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 话说回来你这样的女孩怎么会跑到森林里的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.00,0:12:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 因为不小心把三个男生打得很惨
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.48,0:12:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就想在风波平息前 到森林里躲一躲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.62,0:12:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个男生?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.30,0:12:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是寄宿在亲戚家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.12,0:12:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不想给别人添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.43,0:13:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过人类真的好麻烦 让人讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.77,0:13:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈? 那你喜欢怪物 妖怪之类的吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.66,0:13:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌恐怖的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.04,0:13:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 也是 怎么可能有喜欢妖怪的人类呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.00,0:13:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 出口还没到么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.54,0:13:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还早呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.51,0:13:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 虽在深林中 你却打扮得很美艳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.61,0:13:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 莫非...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.78,0:13:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 被看穿了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.69,0:13:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这丫头如此傲慢 干脆在这里吃掉她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.46,0:13:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 我是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.20,0:13:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 危险
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.68,0:13:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊 一边去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.91,0:13:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这群乌鸦要捉弄你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.39,0:13:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这帮家伙一直觊觎这个发簪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.76,0:13:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了这是很重要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.36,0:13:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊? 让它们得手了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.80,0:14:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那么重要的东西么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.65,0:14:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看招!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.90,0:14:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女孩究竟...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.14,0:14:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么啊 别乱来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.57,0:14:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么...要做这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.97,0:14:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.61,0:14:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你是妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.99,0:14:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要这个的话 领我到森林的出口 好吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.54,0:14:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性格竟如此恶劣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.51,0:14:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性格恶劣 性格恶劣...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.26,0:14:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次想起来都让人心神荡漾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.49,0:15:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听了多少遍都不明白 为什么那样就迷人了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.90,0:15:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这种又丑又肥的石头猫是不会懂的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.73,0:15:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说清楚谁是又丑又肥的石头猫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.62,0:15:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子外婆她...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.64,0:15:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 你已经醒了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.45,0:15:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了拿发簪 跳到湖里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.86,0:15:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 净逞强
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.07,0:15:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 雾叶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.47,0:15:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说铃子吓唬你 说如果你拿走她绑的契约纸
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.23,0:15:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会令大海肆意泛滥 世界毁灭 是吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.38,0:15:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.29,0:15:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她为什么对住在森林里的你说起大海呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.29,0:15:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是因为我说过想要去看海
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.21,0:15:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.13,0:15:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我出生在这里 只知道森林周围的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.77,0:15:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是听候鸟说 大海是非常美好的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.57,0:15:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那铃子是怎么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.55,0:15:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说「想看的话去看不就好了」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.01,0:15:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有点远 但海边还是能到达的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.73,0:16:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能离开这个森林
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.93,0:16:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.23,0:16:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生于森林的人 便不能离开森林
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.92,0:16:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有结界的话还另当别论
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.59,0:16:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可没听说过只因在那里出生就不能离开那里的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.84,0:16:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总...总而言之是不行啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.66,0:16:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 你不知道大海是什么样子么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.94,0:16:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于那个铃子她有告诉过我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.50,0:16:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子她?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.69,0:16:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 大海是湛蓝的 广袤无边的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.54,0:16:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.51,0:16:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是漾着波浪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.81,0:16:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳和月亮的光芒照耀在水面上熠熠生辉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.93,0:16:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.45,0:16:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有住着长脖子的恐龙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.94,0:16:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯嗯...诶!?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.65,0:16:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岛上还有秘密基地什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.80,0:16:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,运气好的话还能看到圆盘起飞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.55,0:16:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.29,0:16:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实很厉害呢 从中间开始
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.11,0:16:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.87,0:17:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着就能想像铃子跟你描述时的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.57,0:17:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 果然我还是被骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.68,0:17:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.50,0:17:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后名字就被夺走并绑在树枝上了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.50,0:17:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是铃子应该不会夺走听话的妖怪的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.06,0:17:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是非常想捉弄他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.37,0:17:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好过份
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.27,0:17:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真那么想么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.01,0:17:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的认为铃子外婆是个过份的人么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.83,0:17:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.02,0:17:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我烧退了 我们再去找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.03,0:17:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到绑着名字的树的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.94,0:17:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定就能弄清楚铃子外婆想做什么了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.54,0:17:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.85,0:17:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 烧退了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.73,0:17:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 不要再逞强了 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.58,0:18:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 不好意思 让你担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.59,0:18:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 我出去买东西了 好好休息哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.32,0:18:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.23,0:18:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您要出门吗 慢走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.14,0:18:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丙找到那棵树了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.82,0:18:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 所以要我们带大家去森林
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.80,0:18:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.63,0:18:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.52,0:18:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要去哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.95,0:18:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 雾叶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.53,0:18:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都~说~了~
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.31,0:18:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔子不是吩咐你在家好好休息嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.37,0:18:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这上面哦 契约书
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.13,0:18:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.26,0:18:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后会怎么样我可不管
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.12,0:18:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾叶 你爬上去取下来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.73,0:18:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶? 我去?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.81,0:18:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我办不到 这么高的树
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.56,0:18:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不怕契约书被弄烂 就让粗暴的丙帮你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.71,0:18:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么? 你再说一次试试 斑
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.98,0:18:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这又丑又肥的石头猫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.05,0:18:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈? 你不用再特意纠正 真让人郁闷
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.10,0:19:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 讨厌 你很讨厌哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.67,0:19:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼嗒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.88,0:19:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.59,0:19:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了 在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.67,0:19:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.02,0:19:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.54,0:20:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 闪闪发光的 那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.35,0:20:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是海吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.39,0:20:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.69,0:20:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到大海啦!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.52,0:20:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对妖怪来说50年不算什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.41,0:20:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深知这一点 铃子才做了这种约定
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.87,0:20:38.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 铃子才不是这种浪漫主义...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.77,0:20:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.12,0:20:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子外婆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.35,0:20:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.73,0:20:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾叶 归还汝名 收下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.99,0:21:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好寂寞呀 什么都没有留下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.07,0:21:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.50,0:21:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.20,0:21:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所见到的东西 感受到的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.12,0:21:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远都不会消逝
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.47,0:21:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不会遗忘
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.71,0:21:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.21,0:21:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是...是塔子婶婶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.99,0:21:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被子被子 快脱 袜子袜子 快快快 呜哇
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.56,0:21:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉怎么样 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.85,0:22:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伴随着各种相遇与邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.93,0:23:51.06,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,550)}{\fs52}少女之阵
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.13,0:23:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在野原看到了奇妙的图阵
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.45,0:23:42.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了与宇宙人取得联络而成立的社团吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.11,0:23:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 你啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.31,0:23:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目同学
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.53,0:23:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 我刚才说了你的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.08,0:23:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像是...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.10,0:23:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是5班的多轨透

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 少しだけ大人の色に染まる指先
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 指尖稍露成年的沧桑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 照れくさそうに そっと隠して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 你就害羞得将它悄悄收起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 頬杖ついた君 見つめてる視線の先に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 手托下巴的你将视线投向
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 小さな蕾が ゆらゆら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 那随风轻曳的小小花蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} ねぇ 僕なんて いまも迷いばかりで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 喂 现在的我仍迷茫依旧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} あの日贈った言葉 今さら思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 这才回想起 那日你的临别赠言
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「君色に未来染めて...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「将我的未来染成你的颜色...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ 聞いていてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 听我倾诉好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ わがままいいですか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 让我任性好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手に入れた途端に消えてしまいそう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}拥有的瞬间仿佛就会消散
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}言葉をくれませんか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不说点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あなたがいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}因为有你在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}それだけで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう世界が変わってしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我的世界就会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}モノトーンの景色が ほら 鮮やかに映る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}映入眼眸的单调景色也会光鲜亮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}いつのまにか 離れていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不知何时却已离开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手を繋いで歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}牵着手 向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}上手く愛せているかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}能够好好去爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あの空に聞いてみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}天空也许会回答
