[Script Info]
Title: SOS动漫社团 - http://www.sosg.net/
Original Script: SOSG字幕团
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,1
Style: small,方正隶变_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,1,0,0,0,80,80,1,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,46,1
Style: Banner,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H50000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,20,1
Style: Title,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&HA0C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,10,10,12,1
Style: Title2,方正楷体_GBK,40,&H0003232C,&HF0000000,&H55C5DECA,&H30C5DECA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,10,300,100,1
Style: OPjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: OPch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00E1FDE6,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: OPjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,9,12,10,9,1
Style: OPchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H20000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,1,12,10,7,1
Style: EDjp,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDch,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECE5DB,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,8,1
Style: EDjpb,麗流隷書,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,9,10,10,8,1
Style: EDchb,方正隶变_GBK,27,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00ECAAA5,&H20222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,8,1



[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.36,0:03:34.37,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\shad2\bord1}困惑之时
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.05,0:24:16.06,Title2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\blur1.6\pos(158,296)}月分祭
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君がどうして泣いてるなのか
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}僕には何も分からない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}分かるようなんて言葉　軽々しく口に出来ない
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君が苦しむ訳を　僕に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}出来る精一杯のことを
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}君にしてあげたいから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今時を生きる　君にこの歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}精一杯　生きる君に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}この歌を送ろう
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}今日までこんなに苦しんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日からは　楽しく過ごせるよ　きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}だから　君を一人で苦しまないで
Dialogue: 1,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 1,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 1,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 1,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 1,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 1,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 1,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 1,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.32,0:00:13.06,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}你为何而哭泣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.21,0:00:16.78,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}我却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:23.98,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法轻易地说出我懂那样的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.98,0:00:27.29,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.82,0:00:32.65,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}让我知道你为何如此痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:36.95,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那样我才能使出浑身解数
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.03,0:00:43.16,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为你无尽奉献
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.31,0:00:51.31,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}活在当下  赠你这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.31,0:00:55.11,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}为了兢兢业业的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.46,0:00:58.02,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}送上这支歌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.14,0:01:06.77,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}至今为止受尽了此般煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:18.55,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,1500)\blur5}明日起定能活得更加精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.37,0:01:27.80,OPchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}所以  请你不要再独自忧伤
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑んだうしろ姿に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}やさしさで胸がいたくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}こんなに日々がいとおしくて
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}風の音(ね)に　夕闇に　懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}いつまでも一緒だよ、と　叶わぬことくり返し
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}ぬくもりはこの手に
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}あざやかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}受け取った愛を　未来にかえながら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑んだうしろ姿に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}泣きそうな顔を　隠してた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}やさしさで胸がいたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}こんなに日々がいとおしくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}風の音(ね)に　夕闇に　懐かしい君も思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}いつまでも一緒だよ、と　叶わぬことくり返し
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}ぬくもりはこの手に
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}あざやかなまま　生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}忘れたくないもの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDjpb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}受け取った愛を　未来にかえながら
Dialogue: 1,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 1,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 1,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}风声中  夕阳下  回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 1,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}曾说过无论何时都不分离  辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 1,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 1,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 1,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 1,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur2}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.10,0:22:36.47,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}微笑着转身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.69,0:22:43.17,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}藏起那垂泪的脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.89,0:22:49.30,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那般温柔  让人心痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.83,0:22:56.70,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}如此的日子里  让人惋惜不已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:23:09.96,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}风声中  夕阳下  回忆起令人怀念的你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.67,0:23:23.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}曾说过无论何时都不分离  辗转反复着那未完成的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.03,0:23:33.63,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}那温暖在手心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.33,0:23:40.04,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}依旧新鲜富有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.68,0:23:46.92,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}无法忘却之物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.47,0:23:56.67,EDchb,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,300)\blur5}得到的爱逐渐化为未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.61,0:01:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住  臭丫头
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.22,0:01:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腿上的血会流光的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.25,0:01:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵吾之名  命汝等妖物封于阵中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.10,0:01:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切卑劣之物皆化为灰烬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.26,0:02:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切烈过火之物全部铲除
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.08,0:02:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切烈过火之物…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.88,0:02:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.74,0:02:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…救命啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.29,0:02:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  你这家伙  原来是除妖人啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.15,0:02:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.57,0:02:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.94,0:03:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真弱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.88,0:03:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和邻镇的除妖人真是差太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.45,0:03:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说又把我们的同伴整得很惨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.32,0:03:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是叫夏目玲子什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.99,0:03:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我见过那孩子打败妖怪的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.80,0:03:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是个很强的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.46,0:03:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  在哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.56,0:03:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了  在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.94,0:03:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.73,0:03:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目…玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.86,0:03:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里这里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.55,0:03:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目  难得好天气
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.11,0:03:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带我去吃点好吃的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.02,0:03:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才不是请你吃了烤鱿鱼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.79,0:03:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说  老师你根本不分天气  一年四季都在吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.28,0:03:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就像前菜一般塞牙缝的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.59,0:03:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  七辻屋的馒头不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.72,0:04:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  又来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.86,0:04:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  到底要把我带到哪去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.94,0:04:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.76,0:04:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘记我了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.21,0:04:18.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才一阵子不见你  说话的声音变得像男人了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.07,0:04:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.40,0:04:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.27,0:04:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙是她的孙子  你这个冒失鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.61,0:04:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么一说  要是夏目玲子的话也太弱了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.14,0:04:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那玲子在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.73,0:04:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就不在这世上了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.39,0:04:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.40,0:04:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.67,0:04:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.00,0:04:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  那个写了名字的纸呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.72,0:04:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本以为是玲子的话总会有办法解决的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.70,0:04:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是友人帐的话  我已经继承了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.23,0:04:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  夏目玲子的孙子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.54,0:04:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能听一下我的请求吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.56,0:04:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请求？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.79,0:04:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.47,0:05:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有在途中忽然放手的白痴啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.09,0:05:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  尽惹是生非
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.82,0:05:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是什么别的请求
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.91,0:05:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是想请你代替玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.88,0:05:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,召唤出被封印的友人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.36,0:05:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是友人帐上有名字的就行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.60,0:05:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  那家伙现在被封印在一块小石头里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.63,0:05:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来要带他去玲子那里的  一不留神…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.12,0:05:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一不留神？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.36,0:05:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掉进这片森林里了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.31,0:05:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哪个混蛋在这里设陷阱的！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.38,0:05:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  要是再有人被绊倒可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.54,0:05:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么井里会有绳子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.94,0:05:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是上等之水  那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.90,0:06:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.82,0:06:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是结界啊  但是为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.35,0:06:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.06,0:06:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在想是谁呢  这不是那只笨猫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.23,0:06:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.06,0:06:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.30,0:06:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜笨猫所赐  这下子出不去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.88,0:06:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么?!  那么这个结界是你做的？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.49,0:06:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为宠物的你在也就是说  那个男孩也来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.43,0:06:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  没必要告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.79,0:06:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说我也不是什么宠物
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.19,0:06:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个石头  看起来是封印了妖怪在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.35,0:06:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不把你也封印在这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.63,0:06:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,办得到的话就尽管试试
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.01,0:06:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但  那不是你封印的东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.31,0:06:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道得真清楚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.10,0:06:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印之后已经过了很长时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.32,0:06:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力量已经消退得差不多
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.94,0:06:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都快逃出去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.67,0:06:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是看着这数量
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.69,0:07:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道是哪个除妖人做的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.24,0:07:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多半是个只抓低级妖怪的阴险家伙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.39,0:07:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真不留情面啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.99,0:07:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  没事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.65,0:07:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道夏目玲子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.59,0:07:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.39,0:07:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前和她发生了点事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.71,0:07:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  这里面只有一个是我封印的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.17,0:07:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了找到那个我才来这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.27,0:07:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来要花上点时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.77,0:07:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也一时半会儿出不去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.58,0:07:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只是暂时的姿态
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.09,0:07:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恢复本来面目的话  这种井随随便便就能…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.68,0:07:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能怎样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.74,0:07:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.02,0:07:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许正因为是暂时的姿态所以才能通过结界呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.22,0:07:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恢复原本的姿态的话  会怎样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.35,0:07:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说  在这里碰上也是一种缘分
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.69,0:07:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如说说往事  来打发打发时间吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.53,0:07:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出生在除妖人世家的我  一直被认为拥有才能而被抚养着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.67,0:08:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但即使是这样的我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.31,0:08:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也曾有青涩的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.64,0:08:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然对弱小的妖怪产生同情心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.99,0:08:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.03,0:08:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祛除邪恶的妖怪  收服强大的妖怪做式神
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.27,0:08:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除此以外  不要动摇心智
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.55,0:08:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是要成为除妖人的觉悟
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.25,0:08:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.77,0:08:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.92,0:08:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.78,0:08:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！ 昨天的…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.49,0:08:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那件事  详细地说给我听
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.80,0:08:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那件事？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.95,0:08:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目玲子的事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.60,0:08:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在马上  把我带到夏目玲子那儿去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.43,0:08:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  那家伙不仅强大得可怕而且还很凶恶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.40,0:08:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样弱小的人去见了又如何
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.65,0:08:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱小？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.57,0:08:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饶…饶命
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.98,0:09:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说昨天也是  要是你不碍事的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.61,0:09:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会被那家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.04,0:09:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来我家做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.02,0:09:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  想做哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.64,0:09:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈妈啊  会做好仙贝等我们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.52,0:09:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.89,0:09:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是经常早退的女生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.38,0:09:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我见过她在后山嘟囔着什么咒文的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.93,0:09:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且总带着伤
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.95,0:09:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是奇怪的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.72,0:09:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是在这前面的森林见到她的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.00,0:09:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个怎么样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.97,0:09:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是奇怪地自言自语  看了就让人来气
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.21,0:09:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼神也很犀利  是个危险人物
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.54,0:09:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来你见到玲子打算怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.21,0:09:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道要拜玲子为师吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.92,0:09:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行  你们完全是两种人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.63,0:09:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.17,0:10:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭丫头！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.24,0:10:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然是…除妖人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.85,0:10:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除妖人？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.37,0:10:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.46,0:10:40.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙就是夏目玲子！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.59,0:10:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然说我是夏目玲子  真是不得了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.03,0:10:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫做御影
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.18,0:11:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.36,0:11:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是笨蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.64,0:11:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把除妖人叫做玲子的是别的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.12,0:11:08.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他们不好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.25,0:11:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目玲子的名字我也听过
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.55,0:11:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说一碰到妖怪就要求对决然后打倒它们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.63,0:11:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然那个人也是除妖人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.15,0:11:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢  如果是真的话  我也想见她一面
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.20,0:11:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.63,0:11:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是附近采的药草  据说可以不留疤痕地治好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.71,0:11:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！ 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.45,0:11:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  差不多该放了我吧  已经没事了不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.18,0:11:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你找错人的惩罚  老实给我呆着
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.96,0:11:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到夏目玲子你打算做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.69,0:11:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想问问她  问问和我一样看得见妖怪的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.66,0:11:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么区分要除去的妖怪和不用除去的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.18,0:11:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区分？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.22,0:12:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家族一直以来接受委托
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.23,0:12:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该祛除的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.40,0:12:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用作式神的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.28,0:12:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以放任不管的妖怪  这么区分着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.21,0:12:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我觉得妖怪就应该全部祛除掉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.43,0:12:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可怕的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.56,0:12:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的家伙  消失掉最好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.00,0:12:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别人明明看不到  我却可以看得到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.00,0:12:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到外貌以后  就想去搭话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.56,0:12:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去搭话了以后  就会产生感情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.79,0:12:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是绝对不可以和妖怪交心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.82,0:12:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话  这样的家伙干脆都…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.23,0:12:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御影先生怎么认为
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.68,0:12:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想听听像御影这样强大的除妖人的意见
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.19,0:12:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是按照所教的方法去封印而已
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.52,0:12:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被教？ 您的师父  说了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.88,0:12:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是人还是妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.20,0:12:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是凭借强大的自然连锁生存着的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.97,0:13:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是以人为食的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.09,0:13:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是以除妖为生的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.95,0:13:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是彼此之间的「业」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.37,0:13:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「业」？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.52,0:13:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「业」是指没有它就无法生存
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.35,0:13:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犹如生下来就被赋予的使命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.23,0:13:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「业」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.72,0:13:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.78,0:13:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的做法就是将妖怪封印的同时
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.89,0:13:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自身也受到同等的伤害
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.84,0:13:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必在意  这就是我生下来就拥有的「业」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.02,0:13:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能再来见你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.05,0:13:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…想成为像御影一样的除妖人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.14,0:13:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个请求
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.51,0:13:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.43,0:13:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我被妖怪缠上  成为不祥之物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.09,0:14:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以在那之前将我封印吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.06,0:14:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？ 那是…什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.59,0:14:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.81,0:14:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  拿着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.08,0:14:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.41,0:14:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过了几天
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.79,0:14:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又去见那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.27,0:14:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御影先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.33,0:14:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.52,0:14:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  醒醒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.10,0:14:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.41,0:14:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御影先生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.68,0:14:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.52,0:14:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又去哪里休养身体了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.30,0:14:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休养身体？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.82,0:14:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那位先生活不久了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.57,0:14:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟夏目玲子对决的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.60,0:15:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就已经是伤痕累累了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.90,0:15:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟夏目玲子？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.32,0:15:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  先生拜托我找出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.20,0:15:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要和夏目玲子对决呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.76,0:15:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.10,0:15:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于抓到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.61,0:15:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭丫头  这回一定吃掉你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.76,0:15:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.10,0:15:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御影先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.99,0:15:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾为祛除汝而来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.11,0:15:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切灾害之物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.63,0:15:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回归于此玉石之中吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.09,0:15:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.13,0:15:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御影先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.21,0:15:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别过来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.73,0:15:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御影先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.11,0:15:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御影先生  难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.08,0:16:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.50,0:16:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  你怎么在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.63,0:16:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.81,0:16:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这一带你感觉到什么不祥的妖气了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.64,0:16:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有看见过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.84,0:16:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.43,0:16:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个屋子的除妖人去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.86,0:16:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去主人的式神好像在四处游荡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.30,0:16:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,式神吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.72,0:16:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中了被祛除后妖怪的邪气
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.60,0:16:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将会变成能引来灾祸的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.66,0:16:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再去别的地方找找吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.83,0:16:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.14,0:16:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也别在这种地方瞎晃悠  快点回家去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.88,0:16:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御影先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.24,0:16:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你原来是妖怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.43,0:16:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原本就是掉在河床上的石头
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.59,0:16:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找封魔之石的主人找到了我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.36,0:16:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收我做了式神
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.18,0:17:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人命令我封印不祥的妖怪后就去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.15,0:17:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那以后我就缩短自己的寿命做出这些玉石
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.54,0:17:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用来封印妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.49,0:17:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将不祥之物扔进井底就能得到净化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.40,0:17:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回归自然
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.92,0:17:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  若是再继续接受妖怪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.20,0:17:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自身就会变成招引灾祸的东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.28,0:17:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在情况恶化之前
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.58,0:17:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在寻找可以封印我的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.82,0:17:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才去找夏目玲子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.48,0:17:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是被玲子拒绝了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.94,0:17:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一个请求
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.52,0:17:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将我封印掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.39,0:17:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正都要被封印
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.25,0:17:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让像你这样强大的人来封印
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.15,0:17:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做不到  我一点都不强大
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.25,0:17:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你很强大
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.04,0:17:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.60,0:18:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为你了解除妖人的愤怒和悲伤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.14,0:18:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此  这会让你以后变得更加强大
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.19,0:18:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印御影先生  这种事我做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.68,0:18:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印我之事  那就是你的「业」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.90,0:18:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  快动手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.39,0:18:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁我还没有成为灾祸之前
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.78,0:18:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你是认真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.52,0:18:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前不是也受他照顾了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.39,0:18:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也不一定非要这么做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.70,0:18:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那就是御影先生的愿望的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.20,0:18:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想去实现它
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.01,0:18:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬告吾之神灵  封印魔物
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.12,0:18:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,招引灾祸之物  请回到这玉石之中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.79,0:18:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬告吾之神灵  封印魔物
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.56,0:18:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,招引灾祸之物  请回到这玉石之中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.46,0:19:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至此之后  我就不再纠结于祛除妖怪的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.62,0:19:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那就是我的「业」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.76,0:19:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近  听说这里快被拆除了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.90,0:19:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为担心就过来看看  但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.50,0:19:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是因为井的净化之力
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.69,0:19:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印在玉石里的不祥之物都消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.72,0:19:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只有互相帮助一下了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.60,0:19:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经变得微弱的结界由我来解开
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.64,0:19:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结界解开后
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.62,0:19:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带上绳索回到地面上去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.37,0:19:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我就那样扔下绳索跑了  你怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.10,0:19:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样就烦恼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.16,0:19:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.27,0:19:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.39,0:19:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干脆一起将你封印掉好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.19,0:19:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知天高地厚的家伙  别太嚣张了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.24,0:20:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是算了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.67,0:20:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被小鬼怨恨的话就无聊了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.70,0:20:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得应该就在这附近
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.92,0:20:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说那个用玉石封印妖怪的人是什么样的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.59,0:20:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是什么坏人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.91,0:20:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个不必担心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.64,0:20:21.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,影响他的妖气已经消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.07,0:20:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在等待搭救他的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.01,0:20:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近那个结界终于变弱了一点
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.05,0:20:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于可以带出那个小玉石了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.26,0:20:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后又弄丢了  完全没有意义嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.27,0:20:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.04,0:20:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.87,0:20:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.17,0:20:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.69,0:20:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还汝之名  御影
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.16,0:21:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.24,0:21:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直感觉到你在我身边
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.28,0:21:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过了那么多年  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.48,0:21:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子的孙子啊  谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.85,0:21:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御影
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.46,0:21:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想感谢封印我的人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.77,0:21:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来我终于可以从「业」那里解放了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.15,0:21:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.69,0:21:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  我只是恢复到原来的样子而已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.68,0:21:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.54,0:21:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印御影的是什么样的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.52,0:21:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是很了解她的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.00,0:21:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是个有趣的人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.11,0:21:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.39,0:21:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玲子的孙子  让你陪着我  真抱歉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.97,0:21:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.66,0:21:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.06,0:21:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.71,0:21:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在找你呢  夏目  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.23,0:21:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.06,0:22:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛  终于被解放了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.52,0:22:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.56,0:22:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那里发生什么事了吗  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.78,0:22:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啊  没什么大不了的事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.11,0:22:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪天心情好了  就告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.50,0:22:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  真是小气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.17,0:22:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  夏目  刚才完全忘记了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.91,0:22:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去吃七辻屋的馒头吧  走咯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.05,0:22:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  老师  马上就吃晚饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.67,0:22:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馒头…馒头馒头
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.12,0:22:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下啊  老师
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.79,0:22:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糯米馒头
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.65,0:24:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丰月神？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.88,0:24:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是十年一次的月分祭的神明
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.96,0:24:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去寻找那位神明？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.49,0:24:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.08,0:24:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去  山就会荒芜的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.88,0:24:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.67,0:24:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得曾见过像是丰月神等人的生物
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.56,0:24:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  猫咪？
