[Script Info]
Original Script:H&C字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正隶变_GBK,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,15,15,16,1
Style: OP_jp,方正楷体_GBK,33,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,45,1
Style: OP_ch,方正楷体_GBK,36,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&H1EE8EEF4,&H96E8EEF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,20,30,5,1
Style: ED_jp,方正楷体_GBK,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,45,1
Style: ED_ch,方正楷体_GBK,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00958182,&H78FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,3,30,20,5,1
Style: bt,方正楷体_GBK,55,&H0023384E,&HF0000000,&HFF0F0F0F,&H327AB8AC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,3,2,30,30,10,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text



Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.35,0:03:54.18,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被夺走的友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.06,0:01:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从小我就时常会看见奇怪的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.32,0:01:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那大概就是被称为「妖怪」的家伙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.75,0:01:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 你往哪儿踢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.57,0:01:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 危险 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.59,0:01:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 夏目摔下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.04,0:01:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惨了 掉进别人家院子里了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.94,0:01:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.26,0:01:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.23,0:01:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.95,0:02:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 帮忙捡下球吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.25,0:02:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.69,0:02:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,球啊...球呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.11,0:02:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.56,0:02:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看您的长相 您就是夏目大人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.82,0:02:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身上带着友人帐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.16,0:02:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.78,0:02:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 追过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.41,0:02:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这稻绳是...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.25,0:02:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.29,0:02:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来 这场景之前好像也...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.96,0:02:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把友人帐交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.31,0:02:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放...放手
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.01,0:02:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...快交出来 快
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.52,0:02:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 哎呀 吵死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.80,0:02:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫...猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.20,0:02:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又被妖怪缠上了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.02,0:02:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闲着无聊跟你出来转转 没想到又变成这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.08,0:02:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先...先生 透不过气了...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.80,0:03:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蝴蝶呀蝴蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.87,0:03:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出来 交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.06,0:03:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说透不过气来了么!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.84,0:03:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛呀 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.24,0:03:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么干嘛啊 大笨猫
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.82,0:03:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早说过我不是猫了!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.33,0:03:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只不过附身到招财猫上罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.33,0:03:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生你是我的保镖吧 那就该...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.08,0:03:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啧 啧 啧 别以为我只是个保镖哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.61,0:03:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是为了得到友人帐才在等你小命玩完的 可别搞错了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.47,0:03:39.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别得意忘形了 大肥猫
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.83,0:03:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说啥?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.10,0:03:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这蠢货 我一定找机会吃了你!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.41,0:03:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.32,0:04:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收留了无家可归被亲戚们推来让去的我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.32,0:04:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是心地善良的藤原夫妇
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.07,0:04:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵志 吃饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.89,0:04:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.56,0:04:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 贵志 猫吉还没回来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.07,0:04:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午饭也没回来吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.27,0:04:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 大概在外面吃了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.17,0:04:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿了自然会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.42,0:04:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 那就好 来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.11,0:04:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.13,0:04:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 快吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.74,0:04:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,味道不错 这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.13,0:04:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是百合啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.99,0:04:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了不给这个家添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.56,0:04:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用白果试着一起煮来吃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.25,0:04:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.32,0:04:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看得见妖怪这件事要绝对保密
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.45,0:04:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没回房间啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.67,0:04:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是我下手太重了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.12,0:04:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫...猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.47,0:04:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要吓我啊 你去哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.52,0:05:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这身乌鸦黑算怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.86,0:05:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了嘛 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.13,0:05:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.49,0:05:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脏成这副样子就别到处乱转了 真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.62,0:05:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 洗不掉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.30,0:05:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么去了 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.71,0:05:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么不说话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.44,0:05:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在为刚才的事闹别扭么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.64,0:05:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 白天明明是先生你不对嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.65,0:05:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺回来~~啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.42,0:05:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊! 先生?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.98,0:05:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.05,0:05:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊! 那只黑猫是啥啊~~~!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.82,0:05:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙应该是妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.68,0:05:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 不是先生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.54,0:05:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是显而易见的嘛 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.41,0:06:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长着这么大张脸的猫 不多见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.13,0:06:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这家伙就是来冒充先生你的了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.13,0:06:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么目的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.62,0:06:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 夏目 友人帐没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.13,0:06:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 没事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.50,0:06:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.59,0:06:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊 糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.86,0:06:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.77,0:06:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 那只黑猫跑哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.38,0:06:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呿 要在这么黑的地方找只黑猫是不可能了 回头再来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.48,0:06:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是友人帐...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.94,0:06:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是人类 在夜里乱晃太危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.06,0:06:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 总觉得今晚空气中有异样的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.86,0:06:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一会
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.35,0:06:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我再找一会
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.08,0:06:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪们重要的名字都写在那里面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.42,0:07:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.26,0:07:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 先冷静点 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.97,0:07:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然友人帐被抢走了你可能觉得很不甘心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.82,0:07:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我并没从那只黑猫身上感受到恶意
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.66,0:07:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我也疏忽大意了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.98,0:07:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且现在要是大肆宣扬\N让其他妖怪知道友人帐失窃的事就麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.94,0:07:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.94,0:07:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些光是?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.93,0:07:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 鬼火啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.20,0:07:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼火?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.50,0:07:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不少 这是要去哪儿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.61,0:07:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.97,0:07:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.68,0:07:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有人类的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.15,0:07:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先...先生 压死我了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.77,0:07:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.97,0:07:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在用我的气味蒙混过关
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.16,0:07:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是错觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.58,0:07:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为是人类的味道 原来是狐臭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.98,0:08:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然敢说是狐臭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.65,0:08:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这么高贵伟大的我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.62,0:08:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 算了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.74,0:08:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 以前主人总是带着人类的味道回来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.50,0:08:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是啊 扮成人类和那些家伙一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.20,0:08:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.19,0:08:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还常常给我们带美味的人间特产
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.95,0:08:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 那些臭人类 和他们扯上关系总没什么好事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.27,0:08:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.88,0:08:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去了么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.65,0:08:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是斑大人么 许久不见了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.85,0:08:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何时您的身姿都是如此美丽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.37,0:08:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 你是...红峰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.86,0:08:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是先生的熟人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.45,0:08:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.80,0:08:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀 人类啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.20,0:08:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您是在用餐吗 请务必也赏我一口
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.66,0:08:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这张脸 好像在哪里...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.88,0:08:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 夏目铃子!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.95,0:08:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢材 太大声了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.80,0:09:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 是夏目铃子的孙子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.03,0:09:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红峰 刚刚那群妖怪是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.65,0:09:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 森林里的妖怪们准备聚到一起开宴会
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.56,0:09:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯... 在这一带有没有看到一只叼着本簿子的可爱黑猫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.98,0:09:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.94,0:09:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你说那只大脸肥猫的话 刚才往会场方向去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.50,0:09:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?! 肥猫!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.09,0:09:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是它 红峰小姐 能带我们过去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.45,0:09:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没搞错吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.77,0:09:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类一过去马上就会被吃掉的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.82,0:09:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就装成妖怪去 拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.66,0:09:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无论如何都必须找到那只猫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.27,0:09:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连这不知天高地厚的眼神也很像铃子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.11,0:09:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您就是中意他这点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.04,0:09:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白痴啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.49,0:09:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说些有的没的就吃了你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.13,0:09:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很有趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.88,0:09:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 那我就给你们带路吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.52,0:09:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能装得万无一失当然没事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.18,0:10:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但万一被揭穿那就只好请你当大家的晚餐了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.23,0:10:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.66,0:10:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.28,0:10:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又自作主张...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.31,0:10:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊! 斑大人变成小不点了!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.02,0:10:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可悲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.48,0:10:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝酒是往这边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.78,0:10:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是去喝酒的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.86,0:10:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 夏目你必须化妆假扮
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.83,0:10:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑大人您也不可以显露原形哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.84,0:10:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 为啥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.20,0:10:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟 夏目铃子太有名了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.37,0:10:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且听说友人帐现在在一个带着妖怪长\N相像铃子的少年手上
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.08,0:10:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这传闻可是满天飞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.84,0:10:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.16,0:10:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 我们要照顾那孩子到什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.93,0:10:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是没办法嘛 大哥也不愿意...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.66,0:11:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 欢迎回家 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.06,0:11:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来得正好 找到了点铃子外婆的遗物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.48,0:11:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃子?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.61,0:11:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你外婆哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.93,0:11:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 这什么啊 涂鸦本?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.75,0:11:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就听说她是个怪人 果然如此啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.73,0:11:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是扔了吧 贵志
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.04,0:11:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种东西拿着也没什么用
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.49,0:11:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.54,0:11:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生来就拥有强大灵力的外婆 铃子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.81,0:11:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让被打败的妖怪写下名字以此来缔结主从关系的契约书
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.47,0:11:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时我对友人帐和铃子的事还一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.58,0:11:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.91,0:11:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.65,0:11:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑大人您就打算用这副尊容么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.03,0:11:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.09,0:11:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.22,0:11:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.03,0:12:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 红峰啊 来得这么晚 干啥去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.59,0:12:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是失礼 我去化妆了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.19,0:12:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀 面生的家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.83,0:12:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是我带来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.76,0:12:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很有趣啊 让我们也加入吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.46,0:12:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 来来 一起喝点酒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.13,0:12:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你身上好像有点人类的臭味
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.33,0:12:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 让我想起主人了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.07,0:12:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是啊 主人也总是散发着人类的气味呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.67,0:12:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.68,0:12:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是这座与世隔绝的森林的头领
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.38,0:12:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化成人形进入村子时掉进了抓狐狸的陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.09,0:12:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被一个猎人救了后就经常化身人类去见他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.15,0:12:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说后来他还高兴地和那个人类成了朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.65,0:12:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人虽然有强大妖力但脑子却不太好使呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.08,0:13:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然和人类做朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.61,0:13:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 还和那个叫夏目铃子的女人决斗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.92,0:13:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 喝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.93,0:13:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.02,0:13:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 各位有谁在附近见到过一只黑...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.03,0:13:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了诸位 下面来谈正事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.78,0:13:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的人类封印主人的地方已经知晓了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.28,0:13:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在正是报仇的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.86,0:13:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人对我们有大恩大德
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.83,0:13:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将力量分给了我们这些住在森林里的低等妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.24,0:13:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚将进行夜袭!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.41,0:13:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要对人类有所畏惧!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.92,0:13:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起上的话 人类就是不堪一击!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.79,0:13:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜袭是怎么回事?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.22,0:13:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人偷袭过一次家禽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.42,0:13:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以被人类封印了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.41,0:13:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过那个封印的地方终于被我们找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.84,0:13:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在红色大石墙房子的地板下面
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.42,0:14:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 但也没必要袭击房子里的人类吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.24,0:14:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没有必要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.11,0:14:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这帮家伙喝成这样不知道会做出什么事来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.64,0:14:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.99,0:14:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不要再多管闲事了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.58,0:14:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这阵势不是简简单单就能阻止得了的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.71,0:14:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊是啊 别管了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.95,0:14:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底仅凭个人的力量实在也过于渺小
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.98,0:14:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.38,0:14:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是幸好我还能听到你的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.16,0:14:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这里所有的妖怪 以及人类说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.68,0:14:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些能清晰明了地进入我耳中\N是否这也可以成为一种力量呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.21,0:14:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和铃子不同呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.69,0:14:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了! 给我站住!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.24,0:14:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个让人搞不懂的小鬼 您看中他哪里了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.33,0:15:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感兴趣的只是友人帐罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.42,0:15:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话赶紧把他吃掉 抢过来不就好了么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.45,0:15:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是不错的消遣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.82,0:15:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的一生太过短暂了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.56,0:15:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短暂到乏味的程度
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.38,0:15:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抓到了 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.04,0:15:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙还真是老实呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.70,0:15:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只黑猫是故意的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.60,0:15:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,故意的?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.88,0:15:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仿佛是故意抢走友人帐引我们到这里一样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.07,0:15:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.40,0:15:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.96,0:15:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红峰 你有这能力吧 给我查一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.56,0:15:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就让我来试试
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.19,0:15:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这恐怕是只非常强大的妖怪被封印附身在里面了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.98,0:16:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,附身吗 现在流行这种么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.93,0:16:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这股妖气 好像似曾相识
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.67,0:16:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是主人!?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.48,0:16:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.38,0:16:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.81,0:16:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的人类啊 竟然将您封印了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.68,0:16:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明被封印了 却还能走动 难道...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.52,0:16:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有红色高石墙的房子...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.12,0:16:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道 那时候弄断的稻绳就是封印这只黑猫的结界?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.92,0:16:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红峰 快点通知大家
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.81,0:16:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个样子的话 谁都不会相信这就是主人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.05,0:16:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不解开封印让他恢复原形的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.20,0:16:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是要怎么做呢...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.76,0:16:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 刚才那群低级妖怪们有说这家伙和铃子决斗过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.98,0:16:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是这么说来着
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.95,0:16:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.89,0:16:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许就是因为名字被夺走了才没有力量打破封印吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.38,0:16:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那把名字还给他的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.11,0:16:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但问题就是那个名字
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.65,0:17:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是附身的话 友人帐是不能自动找到他的名字的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.80,0:17:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红峰 主人的名字是?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.32,0:17:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直只是叫主人的...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.48,0:17:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人大人 我一定会把名字还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.02,0:17:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以请赐予我力量来阻止大家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.94,0:17:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在这干啥呢 差不多该出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.58,0:17:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出发是指去袭击人类吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.90,0:17:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本没那个必要 主人已经回来了!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.76,0:17:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 别...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.35,0:17:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有谁知道主人的名字吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.25,0:17:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要知道名字的话 主人就...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.75,0:17:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙是人类吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.40,0:17:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.80,0:17:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.16,0:17:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.39,0:17:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.77,0:17:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 一边去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.60,0:17:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.31,0:18:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静心倾听 这当中...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.48,0:18:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定会有知道主人的名字的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.56,0:18:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.27,0:18:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开夏目!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.67,0:18:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.50,0:18:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「狸追 归还汝名 收下吧」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.96,0:18:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.78,0:18:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狸追大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.92,0:18:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是主人大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.51,0:18:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.79,0:19:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.00,0:19:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.21,0:19:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类啊 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.60,0:19:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托你的福 我能走动之后 去见了重要的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.15,0:19:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他已经不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.33,0:19:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类的一生真是短暂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.65,0:19:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总算能理解大家为什么说我是傻瓜了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.41,0:19:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要拿走友人帐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.73,0:19:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到森林后
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.38,0:20:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到大家打算为我去袭击村民
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.73,0:20:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有力量去阻止他们的我 只有将你带过来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.18,0:20:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能来做点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.82,0:20:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 夏目
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.85,0:20:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印你的也是人类吧 但你却会去阻止妖怪们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.23,0:20:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我喜欢人类啊 所以再也不会去人类那里了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.87,0:20:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗澡很舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.83,0:20:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永别了 人类
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.78,0:20:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永别了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.79,0:20:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了呢 黑猫
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.04,0:20:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑色的猫咪 还真是很可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.60,0:21:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思啊你 也不想想是谁帮你解围的啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.23,0:21:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 既然斑大人的伤也不重
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.97,0:21:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我先回去咯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.43,0:21:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是无法喜欢上人类呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.34,0:21:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来还想为了斑大人找机会吃了你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.01,0:21:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你又是主人大人的恩人 自然不能那样做了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.16,0:21:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斑大人 不一起回去吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.06,0:21:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了 我暂时还是待在他身边好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.20,0:21:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到他那「短暂的一瞬」过去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.81,0:21:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你呢 猫先生
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.39,0:21:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 你直率得真叫人恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.14,0:21:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近在心里挥之不去的 是小小离别所带来的寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.34,0:21:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论短暂的分别还是片刻的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.67,0:22:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一分每一秒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.03,0:22:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都想要将它们好好珍藏起来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.96,0:23:50.99,bt,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(370,550)}雪化之后是春天
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.08,0:23:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字是?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.11,0:23:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫玄
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.42,0:23:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏目大人 请帮帮我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.89,0:23:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是柴原的石像吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.40,0:23:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得应该是2尊的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.97,0:23:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外一位怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.53,0:23:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翠她...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.66,0:23:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.63,0:23:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经...

Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.57,0:00:03.86,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.97,0:00:06.54,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.71,0:00:11.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.76,0:00:14.45,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:19.48,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:23.40,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 少しだけ大人の色に染まる指先
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:38.08,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 指尖稍露成年的沧桑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 照れくさそうに そっと隠して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:43.37,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 你就害羞得将它悄悄收起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 頬杖ついた君 見つめてる視線の先に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.42,0:00:48.74,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 手托下巴的你将视线投向
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 小さな蕾が ゆらゆら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.91,0:00:54.06,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 那随风轻曳的小小花蕾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} ねぇ 僕なんて いまも迷いばかりで
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:59.63,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 喂 现在的我仍迷茫依旧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} あの日贈った言葉 今さら思い出す
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.78,0:01:04.67,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 这才回想起 那日你的临别赠言
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「君色に未来染めて...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.73,0:01:07.01,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 「将我的未来染成你的颜色...」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 走り出せ前向いて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:09.83,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 奔跑出发吧 勇往直前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} かじかむ手で空に描いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.83,0:01:12.46,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 冻僵的手在空中描绘出
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 君の未来に祝福の灯りともす
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.61,0:01:17.76,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 点亮你未来的祝福之灯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 切り開け その手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.83,0:01:20.30,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 勇敢开拓吧 用这双手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 聞こえてるかい? この声が
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.38,0:01:22.88,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 是否能听见 我的呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 素直に笑える事 抱きしめ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.04,0:01:25.56,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 珍惜这挂着纯真笑容的岁月
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 今 走り出せ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.64,0:01:28.52,OP_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,80)} 就是现在 迈出你的步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:10.45,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ 聞いていてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.76,0:22:18.38,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 听我倾诉好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}ねぇ もう少しだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.15,0:22:23.37,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我说 只要再一点点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう少しだけ わがままいいですか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.73,0:22:30.66,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要再一点点的 让我任性好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手に入れた途端に消えてしまいそう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.21,0:22:38.01,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}拥有的瞬间仿佛就会消散
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}言葉をくれませんか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.17,0:22:42.74,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不说点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あなたがいる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.93,0:22:45.59,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}因为有你在
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}それだけで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:49.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}只要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}もう世界が変わってしまう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.16,0:22:56.26,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}我的世界就会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}モノトーンの景色が ほら 鮮やかに映る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:23:08.13,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}映入眼眸的单调景色也会光鲜亮丽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}いつのまにか 離れていた
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.35,0:23:14.53,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}不知何时却已离开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}手を繋いで歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.76,0:23:22.02,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}牵着手 向前走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}上手く愛せているかな
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.75,0:23:28.93,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}能够好好去爱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_jp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}あの空に聞いてみるの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:34.67,ED_ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(350,350)}天空也许会回答
